<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[to them by nation-states. During this era, merchants, who had traded under the previous stage of mercantilism, inve… https://t.co/bMuqyrj6LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pregnancy Rant: I bought a box of LIMITED EDITION Birthday snack cakes on Friday for myself! It’s sad when you have… https://t.co/CRUbQuUkqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t know that day would be today. Adults who “cringe” when seeing my beautiful baby because issues they have wit… https://t.co/HTu3cMHiMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex! 😻🐈😇 #happycaturday #gingercat #teamginger #thankful #love #alexstevens @ Norwalk, California https://t.co/5F6fp7UHdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unisex spanish knot distresses brown leather bracelet with leather… https://t.co/uPlfvvWMfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buddy_earth @Model3Owners I see a retail opportunity to help save the Earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonatha97947998 @mabel_carrera @AngelosOnassis @Lunarteddy @malucadua @RasnawatiR @AintitMarvelous @heroldbarton… https://t.co/JDjow8KXoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would go to law school just so I could divorce Bradley Cooper and Irina Shayk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraSantaMaria hey! I was wondering if you had a past agenda for @SciCommCamp you can share? Trying to pass more i… https://t.co/PSOXzkB2kq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crying through mascara and sweating off your ashes are the same look, and both mean you’re in for an extra sinful year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump That photo has been proven wrong a long time ago. It’s a pic from ear… https://t.co/88SYx2ZXnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the police have identified him. We should  hear soon. What a bully! #LockHimUp!]]></document><document><![CDATA[idgaf if they’re black, I’m not saying free no nigga/bitch that’s killing/shooting/stabbing/etc., anybody. y’all fried.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalReporter @QueenVicMirror @chrisshipitv @guardian One side of the DOS family's word is taken as fact in spite… https://t.co/VOgXrJKhz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, all joking aside, she's probably thrown up now about a dozen times, not an exaggeration. I think she may have s… https://t.co/c9YTHTAp06]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 more newbies. Sweet momma chi and her adorable son 😍.  Mom has collar but no chip or tags and baby is wearing a f… https://t.co/X3ziWOaWWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you missed this the first time around, #MichaelCohen was the National Deputy Vice Chairman for the… https://t.co/l8m5s8vWJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@08wvdcfan Theu don't do bloopers very often but this https://t.co/oU5Eg7WTbb both great and  funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMerkley @JacquelineHine1 Get it fleshed out as legislation. All Dems want to deal with climate change. We also… https://t.co/azudhULxOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inertiauk I think I remember reading an interview with Alex and he came up with the idea? I could be wrong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom found her true identity yesterday 😂😂 I see no difference 😂 https://t.co/2wRJSC9n4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤ Had so much fun sharing creative Spring craft ideas on WATE 6 news with the amazing Kelli Smith and the whole cre… https://t.co/swHADvoEfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGelb @antwanstaley @JSalisburyNBCS If Phillies or Harper felt like each other were their first (or even second… https://t.co/JIogxF7arI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefBinedu Over E’s, OVARIES?! Yo come onnnnn that is crazy wordplay. Stop it now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz Please get out of the way of Democrats who can win. Please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my spirit animal.....it's been way too long! ❤️ @ Raleigh Wine Bar + Eatery https://t.co/Gfiy2qPYKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalimbaMX no me sale el video de como participar para ganarme los boletos pero... https://t.co/b6yMcsiaJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvelynChoni I mean it’s good for them I guess to have a small break cause they’re always together but hopefully th… https://t.co/l0qJjAYDDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just hanging out in my favorite #familyroom at 3321 N. Oakley while we finish filming this video. #realestate… https://t.co/XCu84UMqlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I always find out about these days when it's too late to do anything?  #PatronMargarita]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got the microphone at senior night and told everyone to follow my instagram and twitter and I haven’t gotten one follow. Crying!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might have to see if we can get @theestallion to pop out if she in the Lou 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got rid of all my negative shit in my life before my birthday tomorrow. I’m about to have the best year of my fucki… https://t.co/p7Swvtsxgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopThird @Tyne_Ag @AnnaLaca1 I said the exact same when I read this statement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LioConvoy85 Cause you squeezed the back of their head... ... obviously...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SKMMarkedUp @cheekysu If you don't have specific shows, TKTS for day-of. Many shows do day-of rush (sometimes onli… https://t.co/wMohFITQMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He just jumped the f**king fence” is the best part of Chris Harrison’s 648282 year run on the Bachelor. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerweber @atrupar @foxandfriends I can’t watch it even for a half second. It’s pure propaganda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is the picture i get from my mother after she tells me my dog ATE MY RANDAZZOS KING CAKE!!!!!!!!!!! https://t.co/pAfQZnBjsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightFighter5 @jhofromcanton @senrobportman Oh please, you piece of shit. Portman's done. Same goes for Dirty Don.… https://t.co/uM3kzWLlgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our ability to heal is like our ability to overcome evil—non existent. Therefore the transformation and inner purif… https://t.co/p7tfto51Ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[*cough* witness tampering...*cough*...blackmail...*cough*...*clears throat*...excuse me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident just happened on one of my campuses, and they just emailed to tell us that we won’t be closing, and we’ll… https://t.co/Eh6JoKUnkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's mood brought to you by Kimbra Lyn portrait https://t.co/6wXjkHDVyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go.... @RedCon1Official ⠀ The best Shape that we have ever brought to the stage. 💪🏼 ⠀ This year, unfortunat… https://t.co/GqTOZ7GJsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@cerrito, @GregAkers, and I brainstorm crazy Memphis ideas for our #CerritoLive Think Tank series. We’ve done team… https://t.co/Jdb8eU0s6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nazariteoracle @BET You're the kind of people that prefer the Clinton's Crime Bill that imprisoned over 300,000 Bl… https://t.co/O22blTxea2]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a left handed person, I’m offended there’s no left handed writing emoji. Also as a left handed person, I underst… https://t.co/14eUVBhMbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff GOP=Liars.  Your ethics bill will be routed by Mitch and GOP.  Why?  They don't want to go to jail f… https://t.co/43OjKMxNal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS I loved Blockbuster my best friend worked there.....I would help her finish up at night just because.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I submitted my paper at 5.30am and received the grade and comment from my professor at 6.45am.  Like y’all don’t sleep?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathyhadenough @canadiandaws83 @ShaunaPembroke @Ummismaelsf @Eathbound420 @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16… https://t.co/yba5Z95oeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We saw this a lot with Annie this weekend - it’s helpful to know the signs! https://t.co/Wf1niAs9TE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day late but I’m ready for this catty #WomenTellAll #thebachelor https://t.co/0757hCDppu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HappyTedVault @CoreysDigs It is horrifying to say the least! I am sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I remember I don't have a bf to buy stuff I think they'd like for https://t.co/GGMiOOkfO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowcountry1Girl @Balind8 @AOC So tired of seeing her name. She and her kind need to be kept out of the news! Are t… https://t.co/3bEShA0zli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GTA_Redhead @magnumCJ Right? I do enough dumb shit without being encouraged to do something dangerous lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[An untold number of workers are about to get screwed.  File this under “Elections have consequences.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[if she passes Muslims are not allowed to make duaa for her so please make as much as you can for now]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾  Everyone wants to be outraged &amp; oppressed. We’re tired. Let us be happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fabulous @tschaffer1 and I are volunteering to judge for the @WCHS_Warriors / @msdwarren speech team at State t… https://t.co/jvS9qukQTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s just something about this city that makes me want to live back here again]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the roads travelled adventures taken, kids bundled together on our journey, I am so grateful for this man at my… https://t.co/1caWupRkXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may be the best slide I've ever created in my life. https://t.co/ekeySZvL1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 For Pete's sake. This should be interesting, I know many Republicans whose kids are selling the cookies! hmmm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump That’s a good one for trump, don’t understand how he had a ‘good’ education and yet… https://t.co/LBHOc9w5YQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatRU4USA @realTrumpForce Who?  Do you mean heterosexuals in straight relationships???  😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other news my 80yo patient told me I should join Match today so I can meet a nice man am I really that pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamelaPrattles I used to watch it like every day when it came out on VHS back in the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EatonRifles1 @krassenstein Btw, I looove your profile picture! I’m a rescue mommy myself. For years I had pure bre… https://t.co/CYHfUvHwn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t sleep bc I’m so excited that I’m real life gonna see @GGYOUNGBOY at @thejmblya 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning ppl! Back to grind  😕.... Make it a good day! @ McAllen, Texas https://t.co/7p5ms9mapg]]></document><document><![CDATA[How sweet! All of the @PTXofficial guys posted lovely, heartfelt individual messages for their friend and musical s… https://t.co/saS4qaNZ8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[What else are you supposed to do on a rainy Saturday?!? 🤷🏻‍♀️ At least I’m able to get #chores done while everyone… https://t.co/KsADeKqGNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dneedles12 I still can’t believe you’re there! Soo jealous! That’s on my bucket list!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ieVincentDemers Dans votre comparaison, vous parlez d’un examen final pour une spécialité en médecine exigé par le Collège des médecins ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ⬇️ Thread pretty much shows my confusion as to how little time Manafort was sentenced to today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiek_johnson @NCCATNews More to come! We get to work together twice this year! #NCCAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealstylesp Lmao it’s funny until it happens to me 🤣 https://t.co/8FGes5y6WE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PlayStation Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/Btln8nFMOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the heaven  he would go to hell for.  Natures Allure 🌿 @ Plaza Midwood https://t.co/HKGMtL4X1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to My Big Baby @davidealy1 #Pisces #Piscesseason #Seventeen #Mybaby #Mommasboy #Blackboysrock… https://t.co/hGXJLHTrsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pearly16065727 @mom_norie Ako / kami  sa dalawa lng...support lng sa TS or movie.. ( kahit sabihin ng mga mulats o… https://t.co/IyyUORhswp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un @AccionJuvenil fuerte da esperanza al futuro de @AccionNacional   2da reunión de secretarios estatales.    Mucho… https://t.co/GKOY8pKhVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtuallyBeth @TheXquisiteH @HoarseWisperer It’s the heartbreak of cases like this which make me miss criminal law a little less. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @mdwhite121, for inviting me to guest lecture for your Intro to Policing class at @asuwestcampus. I spok… https://t.co/lVXc6AowPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayedathickest Here’s my amazing friends side of the story. I love her! She a real ride or die 💓💓💓 https://t.co/RcPM7w8a1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m supposed to wear blue or green today for a work thing but I only own black 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING performance last night!!!👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾 So glad I could experience it with these young leaders! #sunrisevcs… https://t.co/E9PYKpYINt]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the snowdrifts continue to build out my window...this could not come at a better time. #EverybodyIn #FlyTheW… https://t.co/Tdb9BN1ffV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travelwithirine @RoadtripC @GatewayArchNPS @TouringTastebud @MadHattersNYC @MattsRoadTrip @suziday123… https://t.co/iy2ppn5qLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nearpod if I just got certified how do I level up to gold for free?? #nearpodchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriswwright1 YES #SPEAKINGLIFE brother Christopher W. Wright   GOD BE PRAISED!!!☝️✝️🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little girl just asked if I had a boyfriend and I said no I don’t need one and she said yes you do you’re lonely🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @JarBomb @RadioFreeTom Yeah another scum @realDonaldTrump as unearth to be part of his #scumgang wit… https://t.co/p48FPs7D4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meg said that if we get married i’m not allowed to put Brandi Carlile on the playlist :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo que considerar la posibilidad de que a Dios no le caes bien Fight Club]]></document><document><![CDATA[Styled and shot by my husband @JeraldM.  . #calvinklein #ckest1978 @ Kinfolk 90 https://t.co/knYCNOCMzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ante medios de comunicación expusimos la problemática que viven en este momento trabajadoras de estancias y guarder… https://t.co/FSM0RsJuZf]]></document></documents></author>