<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Mercy Health? We're hiring in #Festus, MO! Click for details: https://t.co/4qAz55rLPs #Physician]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paigeeeeeo Too bad they didn’t do likethey did with the Kiss ones a few years ago where you could order a custom o… https://t.co/AaXtoAZZ8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather needs to make up its mind bc my jackets are taking up half my closet...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shadow Reason 1: I worked with fantastic students for a team math game.  I haven’t simplified expressions with expo… https://t.co/idu20nEQSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaniaArth @plavaraja Multiple call sheets, and multiple articles from production stating Galo was the DP. More than gossip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Just wow. If you get a chance to see @Lynnbrooklyn ‘s words brought to life and leap off the page- go!  It’s g… https://t.co/6ewCGnqFaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magggiemayy @MVP_Linds Ok so sure the step mom is absolutely a terrible person but i didn’t see her forcing her da… https://t.co/NUAt1AWEuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would @directtv assume that I would like to renew my Sunday ticket and bill me 48.99 for the next 6 months. The season just ended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk People like her should be jailed on charges of being menace to society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leafer1984 Seriously!!!! This is the laziest I’ve seen them play throughout the whole trip!! So disappointing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msbedlam_caz @DoItToJulia5 @ABRadFems @TeelaWild @MorganeOgerBC @preta_6 @FeministCurrent What was Julia doing the… https://t.co/4pVcmtFe8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I AM MOST COMFORTABLE WHEN... March 30daysoflists . #idocument #photojournal #memorykeeping… https://t.co/E2f4WRqI6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @LeslieSanchez Yep. What do we expect from a guy that went bankrupt 6 times?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, engineer is moving on to the final round. #ItWillCut #ForgedInFire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiedermannJoey This could not be less true but thanks for the attention buddy 😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's Day.       #nolisafilter ☕⚡💗 @ Carlsbad, California https://t.co/MJq9UDRJES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a parking ticket after paying $200 for a parking pass that doesn’t guarantee u a spot is just the icing on… https://t.co/qIs97U3tS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 de febrero.  Si nadie te dijo ¡feliz día! Yo te lo deseo, tal vez no soy la persona que esperabas pero lo hago de corazón.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, thinking my boss forgot about no school tomorrow: 😎 my boss: u come in at 8am:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I’m cleaning the house I never do one thing at a time , I always get distracted 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hellapercent Who tf is gonna take the watch dude, you just don’t wanna admit that you misplaced it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning and Happy Monday🤗! Hopefully this cute clip gets you up and ready to take on the day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oiselle @PattyMurray @SenWarren @SenGillibrand @SenKamalaHarris @amyklobuchar ✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Match Alert🚨  🆚 Saginaw Lady Rough Riders  📆 Fri, March 1st ⏰ Varsity 7:30pm 🏟 SHS Stadium ⏰ JVA 6:00pm  ⏰ JVB 4:3… https://t.co/NxICNrcSnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy there are fake people in your life that present themselves to be so caring and so loving. Stories are wr… https://t.co/Y73k23GGUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsayDurr @laddhuasteco We love and miss you too! You’re one of kind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mytweetology @washingtonpost ..and I suppose if you were raped, and became pregnant, you would have no issues, no… https://t.co/YgscSOfp46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood @JonSummersdc Actually 29% and 33% are encouraging. These people aren't saying no to impeachment. The… https://t.co/Mc3tw0cB0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youth Opportunity Hubs Anniversary https://t.co/SuD6gpCk0y via @YouTube .@NMICnyc is proud to be a part of the @nyphospital Youth Hub.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any time you catch me bragging about a professional accomplishment on Twitter dot com, you can rest assured that it… https://t.co/wKsUmuoonu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenwoodBCPS share the reasons why you #LoveTeaching students and how they impact you! https://t.co/xEQsuOhgFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader How about having a "chat" with your boy Matt (Witness Tampering brings me Joy!) Gaetz. You claimed you'd… https://t.co/WKQe28l2w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positive vibes only in my school 🥰♥️🥰♥️ @elvisduran https://t.co/uB0TvvRuZM #epicday @DonorsChoose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakebradley99 @indstateDM @derekhough Swing dancing was the best dance to learn and build on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently this airline has a good reputation so I wonder what produced this horrific result... 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parscale @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @ewarren @JulianCastro @gillibrandny @amyklobuchar @BetoORourke Republican LIAR.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clinton camp cable news pundits continue 2016 primary with new round of Bernie smears:  1) private planes 2) doesn'… https://t.co/FSwNNOMYyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 I'm so sorry. When my son was in the hospital they sent pain specialists . Ask if yours has them. They were awesome and helpful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to 2 former Ss for stopping by yesterday! I am so proud of you! Keep reaching for your dreams! @JacobSpeaks_ https://t.co/c1cgsFlqXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bday din with my biddies ❤️ (@ Brass Union in Somerville, MA) https://t.co/cgRIUjtFNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[do any of my friends have a good camera they want to take one picture for me?? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@srebeducation @gedtophd Craig was a keynote speaker for the Missouri AlternatEducation Network a couple of years ago!! He is amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec People care more about what the Smith's think about them down the road but could careless about the o… https://t.co/HzGE9VgCQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sculpture intro lesson 2D into 3D &amp; art collaboration https://t.co/FzmylsuYtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@applejvck01 @AmoyNelson Westbrook and Creed on May 16, she ran a 12.76 in the 100 and 26.23 in the 200. Shoreline… https://t.co/wq816OByHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only one I’d be crossing my fingers for him to NOT say is Bucky...I don’t like him or the person who plays him]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all respect to Denver...  I was in love after this....my mind was blown. I loved the Que Dawg Mr. FAMU before… https://t.co/98MXcQWfd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing a very happy birthday to the incomparable, legendary @TheMickyDolenz1! Hope you have a wonderful day and a… https://t.co/6sObeww1Mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByDonkeys @Ajad_d Funny, this billboard sounds like a Trump tweet.  We're being scammed on both sides of the Atlantic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call get every Muslim out of our government now Obama put alot get them out we want our government back each state… https://t.co/vY7971AKCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__Macmane__ In that case I’d expect some foot fetish, not the trash that’s been following me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acoustic version of Sahara Love Seven Lions remix. I’m speaking it into existence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 29: Check your natural gas rates.  Most natural gas providers have Fixed Therm pricing when you’re on contract.… https://t.co/3Qr27oMMPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can fight off all the darkness that comes into this world I believe in you and you believe me trust each other… https://t.co/zb22a9wHRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpreed11 @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump This must be the day Trump forgot his DEPENDS! https://t.co/M0MPbHvSz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/n5WaSfgtQb al melón capo narco y delincuente criminal @dcabellorcmd. No amenaces a nuestro presidente… https://t.co/w1FS62YCvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello #2019  Hair Bundles Deals 💃💃💃  Geisha Art of Hair  Online booking available  Shipping available 🤗🤗🤗… https://t.co/7cWJk5kR5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business Insider: Amazon could be gearing up to reveal Walmart, Kroger, and Aldi's worst nightmare. https://t.co/UXXyoDKZPg  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AMC Loews Liberty Tree Mall 20 - @amctheatres for Isn't It Romantic in Danvers, MA https://t.co/HjALqByhaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling so good after a facial and using my new skin care products before bed 😍❤️ https://t.co/5pN33jOQnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkenTigerJK Wishing you all everything you strive for. Fighting!!! https://t.co/eQcOuYuqfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday, hope you’ve had a great day💓💗  @allisonfv_ https://t.co/5sSWhAHmeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola 👋 @PotrankaOficial Votamos por el tema #QueNoTeFalleElCorazón de @AlexisMusicMX  en #ElElevadordelaKebuena… https://t.co/Omou6oQf9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[A strong woman builds others up because she knows what it's like to be torn down. https://t.co/Krcb4O9iRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanKellyMusic @byrneandkelly @neilbyrne_CT @CelticThunder @nicolehudson81 Can’t wait!! My aunt and I will be watching from Virginia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @SenFeinstein No matter how you slice it she basically told them that the plan to save the planet w… https://t.co/SC1AvTboJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or President is working for the people and our country, he can’t be bought or told what to do. He is exposing so mu… https://t.co/zIx7KI9Scl]]></document><document><![CDATA[the biggest ideas are often the most criticized. https://t.co/iOOJOInRun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone want to give ya girl a ride to the airport at 7 cause my fam ain’t doing it 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenatorCarper for hosting Service Academy Night @delawaretech #dtcc #NetDE https://t.co/vrMzLo0DSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 This absolutely makes no sense! How lame is that? Is she going to boycott dancing because AOC was videoed dancing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter where children are in the world, take a moment to place your child’s face on them, and then look again at… https://t.co/1gPW2ttaqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If everyone close to you is telling you the same thing, believe them. They see it clearer than you do right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pop into one of our Career Day presentation at AIMS! https://t.co/yaNoBwbKVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread may just be the most awesome thing on the Internet right now. Wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I’m more sensitive because I work with little kids but the whole momo thing is not funny to me at all :( chil… https://t.co/XiPkXaE15q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EQLife11 If I had more notice, I’d already have cookies sent your way! Give me like 12 hours next time??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy takeoff to @atlairport @southwestair @sandiegoairport @ San Diego International Airport https://t.co/nqcIWQioYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t matter how many times you do it, driving across the bridge into Manhattan is still one of the greatest views]]></document><document><![CDATA[For reasons unknown there is a fleet of bicycle cops pulling everybody over on the Belvedere bridge so look alive #rva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson @IngrahamAngle @TheFive @seanhannity https://t.co/EDeI7hR19g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigFellaAndJo @GrahamAllen_1 @realDonaldTrump Only the kiddie diddlers in congress hate him. Trump trying to put us in first place again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oliver Mora... ang laki ng problema mo sa La Salle. Natural lang naman sa players yun pag nagcocontest ng call.… https://t.co/1RQOqxlRRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of Bespin from the plane. #cloud #cloudcity #bespin #sky #blue @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/LIiHCBGH0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @DeptofDefense #AI strategy researching “emergent effects,” which is what happens when two artificial intelligenc… https://t.co/OebrAm3qv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicoxw1 @rkelly you remind me of OJ!! A Big MOUTH &amp; GUILTY as SIN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daisymarquez_ I'm still emo so.... 🤷🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/zmxFAFooMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing but stage!!!!!! Woo Hoo!!!! pinklucy74  @jtimberlake #manofthewoodstour @ Golden 1 Center https://t.co/yK2THf127L]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@carolinajuniors 14 Taylor is undefeated going into Day 2 at the Savannah Showdown! Go 14 Taylor!! Go CJV! https://t.co/uOFiRfV9K4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima kick my friends asses if they back out on seeing Koe Wetzel next month]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Balancement @RepJuanVargas Then how ever do you live with yourself?  Have a blessed day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tatiana is sailing in #AtlanticOcean by #NorthCarolina shore. Hi #Fayetteville #Charlotte #Greensboro! https://t.co/tYB5JddIet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never even been to the rodeo in my life. I think maybe once when I was little. I don’t even member]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anybody tried the colourpop no filter concealer ? If yes is it any good 🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[The X-37B is still up there. Waiting to hear a random sonic boom one day signaling it's arrival on the SLF.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Yes. Come and look at the Arizona border with all the trash and clothes left by the illegals. I have f… https://t.co/Z3OB6ecuJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the person you care about the most finally comes to the stage of being at peace you find the inner peace for yourself 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uniofgothenburg @ken4872297 Why don't you test dental implants on humans next?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp I don’t even want to watch what was once my favorite of the franchise... a bunch of rich mean girl… https://t.co/eJAlAWM3Rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanleejohnson Magnificent performance @ladygaga tribute to The Sound of Music @JulieAndrews]]></document></documents></author>