<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Is a #scrubs revival something that will every happen because I would watch the hell out of it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing Keith twice. You made my day. I’m back on the dance floor with my sweet baboo on the day I married him righ… https://t.co/s0iprxQG6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWBChicago the “alderman candidate” was a no show. My charges were dismissed and I want my pic removed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I messed my life up i dont blame nobody else but me stuff could be way better than it is now, but I learned from wh… https://t.co/z6PiXKAbho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlowInTheDarkXX @ConservaPeach @HonkyTonkJew @AOC Good ones can do both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a smile for you. Don't mind me I just laughed out loud in the library for about 5 minutes... #comedy #chuckle… https://t.co/pflodmH3kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go onto your local Craigslist or alternative and ask for a VHS copy of Bedazzled.  Somebody has it and has been wai… https://t.co/UzP6y8rrRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing off for our tenant and his huge hockey rink- pretty cool! Plus Blue Frog Plumbing is here Joseph Chretien f… https://t.co/sRpfbDrDs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoxPopuliMx @nonalorehedzg03 @LauHedonist Buen día y gusto saludarles! https://t.co/11oz439896]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the country’s best burgers is from Miami — again https://t.co/25tME2zE8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrieunderwood omg. I just did one of those. “Which country song”. Things. And it was Jesus Take the Wheel girl.… https://t.co/EOHO90PAl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excerpt from today’s Sermonic Message #sermonicmessage #sermonnotes @ The New Springfield Missionary Baptist Church… https://t.co/yvHlMDlq5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#donuttuesday at @thesweetbeetllc. This is one of my favorite flavor combinations so far. Anise and raspberry. 💕✨ @… https://t.co/KW7fHWGxft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your kill shot would be audit "Social Security" so many have stolen from Social Security. I am ret… https://t.co/IZMt6pJezX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richzeoli That NJ state bill you've been discussing seems to be an act of desperation.  It seems the Dems are a bi… https://t.co/ieZNpBDGG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrAndyNgo @IngrahamAngle @Portland_State Well @Portland_State  has some explaining to do. These who interrupted, i… https://t.co/CRjMhMp9aR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Berti_and_Ernie Does he swim often?  Great exercise for good hips. I have Standard Poodles. They need lots of spac… https://t.co/EiJMNFeGUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love having my own little space , I do anything for my little apartment ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signs things are changing in your world: your excitement level over legislature committee assignments is palpably g… https://t.co/u5VRTkrggv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Jeanine asks whether Omar's hijab is 'indicative' of her loyalty to Sharia law I AGREE!. '"THE JUDGE" IS  RIG… https://t.co/RiNJsj6q4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Brook Porter for scoring her 1000th career point tonight with a 3 pointer from the corner to sta… https://t.co/BKef6hCiTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to share the latest addition to my #etsy shop: Guinea fowl red feather earrings, hook earrings, gift for he… https://t.co/AsqTYJgj0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les commerçants comprennent de plus en plus l’importance de la biophilie dans l’aménagement de leurs surfaces de ve… https://t.co/aCih4rZImu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeUnloveable @pamelasummer57 Republican congress are like the stepford wives of DC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently getting to work with a cheer hangover, anyone who says those aren't a thing.... has never been to competi… https://t.co/e23hS2oUIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huntsville, Tx - I’ll be at Arnaud’s Cajun Kitchen arnaudscajun tonight from 6pm-8pm. Bring your family, it’s a bea… https://t.co/8TnKn94lg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckStodgers @BernieSanders Oh for sure.  The promise of free everything.  An empty promise, but a promise nonetheless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plains Nails is like a reunion center you will always run into someone you know at that place]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fostering six rescue puppies 🐶 #puppies #rescuedogsofinstagram #cutedogs #love #busymom #puppylove ❤️🐶❤️ @ Westside… https://t.co/8qX4Qw6a0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Marked Trees  This was a fun experiment. Doing something a little different. #GodofWar #GodOfWar4 https://t.co/RbZAb6Nxyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @AriMelber #ImpeachTrump first by the Congress who the people elected to represent them, then indict No one is above the law]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalpetday Luna! 🐱 🌙  #blackcatsofinstagram  #lunathecat  #chicagopets  #catsofinstagram @ Chicago, Illi… https://t.co/X9lsp1l9Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once something is yours, you start taking it for granted instead of appreciating it because it’s “already yours”. T… https://t.co/SRZLZ4ah7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TM_MadHatter Prayer's love!! I failed myne to in my first pregnancy I panicked,I had pregnancy diabetes and it wen… https://t.co/tn7Pi1yhPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just walkie talkied abbey using my watch from scranton and she’s in virginia. technology is crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump He bilked the government out of revenue! He involved himself in another countries bad deeds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynda3035 Oh no!  I've been through that many times!  At least it won't be long.  I ran out of my meds last week w… https://t.co/3kAV69yA9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dimpleverse Thank you, but I wish I hadn't been able to write it. I'd rather not understand my MS. ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chief Legal Counsel Robert Baker Wanted to Indict HRC https://t.co/5uzjSoUREk via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2UnKn0wN @NELLY822 That is bad to teach your children to murder, its Just not right they should be taught to love… https://t.co/bFdb8W4ueA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worshiping with Desirée and my mom (@ Christ Community Church in Ashburn, VA) https://t.co/GGI0iIfHc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lytle Jv beat crystal city 17-3..⚾️⚾️ tomorrow schedule and times @lytleisd https://t.co/CwSRBmFTPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexadaiello22 Love the civic spirit within this post of student involvement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all commenting stuff under the articles about Seungri are awful. This is serious and y’all out here making jokes. 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three days until I get to spend my spring break with the love of my life! I’m so so ready for this break 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump I’m sorry, @tedlieu but have you never watched a vampire movie?? You never invite them in… https://t.co/3TKykkfTfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night my #LivePD family until next weekend @DanTheBeepMan @AngelineDC @PascoSheriff @OfficialLivePD… https://t.co/abFNckBCum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pets_Mag @CompAnimalPsych @healthycavalier @Lucy_Cavalier @PeterEgan6 @ExpatVet @petethevet @puppylovecamp We have… https://t.co/UTGEyYHxMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse Yes...POTUS SHOULD REFUSE ANY DEBATES ON THEIR CHANNELS]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the discussion about recognizing the patient voice in research- we don’t always to the best job in clinic.… https://t.co/6E7DbYbIqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMcCullers43 Tyrion. Dude is brilliant and has been dealt so many terrible hands in life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see people tweeting “I relate to YWN Melly” LMFAOOO r u guys okay ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you are currently leading through "lies and deception"!  Continuing to project your behavior upon others!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitch McConnel advises POTUS not 2 veto executive order stopping him from allocating border wall funds because of f… https://t.co/fgiXY83sz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone in our manager group chat said “what’s going on everything is breaking” and my boss responded with “its Ste… https://t.co/88819EXNQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. Fell asleep with a bit of mascara still on and woke up looking like Momo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Title: We sold out to stay popular and we don't care who knows it. Yes a little long but it fits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Thank you for tearing down this wall that should’ve never gone up the brothers are horrible person]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew4Miles Thanks! I’ve def creeped your runs before. I’m totally going to try that run after Tokyo - I had no… https://t.co/WwxxKyj5ON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCantwell Planned Parenthood is an abortion mill.  Now that infanticide is monstrously accepted as a woman's… https://t.co/02cEi8i3fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamofdaniel Agree it’s too early. According to a survey done by NPR, 14% of Bernie supporters actually voted for T… https://t.co/p8rvtsl5NQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninigirl84 @jahansell @SeraphineDrake @chick_in_kiev But Jeremy Northam... swoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evnieto1 @Ferlopezhr Jajajaja yo tambien iba escribir ni que fuera gripa 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried my hand at homemade baguettes. Seemed like a good thing on a cold and rainy Saturday. Paired it with ham and… https://t.co/JC46PICMOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to skype instead???   15 Min Skype Show $75 Today Only!  Email: BookSeptember@gmail.com https://t.co/Tlv6P8fADd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great show of support from our students and staff! Just another reason why I 💙 MHS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off and running this morning for the 4th Annual Georgia Innovation Summit. Excited to hear from all of our expert s… https://t.co/7RPkcRRywU]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you know who you want, you don’t even want nobody else hitting your phone frfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[When spending a season apart suddenly feels worth it...   The Aggies are Mountain West Champs!! SO proud of you… https://t.co/VwK8QijK1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para eso si son bien pinches valientes pero con un animal de su calibre no pueden 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pedro’s beard looks sooo good. I told him babe your beard looks awesome and he goes “of course, I’ve been using tha… https://t.co/Lpv9ySGAyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammyslav @BBCEarth @maxslavkin @TheOriginalPC Couldn’t agree more, I want to watch all the episodes, but it’s bee… https://t.co/NKZ6EWDkMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking outside with wet hair and my jacket open to de-ice the car because it’s basically 30, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling v emo after watching Selma Blair’s post diagnoses interview. Please send cuddles and hugs and wine and ice cream and snuggles]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much effort and hard work went into making today a great success! Thanks to everyone @WilmotFamilyRC, the volunt… https://t.co/LRDB8RGlfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would Choupette like to meet two cats from Philadelphia? Asking for a friend. 😸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LancePerodin 🤣🤣😘👠⚜️. I would never venture out in a thunderstorm. Hopefully they’ll just hold us until it stops! 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec Sadly that’s also when you sold your soul, to the depth of the dirtiest swamp criminals ever to occupy th… https://t.co/SQOzyQyJP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[All aboard the next train to Swoon City! This is the greatest #GalentinesDay gift I could ever imagine - support fr… https://t.co/hV5k5Np61C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheaSerrano @SamsungMobileUS We've been a Samsung fam for 9 years. My #SamsungGalaxyNote8 is still going strong, b… https://t.co/WLBVD7l2kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tahoequeen21 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Only if Jared is with him!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneFallon Does @myleftfang like to use furniture as a scratching post?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordy ain’t the reason her family broke up. Building a family with a man who ain’t loyal broke her family up. If it… https://t.co/VS8H1uV02m]]></document><document><![CDATA[if he lives where it’s warm enough to wear t shirts, why is he selling hot chocolate]]></document><document><![CDATA[A day of Spring like weather 🙌🏼 Playing outside while I cook dinner.  I dreamed of days like these.  Two healthy, h… https://t.co/jwM6MZcUUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[G-d Bless her and the human who set her free❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly Sully is living the life. (Also, it’s apparently warm in Kentucky) https://t.co/Gq3bnRfGUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so mad at ricky and lolo, if tamar doesn’t win this I’m going to be so bitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish this were the case in more places. It doesn’t matter what you got between your legs, you’re welcome to do your… https://t.co/hJ2yXBlEz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EarlyChildhood literacy is so important, it leads to long term #HealthLiteracy! Thank you State Senator @Troy4NJ7… https://t.co/fHDiP3KYWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Covers_Vegas @darth @dog_rates @yashar @HendersonNVPD @cityofhenderson @HCC_Nevada @CityOfLasVegas @animalfndlv… https://t.co/y3O4FE3FBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[when lenin said they would build a kind and compassionate russia: https://t.co/1Xtkyi9LTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonerjahms69 Aww well text me if you wanna talk, you're beautiful don't be hard on yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking pictures of my wisdom tooth growing in to show my mom is basically going to the dentist, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We will see what’s fake.  Your old buddy Felix will be talking soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is the pentagon welcome in Silicon Valley? “It’s a vocal minority- they say that because they don’t want to go thro… https://t.co/Vvr6idUPBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about China when they could only have one child...by permission.  https://t.co/BiAcF5OBx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[From scanner: Car driving around with a woman on the roof, screaming that she was robbed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadianSyrup @MrsGeorgiosP @LilyYog83 @loonamine @AmazingLovelyGM @GillDoc5 @myaddictionGM @MyAnchorGM… https://t.co/eOJnVcOmku]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ricflair #ricflairdrip #philadelphia #billyruddy #philadelphiapa @ Philadelphia International Airport https://t.co/50VvmC8DsR]]></document></documents></author>