<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sirensaysnope So lobotomised people follow you? Gotta be the only reason to call you ugly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rios just flat out won that round on energy. Put his head on Soto’s chest and worked for three minutes. #RiosSoto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to remember it can get colder out 😂 #iihf @ New Era Field https://t.co/xlJbxm6O6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @Ladyhoyabball for Sweet 16 win tonight against a tough Dacula team!! Next up, our girls will play at home… https://t.co/69jwlEb90M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Legski0301 @hildebran @Kasparov63 Trump is the most divisive, unethical, corrupt, and manipulative POTUS in US his… https://t.co/9z2HMPaINg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpowers3 @lndeutsch @msjlura @WickedDecent @ZeinaChalich @christybrenn @Glennr1809 My response is exactly the same as hers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Phillipians 2:10.  "that at the name of Jesus every knee should bow, in heaven and on earth and under the… https://t.co/laHDmqkCQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rainy departure @ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) https://t.co/aIHdfeGkdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeevesPT Hey bro, if it makes you feel any relief, know you’re not the only one whom feels the way you do! I, too,… https://t.co/DrXX2LK3bR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace 2 torneos en ésta estadística figuraba Dorlan Pabón, prueba de lo que mencionabas en otros tuits @Orlix77 , se… https://t.co/46UtsR9Fgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨@UTS_INC_Sports (HS) Tryouts🚨 #GrandRapids #Detroit #ChangingTheCulture #WeBuildStudentAthletes 📚🏀 #MYPYP #BeTHERE… https://t.co/VuYxFjF9oz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dear Mr President. The reason you have so many trolling you with negative crap is because many of… https://t.co/wCIc9BL3EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newballpark @Nicosan1 You would have had to start talking about that 10 years ago. But as always, the easiest way… https://t.co/hwpgc3K1nC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emanavery But his atrocities weren’t really detailed in my high school history books . It’s TRUE American history]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanyockey @livingbreely Chinese food never last me past 3 hrs https://t.co/hF9CXjDVBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tahlequah, OK Stilwell, OK  Ames, Iowa Salt Lake City, UT  Pecos, TX Crystal River, FL Ponca City, OK Cushing, OK A… https://t.co/Y0IkL8EhOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Atlantic City boat show keeping everyone connected and entertained. Day 1 of 5 baby Fish on 🎣 🐠🐟 https://t.co/EjYIHQ57a7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @CraigRSawyer @SenFeinstein That was before she went senile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Far Gone made it to all major steaming platforms. Idk why I’m so emotional right now. I just want to thank Drizz… https://t.co/yyUMVYBdPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watspn1013 Well you know the liberal elites do know best.  point in case: San Fran.  Detroit City,  our school sys… https://t.co/PNlzy5dx68]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you aren’t watching this @uclagymnastics meet rn what are you even doing with your life?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy came to play. #Cal on a roll heading into @pac12 Tournament next week.  #Pac12Hoops https://t.co/Z37OKJCLyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plc1790 @JeepJewel You should check out @JeepsGreen on Twitter and Facebook. Good looking rig! 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would rather be shanked in my chest with my own elbow bone than shake hands with your stupid devil #TeamJesus #weakfucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrockboxing C'mon JROCK, the dude gotz the strongest hair in the game.✊ Your a Philly fighter and your gonna like… https://t.co/HAlEUVMjCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mavericks are rolling in the early going of this opening-round matchup. They have a 16-8 lead over TGU with 1:0… https://t.co/sXqVKW7gwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How anyone can vote for a known liar 🤥 who stole millions from the Indian nations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Maybe they will discuss how she colluded (or conspired) with the Russians to discredit Donald Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BumJF @IJasonAlexander This is a piece of art. https://t.co/yw6r4iKVW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFKARS I'm not arguing for or against her, I'm analyzing her position. In case it isn't clear, my point is not tha… https://t.co/fYQqKAkRVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erickuo Hell no! I prefer trying to harangue @NYCFC into doing better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a girl come off at me because i took my sister and mother out to dinner for my sis bday.... i got all kinds of… https://t.co/J2nfAJ2Pkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an English teacher in 7th grade who called me Mr. Gremlin, Knowing full well my last name is Gramling. I used… https://t.co/s95NjiYxpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwaggXBL Both are good. You have a great stream so it’s good to see both in your case. You have a good attitude so… https://t.co/B2gKb20FEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sandra_Cole44 @reganintheworld @tonyfera1 @ericaracheltv He’s not Tyler Santino.   His name is Corey.   https://t.co/8hMbsiTT4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OANN Thank you for high lighting the Identify Theft problem with Illegal Aliens, its about TIME.  Simple folks lik… https://t.co/PAlT2L5Mki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instructional #leadership as a team sport (via @ASCD @Teachers_Lead): https://t.co/QZrTcZ4T4u #edchat #edu #Lead #Learn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femwriter As long as we all know where the nearest AED is located. Men, women, let’s all be heartsmart. Happy IWD!… https://t.co/RFkBjC9NbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw some guy trying to drill into credit card kiosk for bike share. Cybersecurity conference stunt or nah? (Prob nah, alerted an officer)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer You’re. A true idiot - Go Trump - Best economy ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jersey update: #FCCincy wearing all white at #ATLUTD. That’s means 🔶+🔷 for the first time at Nippert. https://t.co/vwXHQDKtRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the hospital after surgery at age 11, I refused to take Tylenol capsules for fear they'd be poisoned and would o… https://t.co/Lt9Rlt2ENz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Anybody Actually Believe Kim Jong-un Knew Nothing About Otto Warmbier? | Trending https://t.co/hExCDAayBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's sad how people would stand up for #greatfalls a place that has just gone to shit for 20+ years! I think we need another bar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMovies He had no arms or legs. He couldn’t hear, see, or speak. This is how he led a nation. @SteveCarell]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must do everything to acheive your dreams not while your young but while your simply alive to do so]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Nor Cal California Kolsch by @strikebrewingco at @spg — https://t.co/lxM0AeXRza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think SPRING 🌸🌺.. Tag and share with your bestie  . . . . ▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️▪️… https://t.co/4CLOulcPR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseball_wahoo @Tribehypee This is one batting practice AB. The most HRs he ever had in a minor league season was 9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[why does the japanese house intro track go harder than any music released this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t listen to Gunna - Who You Foolin song while you smacked got you doing karate shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have but there not cool people there low life’s like the people that suck dingalings and are petifials Aretha… https://t.co/TKjLPd6AIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCivian Funny, her “mindless hot takes” seem like common sense to me. Guys don’t like getting traded in season,… https://t.co/IyL9EKcvlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SerendipityDizl The problem is that people have to pay their bills. I like Dom but he doesn't do it for me at 6am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayyyylah @yourfavasiaaan @yaboycham This is more like my girls approach hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veritatisperu A mi me parece que los jueces y autoridades que de alguna manera han intervenido en la liberación de… https://t.co/ErZIY59aOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Elijah_M10 on being named District MVP of the Catholic League. Well-deserved. @JPrestonSports… https://t.co/sd17UUnFx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athlete Ally and Out in Athletics Launch Resources for Trans/GNC Inclusion https://t.co/VGxp8DnHZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I contend she should receive a refund as it is so obvious that they did not teach her anything.😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dukekeith @espn @eplocomotivefc Duke, you’re a gem to listen to when you call anything. Your hockey games were fan… https://t.co/KA5JduY59e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eeriley99 @caseymaker @GAINSnetwork @GA_EDLab Beautiful - thanks for sharing the photos and idea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cincinnati Zoo &amp; Botanical Garden in Cincinnati, OH w/ @cincy_kat https://t.co/15AaeTtFgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SorayaKirstin It’s a different rum I’m pretty sure and they are always made fresh some places already have mai tai… https://t.co/aBvDBzfvda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerTalkWileyP @BeerTalkBenji Heard you shit your pants at a Kent state party]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you catch me staring lmao don’t expect me to look away and if we make eye contact oh yeah I’m definitely gone sp… https://t.co/6WuK1smv6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aug1405 @Wblscott1 @da3rd_daniel @ToscaAusten @goofballgeorge @Cali_Tracii @teli707 @fordmb1 @DenzoePatriot… https://t.co/lDOYNEb8YP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also that couch was way easier to get out the house than in. I remember it barely fit in the front door, but it sli… https://t.co/QmMCRHhstb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing the best to my @BeaverBaseball and @OSU_Managers family today! Let’s go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darksideofshoes Sounds like a future pet store manager in the fast track to marketing genius to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormTrack9Bill Is that what that big ball of fire is in the sky I see this morning? I was about to call homeland security.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Friday night - Hottest Party in the city. Ladies Free on Guest list till 1130 pm. Booths and guest list - Cal… https://t.co/tS5PEOtQKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the family, Eurorack #makenoise #malekkoheavyindustry #tiptopaudio #strymon #arturia #korg #eurorack… https://t.co/9kHlp1u8zG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickmon1112 Still the featured Entertainment Twitter Moment as of 3 mins ago https://t.co/5V9BgrL6Tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvelynMaryW I love Richard Burton and Rex Harrison - great casting. So I will watch it again - maybe it’s aged better than I thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to get back out with the moparunlimitedcarclub crew this season. Unlike the others I'm one of the full y… https://t.co/fODZO5Q27a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubanitoenCuba No te preocupes@por Argentina, preocupate@por@Cuba qué hace 60 años desapareció , tú no sabes ni lo… https://t.co/5SUDNgcWMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the tripas  - - #Tripas #Tacos #Food #Foodie #Eat #Eats #InstaFood #InstaEat #InstaGood #WhyCheatOnFood… https://t.co/veG7aNYvEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinchristen6 @cvk35 @HerrimanCity It’s true! They caught it and relocated it Cougar bringing fear to Utah neigh… https://t.co/A2mw4Qvkpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottKaplan @SdLandon @SanDiegoSockers @PechangaArenaSD Two Fridays from now, 3/1 against the Express another $2… https://t.co/mIKXcddpsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such things in common including having church leaders who engage in inappropriate conduct with children, and resist… https://t.co/FKUx9alzwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton: "When I lose my virginity, it'll be soft and tender"... And done over three consecutive nights with three d… https://t.co/PuDkJc1ih3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0319edf @EndColonial1sm @ReeTv51 Exacto, son Estadistas bisiestos. Ahora los estadistas necesitan un vehículo efec… https://t.co/V2oRQcs0SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSinger Still surprised people in Miami made the market frothy at this point.   https://t.co/suqceTBZ82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already doing the challenge mate! But very ironically, I am reading Kahnemahn’s book currently!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IonaGaelsMBB Wins 73-57 over Siena, 9th straight win, heads to @MAACSports finals Monday night. Watch post game me… https://t.co/lOgSXhATLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt Throw back to studio vibes with @whoisjebidiah a few weeks back. He’s cooking up some awesome feel-good hip ho… https://t.co/Se8ooOUQQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got food on the way and I kind of want to tip the driver a blunt💨🍃💣😎🤷🏽‍♂️🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chloe_Arkos @WildlandPeaks @benbrookjohn You’re incredibly naive if you can’t even open your mind to possibility o… https://t.co/vOa7v8AMPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody:  My Neuro Prof: We can remember some things, but we would hope we forget things like my favorite ex girlfri… https://t.co/cfk6RKuU9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi It’s that enough or you still don’t understand ? That we don’t want your opinion traitor. https://t.co/kXHp9Oh2hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my son was destined for Bel Air. When we went to go see Bel Air vs Andress at the Don. #Class2022… https://t.co/1JX2LVAKr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivanovadecan Hola Ivanova. Es Sergio desde Washington.  Como está Vladimir  Saludos y gracias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikeysurf @MLBNetworkRadio I’m already overjoyed. The guy was a 240 hitter last year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarvelNewsPTN Yeah that’s probably the best thing to do with this movie. Maybe do that same thing with @DarkPhoenix2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_softvegan @EBatterson Carnivores must have meat. A cat is a carnivore. Dogs not so much. In my experience dogs wi… https://t.co/1sFxCLizB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh god I forgot, putting clocks one hour forward... 🙄🙄🙄🙄 #DaylightSavingsTime https://t.co/096wgon4UJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieToole @RicFlairNatrBoy @BPTBluefish @AtlanticLg @chhchelsea @geremygrate @Yank2119 #feeltheteal https://t.co/YAbwUsLdZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jf_senechal @samuelpiette Cap de Piette j'aime bien le petit brassard rouge cap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Vote2MAGA_DJT Dear President our patients And our democracy is In great danger it is time for you… https://t.co/rAWLH1zfyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EagleSessions That’s the closest that bum will get to putting that jersey on]]></document></documents></author>