<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Gettin' into the weekday groove! #14splatpoints💥 #419caloriesburned🔥#otfparkville♥️🍊📊 #5amclub🕔 #coachbecky💪🏼… https://t.co/UCRvXuIGtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't watched an awards show since Henry Ford created the 8 hour workday but I guess I'll check out the #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnoopDogg is streaming on @WatchMixer now if anyone wanted to know 🐸❤️ https://t.co/Aq7Pluw7ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonSmith929 @JohnMartin929 @BennettDoyle thanks for a great interview with coach Miller!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirginiaLoughn1 @PVArkol @keanothedog @HondoResists @kaysintBB @McGeezer67 @clairermassey @smokeeater22 @rugbynred… https://t.co/N0z9X4XBT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pnut Thank you!! @pnut  @NickHexum @311 @SXMLiveLoud  for an amazing vacation! ♡♡♡♡♡♡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordoHoustonTX THANK YOU! Him yelling "fight me then, fight me" every other scene - I'm dying for someone2stomp a… https://t.co/UFSMVTnoEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouserAmy Cleaning out my closet is high up on the list for me as well!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Va•Lion•Tine’s Day: the annual occasion marking how much older the 🦁 is than me. To commemorate this, a few shots o… https://t.co/vhNqpuLUfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life consists of way too many moments of me panicking thinking I forgot to pay a bill that I actually scheduled… https://t.co/BXF5mUm91K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissKimShell 👏🏻🙌🏻👏🏻YES! I thought it was just me who gets “tan confidence”, so glad to hear it’s not 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMuscutt @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @LivePD_LEOS @LivePDNation @LivePdBlueLine @Livepd_fans @LivePdFantasyLG… https://t.co/7YfIAKmy7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h1gg5b0s0n @RealMuckmaker He has the Senate and The White House, and the #GOP is behind him all the way. So trying… https://t.co/Lcyuhm8HcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamsOfHam shoot me a physical address where i can send you little gift of my art. 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say “alv el amor” but broke my heart.... mmm okay... https://t.co/j0GaNjLvkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously cannot f'ing sleep right now &amp; it's seriously almost 2:30AM. 😶😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicojumpsuit god can turn her eyes away just this once this is an exception]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlasouArt It’s hard to cry when eating a sandwich, because sandwich’s are the greatest thing in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hansappen The kids look like mini versions of your parents! Hilarious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monitorLATINO Voto X #CuandoTeAmé de @julionalvarez para el 1° lugar en #TopSureste @SAPSGrupero @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F 3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just took my last exam of the week, ain’t gotta study more for now PHEW 😅🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[39. How to: lose stress and weight with acupressure - https://t.co/AqAyc44pgz   #howto #twitter #inspired #me… https://t.co/cvDms0gLmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday handsome there so much that I want to say but let me start off by saying I love you so much 😭😍 I hop… https://t.co/Mv7BzebKS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all some fuckin’ hypes that don’t understand when shit is EXCESSIVE...🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @JohnA_USMCvet Trump was born for starters. A horrible day. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time the wind blows I can just sense the thoroughbreds going absolutely nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @Daily_Star Ok. That was a good one https://t.co/0dHxqiah9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AleCanedoP nos gustaría que tomarán en cuenta a @RioRomamx para su participación en la #FeriaPuebla2019 por favor y muchas gracias 🙌🎶👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[XOXO from the Blue Belle Inn. Seafood Mornay on Puff Pastry Hearts on Scallop Shells. #bedandbreakfast #seafood… https://t.co/9988DvyByR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDarcyExplains Maybe it is just the astrological calendar being bummed out that it has to go from Aquarius to Pisces tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid feds, if it ain’t broke don’t fix it. Dumber than a rock. I could do a better job than that. Hay @POTUS I’m… https://t.co/cb2fJ5GO9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Only a stable genius would think of having a July 4th celebration in DC!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sruthi and Pradeep's Wedding at the SV Temple and Indian Community Center in Pittsburgh, PA  https://t.co/tw5NRw5jFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do some of my best schoolwork between 4:55 and 7:30 a.m. I know that I shouldn’t keep it up, because FOUR FIFTY F… https://t.co/coFNmOIEj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was with a guy for two months that would tell me how beautiful I was but was really making me feel ugly the whole… https://t.co/zyJ4T1T6Lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPASlou Flashback Friday!! So tiny on Leap Day 2016! https://t.co/mDGukRz5Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MentoringKing👑 Is on WXYZ ABC Detroit, Michigan. Host: @MalcolmJamalWar  Outstanding program featuring the power o… https://t.co/w30Ep8hb1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ma dernière née😇  MON MUCEM À MOI #.2 Dimensions hors cadre:  36”x48” ou cm 91x122 Citations en langue française en… https://t.co/ebyDjumkAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starstrickenSF @_Astro_Nerd_ Sarafina!  What a nice desk so organized, efficient with a #SpaceTheme with #Stellar… https://t.co/yZVLkTuKar]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good diet can’t replace medicine or therapy for everyone. But research suggests it can help https://t.co/iVnk3uOjaq via @WSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“hell nah, i’d never kick you out.. i super liked you on tinder, remember?” best thing thag happened all night. 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had to make a pit stop before we drove to Houston!   #shooting #shoot #smart #guns #gunsofinstagram #texas #girl… https://t.co/j90UGKl5RA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I always lie to myself and say that I will do my homework on Friday and end up cramming on Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_mccray @lavndrblue As they should. This admin's insidious corruption must stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charming Spanish style 2 bedroom with office near La Jolla Village available 4-6-19! Click for more info!… https://t.co/CNz1LmwMzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleased to be joined by my colleagues Vice Chairwoman @RebecaSosaMiami, @CommBovo, @DLCAVA, @barbarajordan1, Sally… https://t.co/ytduZu5VlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMcKoon I agree, if true. However, you, sir, are trying to create a false equivalency. For that, shame on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K9Finn Very emotional ...So proud to see Army Lance and Lee 3 tours Iraq and to have Lance Bombardier Ben present… https://t.co/7GPbpCe3pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evan me puso el apodo de cutiebutt y A LA MRDDDDDD https://t.co/hcGG27Hh8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a first today. One of the guys at work congratulated me on it being #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collin did good, beat me every time!! 🏌️👍🏻 @ Topgolf https://t.co/855cRtDyzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Cathcart Towers Hotel in Surprise, AZ w/ @susanlowryaz https://t.co/xizQbieuAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is coming home from work, eating dinner and watching Jeopardy! reruns in bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/cNPTP31NrU… https://t.co/LhHhOzyMOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorning (@ The Forbidden Forrest in Hogwarts, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/h3UFC0exds https://t.co/8R2LdychuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many thrillers in my #TBR pile. Stayed up all night finishing @alicewriterland #SometimesILie. Enthralling &amp; spooky 👀.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elicia Wells '16 and Summer Allen '18 took the field in an ODAC match up. Love seeing these Titan laxers back toget… https://t.co/Gf6lfaq2jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saints playoff basketball against Chino Hills. #MeloBallAintWalkingThroughThatDoor (@ Chino Hills High School in Ch… https://t.co/s3QMLAZYSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a best friend that lets you cry over hearing your favorite song on vinyl for the first time https://t.co/Vw7HWcmxl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JinkiesMsJenks Ok, I know this is petty - but how is this even his signature?? His last name ends in p so shouldn’… https://t.co/UiHJq4n5Cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlyphWildarms well yeah, ppl are hella turned on by an encyclopedic knowledge of kingdom hearts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/n56psrCm8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outfits on point for In The Valley Below  #NoisePop2019 https://t.co/7RYxIfpJmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early continuing to unpack, while watching the sun rise over the city😊 @ Ascent Victory Park https://t.co/KZK2eKSgX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is to the most inspiring civil society representatives I met this year in CentralAfricanRepublic 🇨🇫 with my co… https://t.co/rvpOy2Vx8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really excited for this summer and all the new exciting things coming my way, so winter can fuck off now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of you today!...😊 They don’t make ‘em any better than this!!🥰 #memories #goodtimes #whatalady #happybdayma https://t.co/nMWMWg6ceV]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about a little comedy. 1800s flirting ettiquette, 'cause nothing says, "I'm engaged!" like throwing your gloves… https://t.co/BpuJDpwomY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I met Marty...A robot that wanders the the isles of the grocery store looking for spills, breakage....any… https://t.co/Yxh3PSMwWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anhonyf97 @POTUS @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump She is breath taking beautiful. I love them both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[at lunch and our server just got fired in the middle of our order like do we still get food orrrrrr?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreasuryMog Gladstone, with broken hearts💔 we must report the Nebraska #Ambassacats Trio is now a Duo, as Alexei h… https://t.co/nVa7fD0APN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendonurie, are you even real? Incredible show. #PrayForTheWickedTour https://t.co/QM1Z9M6lX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatherinePaiz is the best slime remover! U go girl!!!! Yo a master! God bless u! 💜🥰😘😍💙 https://t.co/M0wfNmQ6VS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mailmaam68 @MattSerweKETV And stuck in an airport hotel overnight is the worst kind of sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggregg198 @broerkonijn67 wszystkie języki były obowiązkowe, tylko nikt się nie uczył, bo w komunizmie nie spodziew… https://t.co/90RudrBepy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_TrumpIN @Ken19512 I am from Puerto Rico a Lady, 69, i,was the first person to say AOC is,a Comunist, I said, she… https://t.co/o1YBKicsT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews This is the plan - keep it in the news and watch the Dem's split. All of this is playing into the GOP hand… https://t.co/7OVeqT5sHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[*lecturing self about not crying*  Me: *starts crying*  #HappyWednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do *NOT* trust the posted estimated wait times for California DMV locations! It said 6 minutes when we got in line.… https://t.co/gsP3gYQoAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you build a more gender-balanced world? By celebrating women’s achievement, no matter where on our incredibl… https://t.co/m1O40fQ3Zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tanner's 3-point shot and two free throws @ Krum High School https://t.co/Y2VAA4jvV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorrecamii Idc what anyone says loving on your baby is NOT spoiling him! He’s supposed to feel safe in your arms 😌… https://t.co/rcX7IFKm7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Morvelous Pt2. If you said “white people WERE so evil” I wouldn’t have as much as a problem with this. the fact t… https://t.co/cgHaJfomJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umar Azam, a Pakistani government official, said Indian troops had “indiscriminately targeted border villagers” usi… https://t.co/qi6GHxjnIs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just heard that I will be presenting at ILA in October! I can’t wait to collaborate with fellow literacy leaders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the military spouses here just posted how they can't sleep since they're 20 weeks pregnant... Girl just fuck… https://t.co/vi630hVsDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is that possible?!  There is something seriously wrong with the #tax system]]></document><document><![CDATA[....and lacrosse season has started...way to go MCHS 🥍🔴🥍⚫️🥍@MiddleCreekLax @owen13harrison @SDHarrison43 https://t.co/iVwHB4WUal]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am CURRENTLY excited about it and I regularly wish to grab a box of Ellio’s pizza from the supermarket because it… https://t.co/cfaSqghO2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMa68421140 @KirkHerbstreit @JohnnyBench_5 @Reds Steve...calm down.  Kids like to make their own way, find the… https://t.co/pB3mYjZwui]]></document><document><![CDATA[god i’m STUPID. this why it’s so hard for me to take a chance or to give someone a chance. this shit is exactly why]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since being done with tennis every time I work out I wonder how I got through 12 years of tennis with such weak arms 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisgeidner How long do we have to wait until you you tell us what your next adventure is? 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orchid_is I got April 5th off so I don’t have to rush from work to get you guys from the airport]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love 💕 is in the air here @NISDMurnin Our class enjoyed  @JPS_DFB inspiring our future Falcon class of #2029… https://t.co/G5BwC2CpHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjwgenealogy @Oil_vampire @Circa Really? Where do you get your ridiculous figures on drugs? Drugs are pouring acro… https://t.co/imXh5aRXNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m now on workers comp for the rest of the month. Someone please give me something to fill my time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social media is all about vanity metrics. That’s cool, but make sure you are building an email list and creating yo… https://t.co/pKT1cXkiGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sexijamaican18 hey how u Nd the kids u know I lost my mother in October]]></document></documents></author>