<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[And I saw the dead, great and small, standing before the throne, and books were opened. Then another book was opene… https://t.co/ISuZX9Wtid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too much highlighter??? 💋 💋 💋 Don't know her. 💄💗💄💗💄💗 #makeupbyshan #makeuplover💋 #aspiringmua #sundayfunday☀️💕 @ Mi… https://t.co/F4L9TqCP9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!! Fun and practice! Read the word, spell the word, read it again! Such a fun idea! I bet our amazing coaches c… https://t.co/UeLfJEtxVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! We did it! @ West Chester Township, Butler County, Ohio https://t.co/ZdtnPRsjBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[To save or not save tax refund - depends if there is money available to pay bills - or emergency fund less than “0”… https://t.co/m4GdryGzbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Such pathetic bleating of your fake “news” to the sheep who follow you. BTW, stop already with the… https://t.co/5kN2qc8ncX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neverletdown Place 936100108, Brinnon, WA 98320 https://t.co/c7ANRBDYF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I’m okay with living in the south. Somedays I miss Pgh and NJ with every fiber of my being. Today, stuck… https://t.co/hBcLQ5StYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marii_2828 Janiyah needs to know if Crocs always land right side up? Her Vans failed the Vans challenge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚓️🌻🐾 . • • • • #aboutme #selfie #pnw #carselfie #blackandwhite #radgirlscollective #radgirlslife #pnwbabes… https://t.co/04w3w5uLRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only got in trouble at school once.   The consequence? Standing “on the wall.”  The crime? Lining up to go to lun… https://t.co/7V6DmjWL08]]></document><document><![CDATA[The damage of the fear, shame, guilt and self-loathing that exist inside a closet are reflected unknowingly in the… https://t.co/LZvhboB8sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The two validating wonders of human existence are LOVE and the invention of the FUTURE TENSE.”  ~ George Steiner]]></document><document><![CDATA[People be having real deal pressure wit me because of my skin color wtf😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delighted that the great @UNADenver team snuck out of the official meetings to come and visit the briefing room.… https://t.co/p6hio4JR5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shocking!! Embarrassing &amp; Totally UnAmerican!!  Is this Trump’s MAGA method??]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is insane how much of business is just like being on MSN with two convos open talking about the people in the other convos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AviWoolf @Don_Zeko @gina_goldberg We use the term in logic. That is what it means, that is the objection people have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited about today! Today is our Grand Opening of the McNair Mindfulness Mansion! Thank you… https://t.co/MVFWCemiBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neodiva2002 I had my gallbladder removed on Friday. I’m doing a lot better than I thought I would be. Im just incredibly tired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kgathje21 @MLS @ColoradoRapids Colorado is unpredictable. It dumped snow in June years ago when the USMNT played Costa Rica.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow I’m going to wake up and have a damn good day and I’m done being sad girl and that’s the tea. Goodnight ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ve given up on my hair staying vibrant because warm showers are the only thing that gives me even a little joy]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing more important than this.  There is no functioning democracy without a robust free press.  Subscri… https://t.co/ZNDXalP3q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So an update on the sign I made, he wasn’t able to sign it BUT he did see it and acknowledged it TWICE! 1st time as… https://t.co/BVGY8rcOis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Agreed. Although I will say the Saudis are making even Netanyahu look good. One can be the most righteous… https://t.co/pBGHVzfj4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiscaliaCol Su abuelo Rojas Pinilla. desde dónde se encuentre, avergonzado ha de estar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halsey &amp; @thegreatkhalid releasing songs the same day is the highlight of my year 😍 #talk #11Minutes 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good afternoon America we might be on fire but I found a bunch of my grandfathers old letters from Korea and I’ve b… https://t.co/inaS0uWYud]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you drive a white or black Dodge Charger and your not a cop, I hate you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le acabo de prestar a mi mamá 600 dólares. Mi meta de vida es estar tan financieramente estable que mi mamá no se t… https://t.co/edA2Zhc92d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @provocity can you guys actually do some useful construction? The potholes in the road need filled more than we… https://t.co/sA8UmR1PeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrisonjaime @LindseyGrahamSC wake up send his ass to a wheel chair it is time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Session Pale Ale by @fremontbrewing at @fremontbrewing — https://t.co/0pkJ25MzqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Championship Saturday! C3D9 finals in Linn are this afternoon. Girls get it started with Blair Oaks taking on S Cal… https://t.co/pMGxlvurjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vestido lindo chocolate que brilhou no New York Fashion Week 2019 Evento fechado muito marcante na minha vida ❄️💙❤️… https://t.co/bO1ngMnY9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know when you have a glass of wine and break out in deep purple hives all over your face, neck and chest? What’… https://t.co/IGcOfygYtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for watching over my punkin, @shenanigansen 🌛🌛 https://t.co/uE9aOZitxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Censorship is giving an unfair advantage2the pol who's soul purpose is2Siphone all Americans$ In2their Greedy hands… https://t.co/x0rTXs6jV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! ❤️ Remember to celebrate the love you have for your family, friends and significant others e… https://t.co/ojtL0e1OeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No better view.  Thank you mgmspringfield ....on to the next one! @ Bradley International Airport - BDL https://t.co/o42mJiQudh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 @mitchellvii @patni1111 #HELL2THENO! That #MAAM will never disgrace #ThePeoplesHouse again! Regard… https://t.co/UC7QLWy6U6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl! Your a walking Trophy🏆 . #NYFW #NYC #Designer @chromat @maccosmetics @nyfw .  #fierce #makeup #fashionweek… https://t.co/s7jNaqRR6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome say Mary Grace!! It is our honor to serve this family!   Reposted from thewholelivingmomma  -  Mary Grace Z… https://t.co/MioyepooZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When orion’s drunk he doesn’t realize how loud and clumsy he is and he’s literally fee-if-fo-fumming all over my house]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna see your beautiful selves in mah merch so send me pics once you get them 🤓  If you haven’t copped here you… https://t.co/m8b1DWCwFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man is straight up YELLING at a woman about Trump’s wall in the middle of starbucks, gotta love IV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to take the magic initiate feat at level 4 but I feel like it won’t fit my character well. Condrums.… https://t.co/kri8BN9qyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized I drove all the way to church with a flat tire.  The devil works hard but God works harder😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[no offense but i ran the dog category in jeopardy tonight so fuck y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry if my mom friended you on Snapchat... she doesn’t understand it so and feel free to block her lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODITITO 🖐 Prohibido olvidar!! Y no te dejes engañar por la oligarquía el Consejo de Participación Ciudadana es la… https://t.co/bYITIOsIME]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a silly question. I have a tattoo of a cat that says “so cool.” I have very few stipulations for permanent… https://t.co/LpnxZkEdu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PharmasWife @Collabro @CityHallHull Have fun! I loved my visit to Hull in Nov 2017, where Collabro delighted every… https://t.co/NCtX6l9wKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[65 percent of people answered this correctly. Can you? https://t.co/guMSudaATD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrowder #ManCrushMonday #RealMen #SmokingHotConservativeMen https://t.co/NfYsw3Q5si]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @jonasbrothers play a drinking game on @ElvisDuranShow at 7 a.m. is a great way to start a Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano That bullshit I carry to protect myself. Nothing is going to stop the bad guys from getting guns]]></document><document><![CDATA[All should light up if they sew the circuit in correctly! 🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻 #heweshighlanders #lemelsonmit #proudteacher… https://t.co/k3ROJi9R1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeoplesOracle This Rx can fuck right off already. I got no sleep last; my brain wouldn't stop! Hoping my midterm is ok tomorrow...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault I think that the entire HP series made it a point to have these flawed characters and those who wer… https://t.co/DFuePShSYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Leslie on being recognized for the work she does!! @NYSchoolSupts @BCSDSuper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganWorld Why did he do this in the first place? More press? So sad. He’s on a hit show, is a talented actor...n… https://t.co/wxHDbCMMB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the second time I’ve been told I’m not the type to fight someone I’d be the type to slit someone’s throat.… https://t.co/SfUBfxf6W1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a great time this weekend celebrating the chartering my beloved @HowardU. Here’s to 152 yrs of trailblazing s… https://t.co/s1lb0Wrmqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@people @Michaelraymusic @carlypearce So happy for you both! And this made me cry! So sweet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AssocIntl @davidpowell @Bronzie9 @brianwesner @ChristianGratz @Richard03399598 Congratulations Everyone!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[past means it’s right behind you but passed means you’re way in front of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contemplating the truth in this tonight after having a conversation about the connection between SEL, math and equi… https://t.co/A1dLALQYb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMix Voting for either you guys or Liam to win!! If either one of you guys win I’m happy!! #BRITVIDLITTLEMIX #BRITVIDLIAMRITA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior Hey @CNN you DON’T have to offer equal fair coverage to a traitorous crime syndicate such as this ad… https://t.co/3x744k2nYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The JB Show on @ESPN989 today at NOON: Fmr #Gamecocks/ current @aafAPOLLOS K @elliott_fry22 1205pm @VSIdocsports fr… https://t.co/9QBV9c8WOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger Stone just got a little more fuel for his campaign against our laws...#inners]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning has broken...make it a great FRIDAY!  #CVNP❤️ https://t.co/79cSogtBiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crouch down a lil’ closer so you can hear me. Guess what? It’s FRIDAY! 📸: @bagladies - 💄: 1makeupjunky - . . . . .… https://t.co/1ip9Go5Y10]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCabe makes media rounds amid reports that Mueller probe is wrapping up  https://t.co/DtAkLsWtd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoviePass OMG @MoviePass you are such a scam!!! Are you seriously charging me again after I managed to get refunde… https://t.co/CNLiKUSF9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else has less than no desire to see these left wing, very important, overrated, self absorbed people share thei… https://t.co/ktrjzawK5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost a rule, look where the bins are, find the ramp or the lift or the accessible restroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you @brickjp for my beautiful flowers ❤️💐  @1800flowers @NikonUSA @Sigma_Photo  #HappyValentinesDay… https://t.co/iLE8f4e6YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to go see Ariana Grande in concert July 8th. Who wants to come with me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimyanBankAlert @jcary14 He helped found Reliant. I believe he served as chairman for many years, until the merger with Commerce Union.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, I’m just gonna say it.. the new Grey’s Anatomy SUCKS compared to seasons 1-10. Don’t @ me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinoCruzillini @marcuslemonis I’ve learned more and more!  @ChandlerLyles has definitely been the balance for me over the last 5 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YKaija @FilmInquiry @kyenvu @IndieWire @FilmInquiry did they have to get government approval?  Uganda has been wor… https://t.co/9ALuyZRFiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone is looking for someone to babysit, chores around the house, etc for a little side job. id be more than we… https://t.co/gqjgmRCRqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacquel14277925 @LoganMurphy1 @RepMaxineWaters What? Are you that blind? I’m more concerned about FACTS than stree… https://t.co/zpThXKdjzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[every night I lay in my bed and crave the hash browns that I’m going to eat the next morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[A powerful thread on the centrality of education in preparing informed citizens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1barryatkinson @RealMuckmaker Gotta have common sense to use knowledge as a tool. Trump lacks both]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine wanting to take a #NationalNappingDay nap to celebrate but your BPA chapter decides it would be more fun to… https://t.co/bksLWQnlcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you see me at the gym on a spin bike playing SIMS mobile mind ya business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ldebretagne Big dogs are!!! My mom has a new rescue that has so much damn energy but he’s so big so he’s everywhere haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found on my desk. gross.  @chrisecrowley this must be your handiwork 🙅🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/HP4kV9kXYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you demand love from somebody else and you don’t know how to love your self 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more thing. Besides Taryn Hatcher, I was the only female in that room tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reason # 19947 of why kids should not be on electronics especially without supervision and reason # 50282 of why we… https://t.co/8pUDU8NMj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for such an amazing hero @brielarson she means the world to me. #CaptainMarvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usa_latinos @bookkeepPLUS @TalbertSwan Oh, did I mention that your "talented leader" is also a jackass?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sierra Canyon girls advance to Open Division final with thrilling win against Bishop Montgomery – Daily News https://t.co/3FxLT01pHV]]></document></documents></author>