<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Eminem Girls Lyrics https://t.co/CdQPLzHuqU via @YouTube @NoLifeShaq coach! EMINEM DISSES LIMP BIZKIT! React to this diss track coach!]]></document><document><![CDATA[being gay means always living within the kill zone of a first strike city]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jon_Kingston Well, you just did then, didn’t you, Jon? I assume this suggestion will go where all my others go? https://t.co/CmUKImGOHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swisstweet619 @Go_Dawgs_91 I missed the Rose Bowl. How did that turn out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecmille1 Amazing!!!! Someday we will obviously need a live performance of this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyvärr en förlust för mitt kära Rangers under den första matchen jag bevittnar på plats denna resa. Några saker jag… https://t.co/ZbQ8KJ4RcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to thank all of the resistors that have followed me back and those that followed first we must resist i… https://t.co/1n7tyPGCTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @Jim_Jordan Gym Jordan should shower after his sad performance. He’d enjoy that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your NHL pick is absolutely stellar. I’m also quite fond of that Tebow choice 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micronauta I was thinking about dedicating a RaspberryPi to the controller task]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobpaulin Definitely.  Below a certain scale it doesn’t make sense to preoptimize, but scale also creeps up on som… https://t.co/T3D3w9uXZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continuing my trend of hearing random Disney music in MD: they’re playing an orchestral version of Beauty and the Beast at BWI airport]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week has capsulized Georgetown season in a nutshell. But, going forward, a stronger nutshell. This was a big response for the program.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylor_ortega I’m a man but I don’t care about that because I’m a ladies man and almost every single friend of min… https://t.co/ktMvBIeVZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11thHour @JohnCornyn @senatemajldr @RepCloudTX  Is this a baby step GOP needs to start breaking with crime family Trump?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi B concert gon be full of females with warrants and suspended licenses ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DouglasDucote @realDonaldTrump @omar @SpeakerPelosi @TeamPelosi @FoxNews @CNN @MSNBC @DNC @SenateGOP She lives in… https://t.co/5YHUhdDjsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dry-hopped is different. First taste was odd, but every taste after was grat. Really tasty. But I have Primus stuck… https://t.co/0AEMBmJFmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ham's Planning GM Jason Thorne says report will be upcoming outlining governance and financial impact to fed gov's… https://t.co/Wen5WockOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro @IvanOte05870404 esto es lo que no reseñan las noticias en el país. Hay otra realidad que no se muestra en los noticieros.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for my fifth home opener. #FromDayOne #NYCFC https://t.co/OQPtGuj63E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GunterOlivia @LSUgym @sfinnegan37 Way to GEAUX @sfinnegan37 . Good job—@LSUgym is killing it! 🐅🤸‍♀️🐅🤸‍♀️🐅🤸‍♀️🐅🤸‍♀️🐅🤸‍♀️🐅🤸‍♀️🐅🤸‍♀️🐅]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Future of Enterprise Demands a New Future of HR https://t.co/zCsSPfgPeE via @DeloitteUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ogblackmoses I gotta give him his credit. He has some very dedicated fans lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending #WCW shoutout to you gorgeous @HTC_ReeseB aka #HTCBarbie 💕😘👱🏼‍♀️💖🌺🌸 https://t.co/QBuB8h8j2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrea_sez Isnt it weird how now that you're older you are so much more determined]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Strat200 well no @Ford in victory lane but a great race to start the weekend at @LasVegasBowl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MATT_MOYER215 They just can’t compare to your grit and tenacity! You tell those ❄️❄️ Matt!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beef short rib with risotto  OMG #ilVisio massapequa long island  #ImStuffed https://t.co/AMKhogtav8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re including some charitable giving this Lent, I’d be grateful if you considered my @StBaldricks. Help fight… https://t.co/XLxGWFHrDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicukynurse @CherylStottmann @Beast502Mode Hi I cheer for kensucky basketball,  Alabama football and cardinal wome… https://t.co/wQtgP5ceyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chesapeake Blvd &amp; Nansemond Cir in Norfolk, VA https://t.co/8OqzBmPHhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, my big bro, and his girlfriend went movie and seen The Upside. This movie is so damn funny and cool. #KevinHart… https://t.co/l6QLdPG95e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stopped at NH Fish and Game headquarters today to procure more hunting and fishing license for veterans in need.… https://t.co/O1uUoojgv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatBrianLast @TimHornbaker @RonFullerWelch These accusations would be believable if not expected for almost any… https://t.co/aVTkJPV68e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badg4lrihanna @rihanna HI GUYS!!! THIS #RIHANNA #MUSIC IS VERY GOOD, BUT SHE LOSE TO THESE #MUSICIANS, WHICH… https://t.co/04RqFj4oFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Random_Guy_101_ @thelauracoates Donald Trump has cheated his whole life and now sits at the top of the world with… https://t.co/t40rsVTyRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Hollister Place Apartments https://t.co/P4x824QEti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJayapal @HouseDemocrats KILL YOUR NEWBORN BABY! (Vote Democrat in 2020!) https://t.co/i1koeG8Qbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJGIV79 @RalphyVybz @uncleP2009 @ChickFoleyShow @FullyPoseable @HOVAAA @FScopers @FigFreakJLC @Soda_hunter… https://t.co/Y5yF8kEmtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Restore American Glory » Trump Moves to Take Away Planned Parenthood’s Federal “Slush Fund” https://t.co/jBbjsdScoc… https://t.co/X41IUtL8TI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not proud of this team at 25-4 then you are an asshole. #Bearcats]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/xd8byDKZ5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question for longtime fans of @UofLWBB : does Sam Fuehring remind anyone else of former Card frontliner Kelly Rose?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WOAH_itsMO enter hudini land hudini just dropped a new tape https://t.co/GfKL6dhrFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doctrine_Man It looks like he only found the front cover. Bindings are rusted out and it looks like the pages are gone. Still though....]]></document><document><![CDATA[the.real.ams playing with some toys. @ AMS Auto Moto Specialists https://t.co/yHvXk99CMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theconradical How did the Boondocks get put in this? The fact that you would steal this tweet(that’s hella old) an… https://t.co/bucCZhojGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner Over 40,000 Veterans are homeless and living on our streets. You care more about money for illegal alie… https://t.co/tyF5FwTBhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g0rillaGLUE4 @MRSCADAVRSDLITE @OnlyStarGaming you missed a bit war for the ages she snuck one by me, she knows I’l… https://t.co/kZfuksVlYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When one of your favorite singers come into your store eating an apple: ‘An apple a day keeps the doctor away.’ @nickcarter 🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talkSPORT Fucking spurs scum cheats!!!! Proof that the FA are having intercourse with all things spurs. Ridiculous cheats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfFrancesca @netflix I was surprised by your idea of Eden, being a place, Jerusalem. I have always thought of it… https://t.co/tZ5PsMMm0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fordtufff @thehill Actually, no. We’re big and very urban, but statewide, we’re low on the bishops state rankings, and getting better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let a girl try and argue with me at 2am she finna sleep with the birds since she wanna act like one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarikCohen Right?! You’re worth $400Million Tarik.  Just not for your B-ball skills😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lidstrom who pretty much showed the word you dont have to hit to be the best defenceman.  Osgood who scared me when… https://t.co/GqvfqGGZNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CortiIgor @JeanetteJett @McNaughtStew @TheChrisDuarte @Asileaztuk @sfdcKokua @SwapMySwag @RobSalesforce Igor and I… https://t.co/yzBDidmkll]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when my cat thinks he’s being sneaky by walking slowly across like the room like a bad stop motion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aundrey_crane @LHSAA Yes...It was a little over a second before he released the ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@almost5feet Maybe the owners just needed a break and the new ones will keep it coffee shop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dontshootskrlx @shannonmctighe9 @State_Champs @HOBChicago @RyanScottGraham @dereksteez @tyszal @purenoiserecs That kick shot. 🙀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frpatrickop I thought the priesthood was a calling. Are you suggesting gay men are not called to the priesthood? M… https://t.co/b92ZOV8qKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerallChavez @nicaraguainvest More Military deserting from Venezuelan Army as response to the suffering Venezuelan… https://t.co/Rvy1N7BPpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If killing is such fun for him, there are still opportunities in Afghanistan and recruiters are waiting, but the co… https://t.co/pqmR1FYv5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raccoons Are hanging out on the L-train platform in #Canarsie and at least one masked critter took a ride. But whil… https://t.co/bL4CCQCB5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonadane @brycap00 @LakerFilmRoom You’re right https://t.co/q8unHcGqcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Day Lewis truly is outstanding.   His work in Lincoln is mesmerizing. #DanielDayLewis #Lincoln https://t.co/S6tt1qmZG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at I-96 &amp; Meadowbrook Rd (not an exit) in Novi, MI https://t.co/nQcr4KBc4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fiddler on the Roof @SpringmanMiddle and the incredibly talented cast @glenview34 #weared34 outstanding renditions… https://t.co/Dbvo43y7q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[40 days until @SFGiants opening day (photo i took from 2017) #MadBum https://t.co/UpkTqpGH2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandarines121 @trish_regan Socialist #Maduro took the guns from the people so they couldn't defend themselves. Tha… https://t.co/1ktiWWeIuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyPositivity Man I think anybody from this city who sees it will likely smile. Glad you enjoyed it, brother]]></document><document><![CDATA[RSD1373: 2 miles easy after a relaxing day visiting with friends.  Thank God for the gift of this day! @ West Meado… https://t.co/873Lq5f1iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Baltimore Marriott Waterfront https://t.co/Y0ny8wX8iR]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when you try to be friendly to the curmudgeon social security office employee. My bad, that joke was funny to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sources: Jags expected to sign Foles next week https://t.co/kLcOoEz8xp NICK FOLES TO JACKSONVILLE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Borderland Beat Book: In Search for La Linea https://t.co/El33zRHzlF https://t.co/UPTNpEQriP]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only day i see mayra at school she calls me a crackhead,,, should i be offended?]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the recent scandal in N Carolina showed us that in the case of fraud by Repub officials, they don't have much t… https://t.co/T3Fs3j2oeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vops16 @C_Shovald I did not assume that at all. I dont care what you classify as or are arguing for, my position c… https://t.co/LJAyqhCgeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGPAPI08170011 @dhruv_ky @Ballislife @vernoncarey22 Notice the hat he’s wearing. I’m ROFL too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I consider trial by jury as the only anchor ever yet imagined by man, by which a government can be held to the prin… https://t.co/37f6jO395A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up with a damn panic attack from @espn this morning thinking the Flyers traded @28CGiroux or @GrittyNHL with t… https://t.co/LcB9auaco5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@galenhdec @McLaffyTaffy Oh no Galen don’t worry, he said he’s talking about professionals he’s *paid* in the past. https://t.co/hHoqiXgpMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite images of Monroe, Monroe of the past. Judging by the vehicles in this image, I would say this wa… https://t.co/7CXkkOGPEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @daviduscigars with get_repost ・・・ A tradition of excellence...#cigars #cigar #diamondcrown… https://t.co/fIPDvN4MRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing tonight is when @sec officials made a call against KU they’d look at Cal and make sure he wasn’t mad. Happened over and over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. The Chicago Maroon: https://t.co/3Q1fy6aK25 7. WTTW Voters' Guide: https://t.co/eSOhbSeoBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nedryun I mean he admitted to firing Comey because of the Russia investigation, pretty clear cut case of obstruction of justice]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Lotte Korean supermarket and @yearsandyears is played on the speakers -- I feel seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colominaM @Insulza Y quien nunca tuvo la gallardia de responder al resonante "Insulzo", Un claro insulto a su fami… https://t.co/JH17meJ3en]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question, is there a way I can stop Twitter from showing me tweets that people I follow "like", it has taken over m… https://t.co/kgF9QW4Dmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanWHendry @jonathanweisman It shows he has real influence even today and I can’t imagine how one could write… https://t.co/0HkGQPSpOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chukroxx Maybe it needs to be a thing. I said it recently, and now I’m very conscious, and self conscious about it… https://t.co/7D5CiDAdjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDMayer @SearchQueen @RepDanCrenshaw Thank you Dan. No one seems to be addressing the disenfranchisement of Am… https://t.co/h6MRv5CqmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katmindu @JCrongeyer @marcorubio Maybe something about " Palm " Sunday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinsteinMaga @SenWarren Well, I guarantee you that Elizabeth "Pocahontas" Warren would get an honorable mention, at least.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zombot5 For me, it was and continues to be corned-beef hash with sourdough toast and over-medium eggs.  HBU?  #tbh #trufax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vandave @Nemo_o @SteveSaretsky @TheBubbleBubble @HaakonPedersen @HamzahKingKhan @catosletters @cryptomarkets2… https://t.co/1EtQIZwV3G]]></document></documents></author>