<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Great story about River Garden Farms.  Fun Ag. coincidence - my family farmed near River Garden Farms year’s ago an… https://t.co/5dIXiGCu4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @seanhannity Good luck Terrance!  We are rooting for you!  You have lots of love in your life. You are a Blessed man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brought the biggest Price Is Right fan (Dad!) to #tpirlive! https://t.co/78gGLU3q77]]></document><document><![CDATA[I too, thank God every day for my father, and for the man who stepped in as my father when mine couldn't and didn't… https://t.co/I3joywCcT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you take a vacation day to meet the plumber at 8:30, and he cancels your appointment at 8:00.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best day is massage day! Book now and receive your first in home session with a discount of over $25!! Text or… https://t.co/7yYYEBPeuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are good pictures of Jon, there are great pictures of Jon, and then there are perfect pictures of Jon. Say he… https://t.co/WAg6oy6dIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Rhett  ...The Burnham’s and Soliday’s are so excited to see you, your family and your team at the nationals in K… https://t.co/uLASpb8upb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsnorris11 @try2actnormal Me too — one of my now favorite media day quotes as well! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianneIsHere i’m in the clear. (no offense intended, myspace tom! i’m sure you’re probably a cool person.) https://t.co/VWlOeN4gJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't post about our last two campgrounds...oh well, no pics from Creekfire near Savannah, but this is Blythe Is… https://t.co/6xCggIQZ5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realestate #ventura #home #house #luxury #beach #ocean #water #dock #dockside #luxurylifestyle #luxuryrealestate… https://t.co/pjraiKVLRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great start to our Makerspace today!! @BegleyBroncos https://t.co/BT1m1Xs3iL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mogambo on @tcm now! ♥️ Ava Gardner, Clark Gable &amp; Grace Kelly in this classic film!🍿📺 https://t.co/2CTknwcCv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grooms_brody You’re the sweetest. I feel so lucky to be apart of your life. I’m so glad I have you for the rest of… https://t.co/KUMK8mul6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[General Sherman’s Tree - Sequoia National Park @ Sequoia National Park, California https://t.co/W1KPAhpopT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, stressed and scalped, after watching the #BigOleFreak Video... https://t.co/tZCsySZKpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meowmix67 @DonaldJTrumpJr And your dumb ass will pay for both of us to leach off the system then. 🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only question is, why not invest in yourself and your body?! https://t.co/K4gXRegEKc https://t.co/Rdj96VAq9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERomanReigns TY Roman for making our night great again just by being back in ur yard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warriorsworld Shit. What have I done wrong. I’m not blocked by him?! https://t.co/2uGM86IY7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry @IDWPublishing I don’t think we’re going to settle down until @emtothea’s is back filming. #FightforWynonna]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EmployeeEngagement doesn’t take a fortune of perks. It’s the simple things that make a difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofakinglame @ClosexOut @LessIsMorley91 Hm. But I’ve been asking him for MONTHS to call me that 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivePD #LivePDNation @PascoSheriff #9PMRoutine Doors locked. Snuggled under my blanket with a cup of tea watching… https://t.co/PNXWknLnDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Viva México Cuarones! 4th Oscar of Cuarón. 5th consecutive Oscar for best director given to a mexican.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2day my mom bought me this blue heart from Great Wolf Lodge @ Vaughan Mills Road https://t.co/QdrfZ9PAeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdelaineMorin Don’t have a wheelchair, but got a huge scar down my back🤪😉 https://t.co/dyaOBJaZUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPAmericanMom I will never forget seeing him come off that plane on a stretcher.   I still hear his moans in my s… https://t.co/sME5GDMdIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to have been in tonight's audience for the invited dress of Eugene Onegin at Washington National Opera. Co… https://t.co/4ZkfMtGAFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the kind of person that sees your pregnancy announcement and thinks, “you would.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the heck did Ryan do with carly,  and is felicia next!? @GeneralHospital]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best 2019 Wholesale Bath Towel Manufacturers USA https://t.co/CaCdFX5gwG #bathtowelsinbulk #wholesaletowels… https://t.co/LxAkW6CLbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @BreitbartNews You know my daughter loved @MileyCyrus when they were both children.  But their pol… https://t.co/YC2pi7z0an]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lcalvin65 Thank you for volunteering!  My girl was competing on an elementary team today!  #GirlsInSTEM #ourladyofmtcarmel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrity weddings mean nothing to me, but I am finding myself constantly checking for @chancetherapper’s wedding p… https://t.co/ltToytnzAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there’s any advice I can give, it’s to not be with someone that you need reassurance from. If someone genuinely… https://t.co/NdrDnAgIB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is such a pig. Signing her Bob and then then touching a bible. Please let's not put this on children or on survi… https://t.co/WIxgyaqUsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump @BrownDavidb1202 I am praying she puts his ass in a cell today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, since they released the #frozen2 trailer, and it’s #cutiesaturday, have a Queen Elsa. I’ll fix it up later, o… https://t.co/Upbj5KacGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG ITS FEBRUARY 28th and I just realized this! If you know me you know why I’m so excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson @LindaHaleRCSD Maybe she was on both sides at Charleston too! She is a flake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deabting  If I Wanna Attend This Party Tomorrow  Ion Want To Cause Me &amp; This Bitch Got Into Yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never believe the fact that somebody can have access to the finest cuisine and chefs all over the world and… https://t.co/FvuDkdNsHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[A STAR IS BORN (2018) co-written and directed by Bradley Cooper #secondtimearound https://t.co/XMFMDOSOBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRickScott @JeffBezos @amazon Did I stop a heart attack? I’ve been very stressed, yesterday walking dogs I had a… https://t.co/YM9NASHQlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREE FREE FREE FREE FREE ・・・ PAPI BOY FRIDAY'S WAS OFF THE HOOK LAST FRIDAY W/1200+ PARTY PEOPLE #mickysweho THIS F… https://t.co/R697fXRe8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donut 🍩 Disturb #SundayMorning  #SundayBrunch #sunday #beachbutfirst #coffee #sunbathing https://t.co/FStAUrSD8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to strong women. May we know them. May we be them. May we raise them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mena_ganey @Nicholas_Dean_ @SpeakerPelosi Live in a red state. Nancy Pelosi has been in Congress for decades. What… https://t.co/tIptEg8mKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coastalent1 @TamaraBraun @lldubs @wesramsey @finolahughes @EmmeRylan @parryshen @japastu @Theehendrickson… https://t.co/UqZT0UBeUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOY TE QUISIERA #DECIR Cómo quisiera decirte que no dejo de pensar que nos faltó mucho por vivir y que aunque sí fu… https://t.co/ZvCPosPxOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The desire in my heart is to be loved so fearlessly by somebody. I will not allow myself to not feel chosen every… https://t.co/6MmnsNazjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woahhhhh kisses. #puppylove #puppiesarecrazy #chesapeakebayretriever #bigboy #happiness #happy #lovemypuppy… https://t.co/CPWefukAM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO So......women around the world and especially in the United States should not have access to hygiene… https://t.co/ykhAxPqA9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YatesSQL I will submit to #SQLSatLouisville if I can meet the pug while I'm there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VIPCOLLEENROSE @mysexyjenna @disponiblesub I am, but I am also allergic lol!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I signed up for a writing class and I have so much anxiety about sharing creative writing with people https://t.co/Shi8uukazs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listened to @realpinksweats for this first time tonight and WOOOOOOOW. https://t.co/71Y8Xh1R7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else remember that era of twitter where the hardcore Bieber fans aka Beliebers wanted twitter to make them v… https://t.co/iCZhYh2jd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amym1972 @wivk1077 @JenniferNettles Whoaaa! That’s weird timing lol you best believe ima go sit in my car!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews America's wall is keeping out human traffickers, drug traffickers, gangs, terrorists, and illegals s… https://t.co/K76u1qCqV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet these courses are very often the first to be dropped when financial resources get tight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No hay nada mejor que rodearte de amigos creativos y talentosos, dejen a esa gente que no les trae nada productivo a su vida. 🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[However, as these countries are now pursuing policies of Omanisation and other nationalisation programmes, we can e… https://t.co/KUGiLcD9DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, @realDonaldTrump was right about one thing. I’m definitely tired of all this “winning”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosemaryanherb @adndotcom @BlairBraverman Rosie, you’re amazing! Thanks for keeping us all up to date on what’s happening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThursdayThoughts @philliesfan1000 @Goldengal301 @bean_cheile @Claire_1224 @bcmom5 @stefawils  @LGiaPeace… https://t.co/tL7BSrZkwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrooperBob_SC how I personally feel about my Monday https://t.co/7Z9o256fef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drdrew What did medical school teach you about being a leader?   Jen Schmith, Saint Francis University  #theNSLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Who do you think you are?” Is my favorite song https://t.co/pSVPSGjUVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sobre você:  1. t 2. 31/03 3. orgulhoso 4. sim 5. 15 6. nao 7. sushi  8. carisma 9. po kkk nao sei 10. sim 11. sim… https://t.co/oKoWi7rRRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a little context: everyone at work looked at me like I was nuts when I referred to the @MicrosoftTeams “arrow”… https://t.co/65D5IpgfnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xomarcelinexo It was 30+ hours of work, and I lost about 20 hours of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pcos really sucks!!! I have been in so much pain for the past two days and can barely even move so my wonderful bo… https://t.co/D0Zbe5M62e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally been sleeping all day only time I was up was for grocery shopping lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJonesFPS I don’t even go to Fairfield public schools but I’m still gonna tell you that this was a terrible call… https://t.co/N1MP3a7rgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I fuck up now, I’d be proving to everyone who expected that to be true]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier This was her choice not something forced on her and she did it with the consequence of PAYING her ow… https://t.co/K0Waj0cpvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LITERALLY HAVE A TYPO IN EVERY TWEET I HAVE I SWEAR I CAN SPEAK ENGLISH YALL AND DIDNT JUST GET OFF THE BOAT A WEEK AGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Tayshia for planning a date I’m actually interested in watching. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siwonchoi Good morning Siwon Choi and I love you so much and I miss you. https://t.co/9uQbf5ZfEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[if God hadn’t already promised us to never flood the Earth again, I’d be building an ark right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right. @CBP doesn't have "capacity" to handle 29 parents. One of the most over funded agencies on the planet that c… https://t.co/tq0NDjCooT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triiiistan_ @Hannasuewilson girl can i just say YOUR EYEBROWS ARE PERFECT👏🏼🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 31, Married, And Never Want Kids. Leave Me The Hell Alone. https://t.co/IvfEnEIH4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[swear I keep seeing the word bloom every where I turn. I guess this is the year I bloom baby🌸💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[😻😻😻😻😽😽 @BeckyLynchWWE @bobsaget @ReneeYoungWWE @TJWilson @EdgeRatedR @TheBethPhoenix @EandCPod @NatbyNature https://t.co/0LUp8w90GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thetas when                Thetas when they see you                         you   haven’t bought… https://t.co/UQR7pGXdEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi babies! Plumeria cubensis seeds from @Scott_Zona collected Cuban Plumeria now growing @FairchildGarden https://t.co/XTlVACFVal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is a gif --&gt; Thinking of you @RhedaLosekamp #NationalMargaritaDay #friday https://t.co/NYerpHDAyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! Make sure to remind the special people in your life how much you love them. ❤️❤️ https://t.co/piQpBtS22F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: Went to sleep. Woke up. Ate my emergency rations for the day(pepperoni pizza hotpocket) Watched an anime. Th… https://t.co/QSmu9me9ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joeingram1 Bc they can’t yell at the shuffler, variance or themselves, so they...nevermind, they’re just assholes.🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoverDov123 @KFearri @petergraigs @social_stars @Bren_O1967 @MySwilly @ERKRadio2017 @TonyaRBlue1 Lol that too!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Chapel Mar 10, 2019  ========== Seven - The Word of Salvation -Week 2 Follow along with this weeks' sermon note… https://t.co/qh85a0cZpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Project Manager/Senior Project Manager/Senior Project Coordinator of Plannin… https://t.co/PWHuDBMAyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Sale coming soon, follow us do you don’t miss out.   #sale #springsale  #newspringmakeup #fusionofcolor… https://t.co/oIUAfi3mEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afbarron @wbtourhollywood Jajaja Wonder Woman tmb se apendeja a veces, seguro..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTalmadge breaking out the receipts on Bernard's civil rights "arrest."  But he chained himself to a black lady… https://t.co/113o2OONKi]]></document></documents></author>