<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@d_sevareid @soniaharcourtxx @ShiriAllwood It’s going to be a long month! 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some notable nuggets from Tom Herman post 1st spring practice:  •OL Patrick Hudson is done with 🏈 as a player due t… https://t.co/hnUhHiav1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been torn up about this fucking robot for three days and I don’t care who knows it I LOVE YOU OPPY GOOD JOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beap24j Muy buenos días parcerita y feliz sábado tengas tu por allá cuídate mucho saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister I’m not going to listen to anymore misinformation. We must stand together! Hopefully, there will be… https://t.co/sdmJlfLgI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP Rep. Justin Amash: Trump 'is Violating our Constitutional System' https://t.co/3FNErl4ENK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ArielRush Try a devotion in the morning....and gurl listen to gospel pandora on ur commute! IT HELPS so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamJahn14 @MonMcP65 @ramincol @CheckGinny @PHXRisingFC @EnergyFC @USLChampionship Nah my dude, you are! See you soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachB_BROWN 6’3 232 Freshman Beast Juco Inside Linebacker, Full Qualifier, can transfer ASAP 4 years to Play 3, h… https://t.co/rkkfJHkGrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did nothing but respect that woman for over 3 years. And even when we weren’t together last year and she was stil… https://t.co/nEdfYats4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noilean Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to bed at 5 AM because of the time change...because 4 AM is of course a reasonable bedtime...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to all my Houston people. Love this city. This weather ain’t it though. #Houston #Love #Htown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our weekly game! #d&amp;d #dungeonsanddragons #caravanguards @ Непин https://t.co/RGMtdxI6Jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your “B” plan leads to your “A” plan destination too. #ilovephotography #ilovenyc #streetphotography #mtanyc… https://t.co/CyBavB0bqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaltTrapper @thgrace78_grace I bet, that all I use is 1 or 2lb mono, except on my walleye poles, 4lb mono]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lifting lavish Love and you have touched each part of time. And we are frozen intentions resting on lips. https://t.co/HWFG0n65sX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmmm....brisket and grits..... Courtesy of @grapicavoli @theshoesurgeon special collaboration dinner. Thank you zel… https://t.co/cAkHK71d75]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun seeing the Gin Blossoms at the House of Blues with my wife Mindy and my sister-in-law Veronica. @ House… https://t.co/MoFxAWb44z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLigaEN I find it very very frustrating it’s so hard to watch la liga games now in the US.   Many cable providers… https://t.co/A9lrGDCnyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddieBarry8 Well of course it is. Everyone should chk the last episode of 60 minutes(March 3rd). Case in the supreme court as we speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi my name is Austin and this is how I study for cell bio exams (sound on) https://t.co/8f6JVS1EQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else window shop for houses daily on the internet, can’t just be me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2020Again @buckscience @DTrumpPoll @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @BarackObama How do you know how much cash trump has?… https://t.co/Qx1xrBhCAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome commentary on leadership. It isn’t what can everyone do for me but what can we do for our people in buildin… https://t.co/lLyapgsU5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi im not rly a kpop stan anymore but everyone in the #CaratSelcaDay tag is absolutely gorgeous ily all youre so beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MussartAhmadzeb إنڈین پائیلٹ کی رھائی کو کشمیر پر مذاکرات سے مشروط کیا جائے]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisfitsTamara X-Men has had so many iterations with so many approaches. I think first you've got to decide on the… https://t.co/TNGmtXP7Aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to smoke dinner... Can’t wait! Life is Good! #chef #smokedmeat #yum #husbandmaterial #humbled @ Broad… https://t.co/jEMcLOweyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[ACCORD DE RÉPARATION OU ACCORD DE POURSUITE SUSPENDUE  (APS)? Après une semaine plusieurs médias québécois parlent… https://t.co/7ccM1MoWh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeekInStupid @AnitaM86 @mxpalazzo @tomwatson @BernieSanders The other 50 pages of it.  All of Elizabeth Warren's a… https://t.co/uLAsDoIz2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @BrittanyBegley @kristyn_wcpo @AshleeBaracy @lynnmlilly @TanyaORourke @lindacardellini @AngelAlessandra… https://t.co/EQ8bPKZwnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsBBell Good morning Mrs Bell! Happy #ThirstyThursday https://t.co/jJ59lMcFyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marleneMC63 @hallmarkchannel You aren’t terrified at the thought of .... ROSEMARY’S BABY??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ienaxo Oof appreciate the confidence 😂😂but I have no clue ! I always see people taking about One piece and Jojos b… https://t.co/X18s49eCYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARISDENNARD @KatrinaPierson @realDonaldTrump @campusreform This person spoke about the flag. The words are not to… https://t.co/PTR2YUwI7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I propose a cheat sheet for @DarcyLRoss with the bits info, taped to the Darcy-facing side of the front of the table.  😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve not been incredibly successful being back in bham. Like, I’m starting to look physically better again but I ha… https://t.co/J845onb0tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearstownSox35 @tyltsports My friend and I are going to the Sox vs Blue Jays game on a Sunday in May this year, hope to see you there 😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haaylirae What the hell is going on in Portland? I never thought it would be a haven for neo-nazis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Yes. But it’s not going to succeed with him. The sooner he’s impeached and removed, the s… https://t.co/kHP4iEoxfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amer62718488 أتفهم نقطتك.. لكن الفكره يكون تطبيقها صعب أو مستحيل هنا أختلف معك.. بكل بساطه التميمة تقدر تاخذ شبه م… https://t.co/mf1kTqpphe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwinfield_51 @Deadspin I watch Patriots football and glad I do. They are winners. Those guys who celebrate when th… https://t.co/tT9kX6dFe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[LG2s 1st birthday is on Tuesday and he loves the #BabyShark song. 🎶  I could have bought him a little shark toy, bu… https://t.co/9QbZ17gt8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 3: Cocalico back in it, trailing 36-28. Eagles pick up intensity at both ends in the 3rd, getting rewarded]]></document><document><![CDATA[VANTAGE CAREER CENTER Open House and Taste of Vantage Monday, February 25, 5-7:30 p.m. Tickets to try tasty foods f… https://t.co/2Dal1n47uX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THPGolf @jlshuff @SrixonGolf @JB_THPGolf Congratulations! Great way to start the day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelixSalMac Hay viejo payaso con eso de cambiar a los Ministros.Cuando Usted Fue Alcalde de #Acapulco lo unico que… https://t.co/WJ8Qq3DL1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pchdotcom 😎😎😎 @Freebiesmom1   get these and send to me Get @maistotoys  @wellytoys_welly   Rest. https://t.co/fO6E0u0hVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Nigerian pastors dey see vision... Pls i need  5 numbers to win Powerball jackpot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Miami Real Estate 🏡 Source.  Helping Buyers And Sellers for the past 23 years.  Experience is not Expensive-it… https://t.co/6BNmCIj4p8]]></document><document><![CDATA[throwback to when I was youthful and glowing...now I am only ever tired and sweaty https://t.co/Ce4hpl02ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP More than 100 Dems support this plan that would [KEY WORD] force the more than 150 million Americans [SO FIGUR… https://t.co/TpDbpulQlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich Wife and I had tickets to A Night for Freedom last night but unfortunately couldn’t make it. Congrats on… https://t.co/7q5SgLx8Qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments The act of a desperate man who happens to be a sociopath as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realllllly strong start for the Shockers after Day 1 of the Indoor AAC Championships.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gloves Up 🥊 @MikeTyson style https://t.co/KyuuOeZigK cc @Abdul_Qadir41 #21DayCkChallenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[As crucial as it is to understand other’s cultures and be fluent in other’s languages, I would argue it is as cruci… https://t.co/6NGD5vUSeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnarchaMaenad @AOC Have some coffee enjoy a good day ..... be kind to people ... don’t be so negative lol .. it wa… https://t.co/Tso5qORI5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re hiring! Breakfast cook position- must have some kitchen experience and be available M-F 5am-1pm. To inquire a… https://t.co/DLLgvsGLHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss Only if the GOP were to suddenly grow a set...  he gave them a handful Valium in 2017 and they’ve been… https://t.co/KQpDsjPHkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summitfarms_llc 3 inch pumps twice as fast as 2 in. How big is your spray tank? If in no big hurry 2 in. Ok!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇩🇪👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss https://t.co/iCpaNr9rNn The White RACE German BLONDES👑🇩🇪Women Are The MOS… https://t.co/0Eh9VJYoOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPBrody We met on the set of @NikkiGlaser show and shook hands.  You are a funny man and gone too soon. https://t.co/vpfLZ7PZJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great pickup for the Patriots. Will was a fantastic Beach Bum for 3 seasons. 3 time all-star. Solid defen… https://t.co/skMuyF8GgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[No y'all was that good. Yall stayed together &amp; LeBron legacy would be in trouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolfganghawkeye It’s already happened!  I’ve never seen a player blow out a shoe like that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a great privilege to talk with Jacky Ickx and Amelia founder Bill Warner yesterday. Live tv coverage today o… https://t.co/p36rcSJkQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @paulkrugman And Krugman hasn’t been right about anything his entire career. Perfect you pick him as your support]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of my friends like my music taste so I need some to come see @JuiceWorlddd &amp; @THESLUMPGOD w me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Voted no because the measure was not strong enough!!!!    It didn’t name the racists in democrat caucus!!!    You DONT GET IT!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lscott1967 @MarkBedell_KCPS @kcpublicschools @LatinxEdCo @KauffmanKSI @ewilkinsonkc So true!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t need to nag because you’re not@my grumpy old woman you’re my@bright beautiful woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcpoll Find anything of interest about the address of that building he dumped?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrisDCasa Great series.  I look forward to to every issue.  This last one was bananas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waldorf Women finish 2nd and the Waldorf Men were 4th in the North Star Athletic Association T&amp;F Championships: https://t.co/KS399JvYM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the time of my life at Katie’s bday party last night! #TwentyFun #IGotToWearAFunHat #HBD #Bae @ Auburn, Alabama https://t.co/Ae22aj3p0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel I hope your state is watching you. What harm could this bill actually do? If it is your intent tha… https://t.co/FpCi4qMsOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MigiRod1901 @BleacherReport Am I doing this right!? https://t.co/TabGVbijgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you've ever bought a @Ford other than a throaty V-8 Mustang or a giant truck, then you should be recalled, too.  #FordRecall #1stGear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMongan_ @AOC #She went didn’t she ! Big Numbers and growing . She works]]></document><document><![CDATA[Layering dove #unity #valentines #redgold #saffron #flyfree #bird #poetic #graffiti #peace #wip Go #ART #❤️🎨… https://t.co/XLiU2hPeZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of thing doesn’t happen to people where I’m from. To folks with my background. The impostor syndrome in m… https://t.co/ykd1uagcYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist @AreLights @RobAnderson2018 @Twistnshout50 @AmazonMandy2000 @nicj9311 @RolundDad @UomoDiRazzo… https://t.co/nQg5WNKqMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Looks like Bloomberg just got a lesson in tax reform 101]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to have a good time while watching gameplay that makes you feel better about your own?! Well, I’m #Live!… https://t.co/Yj6KCZ9tpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rex_rexchapman @BigOrangeMack Total charge ... but that was one hell of a scorpion landing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seals_881 I loved Comcast Business, I called drunk at 23:00 because my internet was down and I wanted to download… https://t.co/wPRvkG8GjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raybrewer21 @lvlightsfc That belief has to start with the coach or it can never be realized.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never seen this happen on the pitch but I have a game at 7 today, @peet2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myffburner @JakeAndersonFF @aaron_schill @MG_Dynasty @DynastyTradesHQ @MyFantasyLeague @FFDynastyTrades… https://t.co/BnN7XgdjQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FWLRmusic @EthaniBoy @dyl________ @PrometheanS1gma @RlOTmusic @bossfightswe it was weird bc im used to hearing it… https://t.co/3lvYk0Wtad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee weather  7am-9am: light flurries 9am-10am: raisin-sized hail 10am-   : Tropical thunderstorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fotogurl44 and I found a Mediterranean Style Chicken meal kit from @TopsMarkets that looked like a fun adventure!… https://t.co/1FeCnSDyfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch time GDA gets the job done. I prefer to take vitamins mid day vs in the morning due the fasting schedule I ma… https://t.co/6yB9UWebgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world will always try 2 get ur attention in some way, shape, or form. It’s best 2 keep ur mind filled w/ the… https://t.co/21SMJNm46N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DynastyTradesHQ @DynastyTrades @DynastyTrader @DynastyFFAddict @MyFantasyLeague  @DynastyQandA @BrazilDynastyFF… https://t.co/qNNPJnehVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enrique_Rojas1 Que dices de los Dodgers y Harper Enrique??? Se hace o no??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanfieldDan i like 90s and early 2000s too. and damn man, i can’t stand cardi b lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look I’ll give credit when it’s due. This is great news if true. Hopefully decision is not already decided like som… https://t.co/DWGYptYD8x]]></document></documents></author>