<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jrj12 Pretty much. Although I’d be surprised if she was punished in any way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YEMolly @Mac10colorado @mikelowetpt I used to like the ny styles slices at the well in highlands best but not cons… https://t.co/HqoyebDLiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcicilline @suekhi Donald Trump has a genuine smile on his face which is unusual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XaviersRealm007 @BrianParticelli @marieclaire @ConstanceWu It takes a lot more to get people to the theater now. T… https://t.co/5DveXgVbtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never understand how guys can post about no “female” being there for them when you’re out here curving the one… https://t.co/BVxqylLFd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Comic Con a little boy had lost his dad in the crowd, and was scared... #humor #tee-hee #grin #hilarious https://t.co/PaCHJhlQBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlersVanilla Did you complete the ice is the question everyone wants to know tho  😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[More from @DBetances68 on his own contract extension talks ... his agent Jim Murray has engaged in talks with Cashm… https://t.co/3EpYc4mdrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍😍😍 Repost by @team_danmiller  with (get_repost)... #ErikMichaelMonday 💖💖 @ Maryland https://t.co/ovblaPqY4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex don’t mean none , a dick get hard for anybody a nigga can be deep inside u n still not feel u , stop braggin on… https://t.co/o6RyuHfsPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Therefore as the fire devoureth the stubble, and the flame consumeth the chaff, so their root shall be as rottennes… https://t.co/edbOX5zymV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Volunteering for the CCAWR today at the Waterloo Region Museum's BHM event. Getting to meet some awesome people😊.… https://t.co/6BjGxGw05r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyskaye so I recently learned that he has a british accent so that’s cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elissawashuta I need a weighted blanket, since dog doesn’t like to cuddle in bed 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics Cohen who can’t seem to understand questions is a lawyer?  Yea, he’s not as stupid as appears.  Just a liar who plays games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorLorenz @the_wing Do you drink juice? Or we can do B12 shots (it’s an injection, not alcohol!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you meet new friends and end up staying until 2:00am, have a 30 min drive home, and have to get up at 5:45am… https://t.co/F0UkPa05qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[when ur on birth control it’s the whole month   essentially it does not stop   but during period it’s a little bit… https://t.co/cWzYLEAHK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProjectK9Hero Please accept my condolences on the loss of this military hero. May you find the Peace in knowing th… https://t.co/5RALSMLEA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting school today! Your never too old to learn something new♡ Happy Friday Y'all!😉🤠 https://t.co/9KVQiI0keC]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay... this made me dislike Kirpa a little less... this is actually so funny 😂  Kirpa’s Chin Injury - The Bachelor… https://t.co/64Scd13gOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaProfera Hi! I love the one on your index finger in the first pic, but I can’t dm you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A disturbing discovery in Bethesda, MD. Human remains were found in a bag near a bus stop last night. https://t.co/9y0K3LN5zO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieMcGrawx looking good my daughter and I are talking about how nice you always look!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve never wished for something so much before lol. but i still know the truth so this is gonna suck😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catherinem23 @lancslassrach @art_cathyhunt @meesterkurt @mathycathy Yes ma’am! Anything to help teachers! Such an honor to be included.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axidentaliberal @SallyDeal4 @ICEgov @realDonaldTrump So let me get this straight, protesting against racism and an… https://t.co/LQLawZMp6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colton @BachelorABC @kristisunshine3 Since Kirpa was sent home then Taysia should get sent home too although she g… https://t.co/YE8U7PKiyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur @JoyAnnReid Then there is a terrible misunderstanding. Late term abortions happen because there’s a tra… https://t.co/ggbTvkWYgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’ALL... So I had class on President’s Day, and I’m the president of the club for my degree program, and this is wh… https://t.co/tAAJEpJwvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VerlettaWhite @WesternTechLax @sgregorybcps One of my absolute favs too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You too will be pleasantly surprised with the sudden change of events, as I intervene for you,” says the LORD.  “Y… https://t.co/4BgS7tDZuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silvia Yazly Torres Sarmientos, 19 y Yazmin Alexa Gonzáles Jáquez, 17,   heridas al derrapar en una motocicleta en… https://t.co/mMc7CJvG0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaAndriana @ksb78 It's aggravating as hell to get the strong impression that Black cis and straights don't under… https://t.co/yHjWibeLe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disabled or not. You don’t have a right to park like this https://t.co/DW6Nv13KpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrtonylewisjr We appreciate your work with @DYRSDC community based residential programs.❤ #slugg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArikaSato @Poshmarkapp That’s weird. It must have been an automated tweet ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFEliteSports @DallasWings @brooke_bun @2022CyFairAtx @austin_cyfair @nikecyfairlewis @NikeCoop @cyfaireliteDTX… https://t.co/36TQnFuPyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @adidassoccer, I want to #MasterControl on the pitch! Tweet one below to learn which cleat is perfect for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just woke up from a nap and looked at the pictures I took of my painting I’m working on, and for a second was sho… https://t.co/6PhItGE8FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, I love Kandi but her &amp; Todd are boring  #rhoa https://t.co/4GhZRC7ZRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveyourpetday 🐶🐶#shovelingsnow #snowmuchfun #snowiestfebruaryeverrecorded 8-10”  #onlyinmn_winter ❄️ @ Prior Lake… https://t.co/aj3T1oUaji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sen_JoeManchin   https://t.co/oGjwc4SpT2. I hope your staying Dem, gives your party a chance to b/c same again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Liberals have nothing to hide, why are they working so hard to hide something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning from hell. Can I ever come to work in a good mood and not find anything wrong when I come in? 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanBacaro porque no han aprendido nada en 20 años, incluyendo una lección aún más vieja: separación de Iglesia y Estado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr In cuffs, at the federal courthouse? In an orange jumpsuit? Testifying before Congress? Getting arr… https://t.co/yVBdekkeRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is a good idea I was Born to get it My age is not the best? I like to hear you are feeling 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner with my parents Wednesday 😎❤ @ Jacala Mexican Restaurant https://t.co/tZ7oItCZlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[U ever feel so irritated and frustrated that u just end up crying yea that’s me right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catswithnohope What a cute kitty,shes probably been taking a nap already so she is ready to pounce!!😂🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump-defender left speechless after CNN analyst reads anti-Semitic Trump quote over his objections https://t.co/JpLsc4zjbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've only been in for an hour and I got done all my tasks and pre-planned next week... What's am I suppose to do for the next 8 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too all the Women out their be proud everyday! To my Cushings Community I ♥️ u all! #warriors #keeponfighting… https://t.co/l6nYNGlAId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ha ha ha! I guess mc cabe on 60 minutes is getting you unhinged. The truth comes to light like it… https://t.co/th6IvQpTvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCThisisUs Was that love at 1st sight or was that soul recognition or maybe a combination of both ❤ #BethsBackStory #ThisIsUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[it's almost 2 am on valentine's day &amp; im alone watching scary movies ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[About yesterday: me at the #GoldenGateBridge #view from the lovely #sausalito  • • #travel #travelling… https://t.co/NM6s9jRidx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know understand why people say its worth it to spend hundreds of dollars on a dress because it’s so beautiful and is definitely worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geometry vocabulary team challenge!  @graciemespinoz4 @Jkuhlmann4567 @NISDLeonSprings #ThisIsLeonsprings… https://t.co/HYuUTP1fPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenNollWeather Talk to us Benny. Give us a tweet. Please tell us there’s snow, freezing rain or sleet! Hey Benny b… https://t.co/q2qdXLCUZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poniss_CHET that feel when ur having two entirely separate convos on two different platforms, it’s lit]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dogs shaking and panting is shaking my who bed and it feels like my brain is going to explode this fucking ativan is doing fuck all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started David Dobrik &amp; Jason Nash’s podcast and wow they literally have gotten so far.. I NEED to meet them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McPersonfaceFS @VAWrestling @itsvedatime @JayLeeAC @BGBgroup @SCSOpod @SCsirens @HIACTalkRadio Follow my insta sto… https://t.co/GRb5auhsKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun is making me very nostalgic and sad that its not summer and warm]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are substantial governance structures through the continuum of health care]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yankeecannuck @PinkSparkleYums @steve45220 @dennisdiclaudio @MugabeJonathan @nypost Ur such a loser lol pls go cry somewhere else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone who has gotten us to this point! Our first birthday is in one month! Time flies when you're w… https://t.co/ByqhNzxu5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Other #TX  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/GMw9mysPyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad day. I was the biggest fan of Beverly Hills 90210 ❤️ https://t.co/S3MS2BcumZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidsirota You want to talk about something, talk about the size of his Crowd https://t.co/M54cUQJpOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee Brewery FTW - Best renovation - Large #MBJBuildingMemphis Awards!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does this look like a new chapter in his Trapped in The Closet saga? #Rkellyinterview #RKelly #WednesdayThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love lamp. Collected a bunch of cast-off forest debris yesterday and made stuff, mostly little lamps. This one wa… https://t.co/dC6JZ21tUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barrolracer @dbongino Um... Democrats are not trying to control a woman's right to choose what's best for her body… https://t.co/wyWoiRgz9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Size Goal: I need to be in a good enough shape to go to Carnival next year 💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmlewis517 @Astral_AR @SenatorNasheed @OpenSorceress @ArlanWasHere @Backstage_Cap Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[summoning circle hope this works                        🕯               🕯            🕯         🕯… https://t.co/fYSmbBCIdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RashidaTlaib @KamalaHarris @SpeakerPelosi @senchuckschumer @nytimes @maddow @ABC @CBS @washingtonpost… https://t.co/hWm2Bt2eYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m one of the people who says hi to people walking by, I’ll smile at the least.  When I travel out of the #Midwest… https://t.co/VpHjY5huJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Comets of chance and tides of circumstance sculpt the shorelines of the self to make us who we are...” #Figuring… https://t.co/cmK0ru3oQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genevieve in her element. #tbt  20110101 . . . . . . . #dogsofinstagram #dogsofinsta #greatpyrenees… https://t.co/gZv8ARDf7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LucyParker (Not chocolate fudge, obviously. peanut butter fudge is to die for, though!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t tell if my phone has been bugging out with autocorrect or my nails have gotten too long 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember deploying source safe for my team 15 or so years ago and look at where we are at now. #ifeelold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethlynn2196 swear the coach must giving some seriously motivational speeches in the locker room or sum because th… https://t.co/870vYVllDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her coochie look like if you put ya thumb between ya index and middle finger]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ama3ayc4Eq.  The deadline for youth participant signups is Thursday, Feb. 28, 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snow_z4_Luciano I’m sayin for yu to be able to give it up that’s good. some ppl be like they gone die without it]]></document><document><![CDATA[EPL referees are complete utter disgrace.....that was a foul on Allison the goal shouldnt have stood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have two birth order theories. One may hurt feelings, so I won’t share. The other though... You may feel it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He didn’t go too far however he should’ve discussed and notified the mother of his plans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennLynnG @TheHeatherAsh I use Elemis and LaTheripe(sp?). You can get it on https://t.co/Zb0sHK9O50. I use the nig… https://t.co/eOCW0iBxtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen, I only passed physics because I sat next to a future engineer, but this defies everything I ever copied off… https://t.co/MsErRRwFyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t resist checking out this Shaw’s on its last day being open. Kinda spooky, right? (cc @susantran @kc_downey… https://t.co/N4Aq0POcjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to this year's recipients and thank you for your efforts to advance gender equality! #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayPetelinWx Yay! Thank you for the clearing vibes! Supermoon is beautiful. It's practically daylight. I was being… https://t.co/qEhHi2gSut]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SignsYouAreAGoodPerson  I only throat punch people in my mind. https://t.co/N7wauMbbCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How about you giving up grabbing pussies for lent. https://t.co/5SKhPq7EtB]]></document></documents></author>