<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Back2DaJon Yes it definitely is. I wanna spend this weekend figuring out logistics and get started next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he’s having a problem with Trump’s use of such authority for the US, where was he when Obummer gave billions to… https://t.co/hltDmuAaAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[$LTC is about to fly these next several days! 3.2.1... #Profit #FillTheBag #FOMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? LEAD ENGAGEMENT SPECIALIST - PART TIME - https://t.co/cgCFCJUUOb #Denver, CO #EventsMarketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desperately missing the breathtaking views of Glacier NP today, we hope to be there soon! @ Highline Trail https://t.co/8owfcqmSo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADDiane VA is terrible! It should be eradicated and if you had the courage to serve our Country,  you get a card t… https://t.co/J2XkppMtB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senrobportman You consider Donald Trump as a man of integrity (he's a sex offender, marital infidelity, mob linked… https://t.co/o78Ut1CUUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter My wife sez you are the best for letting people know about dangers be it to there pet or to themselves… https://t.co/5ys32J9pAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Distorted Humor colt enjoying life! @ Mulholland Springs https://t.co/VqEEY2HfJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile got grilled for doing the same thing for Hillary at that @CNN debate.  We all already know @FoxNews i… https://t.co/D9QBtf7Kih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KokoKarabadjak @OnlyoneNationCa @TOAdamVaughan @cathmckenna @JustinTrudeau @gmbutts @cafreeland @HarjitSajjan… https://t.co/MswHOC6F1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something really feels amiss, it’s February and the #Bucks magic number to clinch a playoff spot is 5...boy have ti… https://t.co/fymYz54epJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guy @B_i_Z and his wife @RebecaNicole are doing their 1st @Skyway10K this morning!!! They are going to kill it!… https://t.co/PTkPSE15M1]]></document><document><![CDATA[New work. New process.  Untitled krylon and watercolor  on paper board 30 x 40 inches $400 (Unframed) https://t.co/5gcCUmppwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need your voice of hope. That voice that still believes that humans have the ability to love. Let us share this… https://t.co/FkMSC6BWQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Twin Peaks (San Francisco) https://t.co/MYTSHbs1jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impressive but if we bring honest each one getting swatted and I’m aiming for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter friends my mom is not doing well she is battling inoperable pancreatic cancer please could say a prayer for her.  TIA.  #WWG1WGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has to be the most stupid law suit ever. They will have to sue the world, not only America.  Thinking that Uni… https://t.co/alJK4qVJ2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 Pour Off @Molson_Canadian 🍺Ale ? @dmitriperov1 WTF ! @ThomasPKennedy3 @JohnLeksander Remember Great Days… https://t.co/A0b0beUOIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeForeman praying May God give your family some peace at this terrible time of loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fast-growing pot seller MedMen faces lawsuit by former insider: As California’s marijuana industry works to project… https://t.co/0V9Qmkpivy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing the cheers of this crowd is heartbreaking on this day of love.💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker said she’d never hear Return of the Mack before and I straight up had never been so upset at someone’s upbringing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleerwin This hashtag was disappointing and led nowhere https://t.co/L0yLYXa48V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn't look like there's any comeback tonight .. team looks flatter than a pancake that's been driven over by a st… https://t.co/pAvahV1g2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #IWD! One action to take contribute to @avfletcher’s crowd funding campaign!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo' @playaflym3 @moneybaggyo lilbaby_1 @BlacYoungstaFB @macsleepy @mrdontrip starlitogrindhard @Drake… https://t.co/0eRSDV5VmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, it’s too bad because I really did like a lot of it. Oh well! I still think it’s worth seeing because the act… https://t.co/9aaa6ErAmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @duxfeminafactii He gave a reason without giving a reason: political bias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I spent several hours talking race and the Church with an elder Christian who participated in the Selma March… https://t.co/d8kOtIfuFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate texting people that do nothing with their lives. Then like once a month, they have mental fuckin breakdowns… https://t.co/2tWuXyjQUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still in the Bahamas 🇧🇸😊👏🤟 #worldstar #worldtraveler #cruising #beer #relax #likemattjohnson #nevergiveup #smile https://t.co/CmewIFpD3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToonamiNews @MattShipmanVO  I've got to hear @MattShipmanVO voice #Floch on #AttackOnTitan on #Toonami early this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sallyacb275 @Farrell3Neil That’s a fantastic tribute. What a crowd too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside China's ghost cities | 60 Minutes Australia https://t.co/q8AlApc0aR via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackBoxAlerts @chasin_SOLES @stiff_titty_ Bro you are going to be in for quite a ride if you are trying to read t… https://t.co/qnYX6JYDHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[class was cancelled due to snow and I’m ahead on my assignments https://t.co/hWnNDKkqJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dthreetwo @MariaFurth @thehill Heeeere we go... https://t.co/KwIPMlLiQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump The only attacks I saw when trump was at the summit, I won't say when he was in Vie… https://t.co/V25Vwh8w3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1followernodad As is house cleaning. Nothing screams ‘tidy up the living room’ like an overdue manuscript.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicarrera Se necesitan 2 grandes plantillas.. ojalá el atlas se ponga las pilas.. para chivas es obligación ganar siempre al atlas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gPilkertone @JunksRadio @moneymetalcakes @EBJunkies @GlassJoeJP @drabtshirt 😂 I love cheese balls]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I've worn out the same old lines and now it seems, nothing's news to me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[A live look at the commute in Las Vegas this morning. #VegasWeather https://t.co/3zh7TXe8aD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monte Carlo, Principado de Monaco, Sur de Francia, Mar Mediterraneo. https://t.co/sDtDiTeoBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqtrivia jjustiz and I just gave my Dad his HQ t-shirt for his birthday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyEricMan @cspanwj Yeah the fake news media is obsessed with trump and anything they can say to discredit him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antihero_kate @LaakesKaleb You should be kicke off Twitter for this hate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at Regal Movie Theatre for a Double Movie Day: “BlacKkKlansman” and “Bohemian Rhapsody”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[James 1:12 Blessed is the one who perseveres under trial because, having stood the test, that person will receive t… https://t.co/p1SHiH7m1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouPDwifeSheri @FirefightersHOU And the dirty cops need ti be arrested and charged with 1st degree murder of 2 inn… https://t.co/HD3wanyjNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJDeplorable1 @IlhanMN @Ilhan She needs to be deported to a country that has Sharia Law]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You and your master Putin are the real enemies of America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCTimesSports @TreyHeinsius @NoahG_11 Great stuff! I was at this game too. Seems like forever ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does dunking help him on the field? If not why does this even matter? Why!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Italians and some Turkish leather walk in to a bar... #armandosimoniclub #fountainpen #montegrappaitalia @ Virg… https://t.co/Mofl9REyu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/k5jDpsumDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WILLIAMCRUM Also worth noting that hens lay a finite number of eggs. So...better have a plan for after she’s done… https://t.co/bAjjYSd7aR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmcmahon78 @GraceRandolph @Dolby Only for the moon sequence, but yeah, it is out of this world in IMAX. (No pun intended)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Montanaindy @caruso_ric @heidi_weigand @DIXIEDOODLE12 @930VM @realproudmom2 @LoveBling6 @tiffanyblue1122… https://t.co/hGhjqZWeNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePistilPacker You have friends. Myself, @JDPower9191 Meattrain, Huncho.....where did I last see these people....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why wouldn’t trump lawyers discussing pardons relating to investigation in any way with anyone ( like Cohen) be imp… https://t.co/i2ggrStzQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pophealth3 Ahhh yes. Well... that is why I wrote purrr. I’m building this for St. Louis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate hoes who over share personal shit after only knowing you for 5 mins]]></document><document><![CDATA[V/Day, Is 11:2. The Spirit of the Lord shall rest upon Him. The Spirit of Wisdom and Understanding, The Spirit of C… https://t.co/8Qn0hTEU9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliauci16 Ya estas respondiendo imbecil , serasnestupida onsimplemente perteneces a la asociación de sapingonau… https://t.co/moiV8wW2bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's today? March fourth? Guess that means it's time for a use to this year's Walkersville Marching Show.  Tune b… https://t.co/0USLs7OEgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBlumenthal You boob.  Why not get the details aka facts before opening your mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5/ The intensity really shot up in Season 1 Episodes 7/8 of @GameOfThrones. You could tell from the get that… https://t.co/zgkEHETrxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakee129 @BuehrlenbBallin @rhj_24324 Yeah wish I knew what the reason was. Not complaining if he doesn’t have an i… https://t.co/uYRTQW9WL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNatlInterest @HunterDeRensis The need for power becomes a deadly trap for the narrow minded, self-centered, ult… https://t.co/JzHpNJC41l]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many deaths will it take till we know that too many people have died ? Bob Dylan Remember Columbine . Remember… https://t.co/HYOi9wmaZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/epmVqFwXc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @NYCHA @realDonaldTrump Who has been keeping an eye on this.  Why did it happen Senator.  So much corru… https://t.co/mTzmgVbuFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m adopting an Asian kid one day, would it be weird to name him raul, askin for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff You’re wasting your time the Republicans are on his side not yours and your dumb little bill will fa… https://t.co/TzhfXm0HFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksmith4751 wouldn’t have missed it Kathy! I had a great time &amp; I can’t wait to do it again soon! hope you had a great birthday 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHANNELFORTRUTH That’s awesome. Always great to meet another author. If you want, check out my podcast “10-Minute… https://t.co/CIC8vYgxiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s what I’m screaming over here...got 2 more qb’s after 13 holla at AR apologize and get him back in the fold g… https://t.co/O6jfuwmIhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like just keeping my car and doing a build but then I get gapped by Focus STs and STIs and I’m like nah ima get a 435i lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silkride @TheValuesVoter So is this... "Love thy neighbor as thyself."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/WkoCpk9t9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting: “Whitmer's proposal is "big, bold and it solves the problem," said former Senate Majority Leader Ken S… https://t.co/XnCvSxQT8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[You just said Nazis deserve to spread what they believe then went to say that you don’t want this country to be lik… https://t.co/iSzzt8ow3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[im a @BlackYellow fan who are rivals with @s04_us so it would be great if @ManCity beats them  #s04vcity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistressmatisse @WhoresofYore @literaturepeep I saw a dick lamp this weekend and it was as though it could have be… https://t.co/PPPSWyJjxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gov Inslee speaks out more than double all other presidential hopefuls on @climatechange we need a POTUS focused on… https://t.co/B6DG7sSW8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man man man☝🏿 Good run 💯💯 #winningteam #lifestyle #imbornandraised03 #dontbegoodbemajor #needtoloseweight @ Lindblo… https://t.co/SIUYO9PklH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImSteveNicholas @jaysonst @JClarkNBCS True, however revenue is going up at a higher rate than the cost of doing bu… https://t.co/IRoztIz5s7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet cousin made me dinner but her roommate just said that she is not “attracted to guys with certain attribute… https://t.co/nSUqjpAQAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the awesome @MacGyverCBS star, @lucastill. A great actor and an even better human being. So fun to wat… https://t.co/fd90R96TL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS A TWO PART NOT A THREE PART REUNION KEEP IT BRIEF AND DONT BORE US TRYING TO GET EXTRA AD BREAK TIME ITS FU… https://t.co/MAxGKGM1jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricospur @DailyCannon You're correct.  "Often" should have been substituted for "recently."  But hey. laugh-emoji… https://t.co/ih7GfTKWzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine if people talked things out wow we would be in a better situation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me imagino diciendo eso de un Audi. Calidad europea implicaría que rodara en Europa jajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[My aim is on point today !  Dub + kill leader. Woo https://t.co/3jFHaHtdhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webster I still use a fisheye/DSLR for my still 360 client work. I rented a GoPro Fusion for my first 360 video pr… https://t.co/AoPhhafF0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington State County Declines Becoming Sanctuary https://t.co/1UI908cDyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__FJM__ Too long to type lol but if you were to keep up with city politics you would know]]></document></documents></author>