<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@trumptrain1111 Wonder that myself! Group think! They all follow the exact same “script” Listen closely, it’s so obvious!😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my girl for 10 wonderful years. I remember when I got her in 2008 The year my mom died. She had every puppy d… https://t.co/3vSDHc99nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4 Students need to know that potential employers now check their SM and good habits start early. #SatChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex is cool and all but have you ever laid down in a huge empty bed and snuggle the covers all for yourself? Shits amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[with THAT being said, look @ me being that bitch dam https://t.co/IsX8JQgAqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thats a brilliant plan Bill... especially those states in the blue with sanctuary cities. Unlock everything for 24… https://t.co/7vrVkHOVZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielGoddard @BrytonEjames @JoshuaMorrowYR @YRInsider @YandR_CBS @CBSDaytime @soapsindepthcbs @soapoperafan… https://t.co/BhW54lmXIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard she recused because she’s related to Smollett. Don’t know if that’s true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[what if im driving and a song hypes me up too much and i start crashing into everyone, omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[my patient said she saw me in Keeping up with the Kardashians, she thought i was Kourtney 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 27 down, one to go! I really didn’t think when we started we would stick with it but here we are one day out fr… https://t.co/1wdR3C9S3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥Ran into gotdamnlola @ Strokers Entertainment Club https://t.co/Cr2UG7VcgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarellaGayla @HistLit @AllanNotAllen Congrats! Still have a week to go for mine but so happy to see ppl already free !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m not given a chance when it comes to dating, it’s either I talk to you for a month or so and they de… https://t.co/aucI1iyBCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CletusAwreeetus @amour72mg You have to be Canadian to get into that club. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[ughhhh can somebody move out of san marcos/ san jac hall so me and my roomie can stay there 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate answering the phone at work "how big are your titties" " can you send me nudes" BITCH NOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@love_pink114 I ain’t got no job lol I saved a lot before I quit to focus on school 😅 plus that income tax😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_aBrighterDAE @DPMCanty @KCARMOUCHE What kind of issue? https://t.co/ndUYOCnNPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending Valentine's Day with my boss at a college part-time job fair because nothing says Valentine's Day like hor… https://t.co/uGpTKbpDaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Romi_Bean @oldballcoach13 @AndyKOASports Me, right now...okay,  maybe not. I did go snowshoeing and have drunk a b… https://t.co/hWu0LAfJZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who I would love to meet, an aspirational list for #SXSW: @AOC @BillNye @elonmusk @JordanPeele @AnneWheaton @wilw… https://t.co/07NKy040iC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍴 Window is up! We're at The Rail Yard until 2:00pm. Details on @MobileNom https://t.co/Z3TqsYG1NR]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta know when to step away from the game don’t over stay your welcome learn to fallback!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Should ‘In God We Trust’ be displayed in Kentucky schools? These lawmakers say yes. https://t.co/vkN6CJjOAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭  This one time, in like 6th Grade. A kid named Dustin made me mad, so I tried to hit him in the head with a dodge… https://t.co/5fnSHGTEaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You bet ya! The more rain the merrier. Reminds me of my youth in California. Maybe HARP will give us a break this y… https://t.co/n1XzKKKXzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinksMarley Me too before that album I never had a relationship, never had a breakup, never had a heartache... But… https://t.co/bA3tG8CSiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UlrichJvV @RealBlackCoffee We should all celebrate each other birthdays.  Just another reason to smile and be happy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraBareilles Will you ever include your cover of "Stoney End" on an album? That would make my year...my DECADE! #Stellar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Promoted His Scottish Golf Course In A Tweet About Foreign Policy, Prompting Ethics Concerns… https://t.co/omNxDATXvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headdock @zzcouch1gmailc3 @rlamartini @Iamchronicpain @fightpaindaily @DaveH_RPh @LelenaPeacock @stupor2016… https://t.co/qIssTI0j5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peggyssadler @SnarkyLorax @BLU3Collar @bennyjohnson Exactly. Even more secret is that you need them spinning to in… https://t.co/0TGSn9Iezr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieSunnyaz4me @HollieJoyJoy @TimelessSPTV @WhiskeyCav Totally understandable!! I'm relieved #WhiskeyCavalier is… https://t.co/Qd9uWyllyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen: “I never heard Mr. Trump say anything in private that led me to believe he loved our nation or wante… https://t.co/dOPaAloXcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[A need another night where me and nick spiral together ASAP https://t.co/QsvE1kFFIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TammyTomtam @keigankerby22 @EmmaSturdivant why you gotta call me out like that mom...]]></document><document><![CDATA[ECU PHYSICIANS EARN GOLD STATUS FROM AMERICAN HEART ASSOCIATION @American_Heart @AmericanHeartNC #ECUPhysicians]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Femme_Mal So 20 min run is 100 min bike? I don’t think I have 100 minutes but I’ll try for 60?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting emotional walking around my childhood neighborhood. https://t.co/CmdnOTZ8E8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clinicboss @AllisonRBond @malco_barrett Yes, it’s horrible in ANY context.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pip_says Absolutely! I love one that holds my camera lenses safely too. #EUROVENTURECHAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopKiryasJoel @gato_danger @RudyTakala @DailyCaller @VicToensing They planned to kill him &amp; or one of his grandchildren!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm seeing Panic in Oakland, CA 😲😲😲 #panicatthedisco #patd #PrayForTheWickedTour #crosscountry https://t.co/ciTvkP0rxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the right teams he’s a great weapon but right now I think he’s more underutilized if anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah it's important to remember that more malpractice has happened in the past history of our people in very old fi… https://t.co/Vj8jKKWJUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[mardi ft. a soon-to-be Villanova Law student 😍 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/qmt3MZ261k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAThompson16 @paperrocketman @pilliarscreatio @hellyelly @garyparker83 @mistereitch @apollo11movie You could alway… https://t.co/zVCNU7Z7fV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever need a permanent place to practice @KKelly72, mi casa es su casa @StBernadette5! https://t.co/VC4ET9mAq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn have really enjoyed @SPCEliteInvite on espn and @espnapp. Thank you for helping this come to fruition. AND -… https://t.co/dZdOnVrKOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. 100%. I encountered this too many times in my former role. “How are you old enough to be a Vice Provost?”… https://t.co/IP7SyygHWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando aún no sales de tu casa por la mañana y ya quieres que sea de noche para regresar a acostarte #godinezcansada]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feelin’ lucky the Upstate is my home! #hereingreer #feelinglucky ☘️ @ Robinson Lake https://t.co/Vve3LoLwUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my family everyday, but it’s on Sundays that I miss them the most.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad just called me back to tell me that he thinks about me and my mental health everyday and worries about me ev… https://t.co/6Sm9KyTK31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings All! Donna from snowy, rainy  NJ. Graded for about 7 hours today and still not caught up.  #aplitchat https://t.co/zYZEpuOBKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Mirror In The Bathroom by The Beat. https://t.co/GGqiS2hYDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know what time @crookedmedia will do a dissecting live stream on the #CohenTestimony? Because I’m not gonna… https://t.co/eXHvpQCdJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advocacy Day Bound with @MomsDemand  to ask our legislators to help end gun violence. #TNLeg #ExpectUs #KeepGoing… https://t.co/uWr3PW1RiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to stop worrying so much about what people think of me and start focusing on myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS going to BeBest and preach about gun violence to the @NRA now? Sounds like a good idea since her focus of c… https://t.co/GYzQMWdH0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each of us has a spark of life inside us, and our highest endeavor ought to be to set off that spark in one another… https://t.co/SSUZzIl2nW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#scarletthalo: #NYFW Day5 wearing my favorite color for @aveda backstage and @31philliplim runwayshow. So obsessed… https://t.co/IYXQ5GJFRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willispatreon When individuals donate a mask will appear on the screen thx will]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Oh please ladies.  Then Trump should resign for being a disgusting racist lying CROOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbyles_ Those are only my card transactions lol I go a lot more than that 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samrockweezy @RomeshRanga @petercrouch A solid case has been made. I'll second that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbouie when I'm eating dinner i often think about what I'll have for second dinner. i can relate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all let the eternal blue sky bless me and allow my knowledge from studying last Thursday in preparation for the e… https://t.co/TJGhEH3RnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise Tai Chi at the Desert Botanical Garden  https://t.co/AEX9jVuPmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wjpa Oops, that’s a radio station outside of Pittsburgh, Pa!! Thanks for getting back to us!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway the walkway from the local to express tracks on the 35th Street side of the A train is disgusting. It s… https://t.co/kph1OnxhCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @GVHSDramaClub for an incredible event yesterday that raised over $750 for Unite for HER!! Be sure to get… https://t.co/bY9WaekLIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My recliner is comfortable therefore my house is not getting cleaned. 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freedodi On me but I promise if we made it a big deal on face book twitter and all tha other shit we do they ain’t… https://t.co/iYUHsXwnTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Thas my fifth cousin! I can’t escape this dude! I see Lincoln’s everywhere! 👀 the high school, the s… https://t.co/pHPb3pSzoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Josh would wake up and love me cause I’ve barley had any love all freakin day 🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope I have a face cam by the time I play dream daddy on YouTube lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisLu44 @MollyJongFast @matthewjdowd Obama would not be so ignorant to sign a bible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our principal has skills! Kids Heart Challenge! @TurieT. #noexcuses #justdoit #ouradmincanjump https://t.co/wHS1vkJ6Si]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeeeessss! A sneak peek into what #FamilyHome is all about! It's time to consider what #intentionalliving might loo… https://t.co/Y6DgZlBJFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Tristan, #trex extraordinaire!  #christianvoigt #christianvoigtphotography #evolution @unixgallery @ UNIX Gall… https://t.co/55fe5ze2oH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I leanered today that I have to let students progress through Mathia at their pace. I have to allow students to hav… https://t.co/dvW1LcK4VX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious selfie. Still haven't posted one with my bangs, so it's about time. Loving this change, considering I haven… https://t.co/d6gNhVZEsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior year... tons of grit, practice and desire.  This accomplishment came due to the many coaches and teammates f… https://t.co/CRX37vMDqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyDaniela_ Once you get started, you're unstoppable. It's just starting that's the hard part.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was the kid that always fell asleep on the bed where all the coats are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidhogg111 At this juncture, if you are still a Republican supporting any current Republican leader, you are not… https://t.co/vrbtucSX2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[OLIVIA COLEMAN WINS BEST ACTRESS FOR THE FAVOURITE! A WIN FOR LESBIANS EVERYWHERE!!! #LetsGoLesbians]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so sick of the Donald Trump syndrome that is suffered by from Hollywood that's why people don't watch the sh… https://t.co/kZ9wSW4PzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamosumSihammm @PatGrant7777 @Romanof_Martins @CristinPereyra @zerok_z @TAASAA1756 @r95731 @lauragarciabou… https://t.co/stqDaz0NaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Losers on @netflix and the episode on @MichaelBentt “The Miscast Champion” is phenomenal. Just gave me cra… https://t.co/WEhGMlsDdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolmswain MSNBC still can’t figure out Aesop’s Fables.  Keep crying wolf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been the type that loves to bless people because of how much god has blessed me with 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blackout: A Romance Anthology GIVEAWAY! #giveaway #win https://t.co/XJicm2dtTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen 🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻 Stop Telling Me To Travel Like a Local, Okay? https://t.co/VnUubZNqo6 #TravelTuesday #Travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; @MamaPelks at a Jonas Brothers concert !!!!!!!!! https://t.co/OuvL1RxtfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redfoxes_ Né? Hahaha na vdd eh fiz a foto pq ele num ar de independência foi pra minha cama e tomou meu lado na ca… https://t.co/5KQMZhAwIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#done #foodcoma #petcomfortusa #highfeedingsystem #gingerlicious petcomfortusa @ Tyler, Texas https://t.co/L7qrX35AY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. It's almost 2:00 am Tuesday morning, but I haven't been to bed yet so...for me, it's #MultipleManCrushMonday, a… https://t.co/K35CoopmTY]]></document></documents></author>