<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@According2Luke @downtownrob88 It surely helps if you are in the closet, and have little contact with women other than mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willieashman1 @abbyhaggstrom @luke_bartell Who are you though? Like seriously??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomMorrisJr1 @OfficialLivePD Tom seems like many of the officers are not wearing seatbelts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[On top of the world!!!  #hellocanada #eh @ Mt. Baker https://t.co/64ybZwPjfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back by Popular Demand  Sunday’s I’ll be selling my delicious tortillas at the heirloomfm at the @rillitopark. Come… https://t.co/tOZxqIlQgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmlc48 @LadyThriller69 @realDonaldTrump Obama and Clinton avoided Military Service and not a word has been spoken about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dearleader @AndyDererShow How did I miss that? I’m sure there are more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the funniest humbled tweets ever. Ever! Nice work @NUMensBball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro @J_Stephens315 get your man to start pulling up shots! This just down right disrespectful Defense. 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/7CGKKNlb0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out on-campus and working on the Sunday bulletin.  I’ll be here for a few hours.  I’m up near Pulley Diner… https://t.co/pU3xdH2uR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤮Cost to the American taxpayer: $392.66 per inch for 55 miles of political theatre, red meat tRump can toss to the… https://t.co/cwx6tAJEjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NavyFederal @NavyFederalHelp On the app, I saw my ach for my pay pending yesterday on app however today it does no… https://t.co/rf1IgNSYVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Startup Night at Maggie Mae’s just opened. Bit of a line but moving quickly. Open bar, you-call-it, with chicken sl… https://t.co/PhaicJVB9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSchulman Bringing business to America bad. Restrictions on companies with taxes and Epa good 95% bias MSM go… https://t.co/XJpP1YR9hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virtual BL #realtor #kellerwilliams #kwstudiocity #gooutside #forcryingoutloud @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/Rbm02RFrDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJWyndows98 @tedcruzcontrol Oh I thought you were sharing your personal opinion, yeah that’s ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaBD20 What is going to happen to her if by mistake in your organizations she receives classified material?  Whi… https://t.co/KdAOudyFX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get 5 people a month posting stories of them in the hospital, you guys don’t eat veggies or what? Milk helps too bro 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black x White x Grey Area @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/e0dnvXM2eM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLDragonSoccer  I didnt know Preston was the ball? https://t.co/MocQU8nkVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday rd. 2! #pssita #smokeitup #barrelburners https://t.co/XAPTfB030d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stewpotfan @TariBKfan @dinogcole Well he wants to sweep.  Go Kyle. 😎🌞🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Keep Saying That Bro Whatever Makes You Feel Better  https://t.co/ME49EjnKKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[douglas county nevada DBA clark county nevada @mayoroflasvegas        douglas lee thompson @ArcjojoDexterME… https://t.co/WiBrBicykI]]></document><document><![CDATA[...Although your bright star was taken from us to shine brightly in heaven, the legacy of your work will never be forgotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the best option for talking to a member of your support team when your account has apparently been hacked? I… https://t.co/soAePkz8ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt12r I mean it’s because of a 4 team tiebreaker they finished 3rd.  4 teams were 9-9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always there is a heavy price for peace I move my hat 🎩 and my respect to all peacekeepers how left there beloved b… https://t.co/ZEGajqbd9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unttalhanckoc @ElPincheJuan4 @pelon_73 @chuky_diablo @manuel70m @maskarita4 @SoloPHombres Ni aguantan nadaaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnganie1 @HouseGOP @GOPLeader @RepKevinBrady @ChuckGrassley Everybodys rates got cut moron. It just turns out when… https://t.co/tux1ZZYEgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Barton Health? We're hiring in South Lake Tahoe, CA! Click for details: https://t.co/GiCsvAWqPc #hospitaljobs #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @Snowden Cia/NSA BOTH very territorial...9/11 wasnt SUPPOSED to GIVE IT ALL to the NSA...According to the… https://t.co/KzbyjXELlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[518 native exchanging tweets with @Hasselbeck &gt; 518 native exchanging jerseys with Dwayne Wade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dragonstatic You know you'll break down and do it. You have too big of a heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialNBARefs I agree refs have a really hard job. But y'all really be the worst at it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever a great weather, "Chamber of Commerce" day is.......  Today is the exact opposite.   🏀 teams and fans in w… https://t.co/wwwh92tOAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DavidJollyFL @TheRickWilson - Every story overlaps and every story leads back to one person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bnoles6 They are young like us. They check their phones all the time so seeing plus hearing it from crowd to crowd… https://t.co/VurCxlrUKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great LIASCD Conference today! Well done team! @LIASCD @tguskey https://t.co/5BxRtrhDw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a slo mo video of @JordanBullard11 breaking the shaft of a driver that wasn’t his... 😂 https://t.co/FL8NzZyman]]></document><document><![CDATA[1986 Blues vs Flames "Monday Night Miracle" highlights https://t.co/f18FQUpYSO via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirlineFlyer Thinking ahead here, but for airlines/countries that have grounded, what will they need to see before… https://t.co/7IH9J0z904]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelEDyson So sorry to learn your sad news. There is too much unnecessary tragedy in our America, too many forc… https://t.co/407i15uawC]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO ARE TODAYS DEMOCRATS. 1. ENEMY'S OF THE PRESIDENT 2. ENEMY'S  OF ALL TRUE AMERICANS 3. ENEMY'S OF OUR CONSTITUT… https://t.co/xrRWBOqLW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prodnose I try to write plays. My funny plays are very very funny, but they don’t get done as often as my sad dram… https://t.co/hTsoVbdMJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrankyClair @Trobby11 @FootballCapital @ride80 @DefendTheR @lordele It is a real big gamble. A lot of risk. Could… https://t.co/Tz6I8px1Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicabyrne13 @StephenAtHome He's going to wear the ashes of Ted Neely?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paduda You should also come to healthcare city (the home of VUMC, and 500+ top healthcare companies in the country).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IowaHoops Great game guys, way to show fortitude, unlike the UI administration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s interesting how much weather affects #humanbehavior. One anecdotal note on this - I see roughly 40% fewer peop… https://t.co/GKv1YhcbJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cincicjustice @DrivelineBB Goal should be by the next day to influence developmental plans for the following week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @penguins @ShelbyCassesse https://t.co/ubCkIP6YCq @937theFan https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/POXzTDB3nM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tend to agree - most rubrics are designed primarily as scoring tools. This is meant to be a learning tool and hen… https://t.co/i2ldv0lLDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great way to start a Saturday = Listening to Renaissance Music  Radio on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/neFgy4SWfb… https://t.co/DLPduBDKTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#covercrop #knowyourfarmer #sungrown #cbd #cannabiscommunity #cannabismedicine #sungrowncannabis #thca #tincture… https://t.co/6tYsk5Y2U0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmiserpgh @JanePitt @DaveDiCello So many of his are ✨ https://t.co/rD1TQ4n6rT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a well needed weekend. Away from school and work just chilling with friends. I miss everyone from Angelo. If I… https://t.co/P32Ah58Kge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@painter_nancy @matthewaraven And to a certain extent, she does project that image. It's just that her policies fucking blow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wandzel_mark @TheSafestSpace @AnnCoulter Politics is all about money!  Politicians want to take your money and giv… https://t.co/XuM0njlACn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekingnathan @LJ_GhostLife_12 @FantasyFlurry @FlurrySports Well at least we can all agree Rodgers is worth that 5$ hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro when females shave their legs silky, shiny, smooth and soft 🤤🤤🤤🤤😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axelsolisrmz @PorraDeHerodes El poder te lo da la seriedad y sobriedad con que das el comentario este medio te da… https://t.co/fgxt1DLxHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s gonna be a great Championship when these two pair up! They don’t do it often.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Writesskrttt @PageKennedy If he's that injured then he shouldn't play. Instead of activating "Playoff Bron", maybe… https://t.co/7i076ZUOrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC Does anyone want to pay higher taxes? But everyone wants to reap the benefits of big government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday evening...looking toward Alcatraz in the distance. https://t.co/v2EPDiCWYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm @bracketdan @NotJackKemp @CincoDeMino @JulieAnnDobbs Hey now. This *is* fun Bob.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoje é o niver do meu filho caçula!!! Parabens Filhão!!! “I’m so proud of the man you became” https://t.co/Y5UzilfLTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nuggets_Nation Eastern Conference playoff wins should count for half of a Western Conference playoff win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDweck Why would you think your at if you were here? One word please. https://t.co/rNcGXmkRr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalicoAvenger @wvjoe911 Pulling the train ( repeating MAGAMadam has that rhythm) #WooWoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ian_Flaming @mariamtayob @methuengena @mitsusumashi @speedymc67 @fladjah @nangpa01 @LollllllaJR @LunaSonataL36… https://t.co/ldwqcYEbVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NepentheZ I threw in some cardiff undercuts for you Nep :) never finishing that SBC even if I wanted to...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indyman08 @HBRADIO_LV @DJHartbreaker I’ll put you on send me your mixes or do you just play other people’s music?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone luvd bottoms amirite?! Contribute to the project and get one for yourself!!! 🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[There may be The Shield. But the force behind them is The Sword @BaronCorbinWWE @fightbobby @DMcIntyreWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MaineDOE : "Because our schools must provide safe, inclusive, and respectful learning environments, DOE urges scho… https://t.co/3ZnOO9C2Lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voting Machines at Risk: Where We Stand Today @brennancenter https://t.co/dqg7cyXqNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomhoffarth And in elementary school in Atlanta I can remember our teachers bringing that big ass TV into the clas… https://t.co/tFAxf5Gr5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve explained to my wife the differences between bugs, feature requests, and poor UX. She’s very proficient at fin… https://t.co/ReabHGkqEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[With new mobility options, Detroit goes multimodal https://t.co/IUBRJZUBWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You know what’s funny? The absolute hypocrisy. It wasn’t so long ago, that the people who can’t get off of you… https://t.co/85KU6NOvbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BsLegion Please no..  btw Nyquist fetched a 2nd n conditional 3rd or 2nd... regular 50 pts guy, already at 50 now.… https://t.co/tpWvgfNHnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikePearso36 @Michael_Buffer @EddieHearn @TheGarden @anthonyfjoshua @BIGBABYMILLER @DAZN_USA @MatchroomBoxing… https://t.co/CE08Ie0369]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bnicholsonsmith Bahaha... now that’s funny. But seriously... Troy may want to call it a career and consider other options within baseball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea, just like his closet buddy Trump! With Trump and Roger one never knows who do who or who’s on top! Shitty pals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine I am here at the Texas roadhouse in El Paso, and I just had a delicious steak. I’m doing my bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Agghorn04 @JoeNBC @MarkMeadows That’s not true. Live within your means and put a little away every time. Most hard… https://t.co/ICNxQWcHfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rhumbix is hiring a Sales Account Executive! Learn more here: https://t.co/XdpKguWMJs   @Rhumbix modernizes constr… https://t.co/vtEK1HX0af]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Obfuscation by Between The Buried And Me https://t.co/ZXYHuwpniK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmileSimplify @SpaceXFleet @austinbarnard45 @ClementFavaron @CowboyDanPaasch @DOfaquarius @Hein_The_Sayer… https://t.co/sYez2YQtoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been cat fishing you the whole time. @tashaelisab has been my acc since 2016.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Damn you heard that thunder?...how you been tho” https://t.co/edJEHRNZr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a wrap! Great few days of networking with lots of agents who have buyers moving to Vegas. #Kwfr2019… https://t.co/U9AdecsqsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would Sessions betray Trump? He risked everything to back Trump when Trump was considered a million-to-one joke… https://t.co/O8ppcxEI39]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got back home about 1:30 AM from a super Carolina Hurricanes game in Raleigh. THREE goals in the first 90 seconds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sox were never serious.... I am pissed at this and this rebuild bullshit hann and Williams should be fired if this… https://t.co/0aPma6iXMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Coal fired trains be like "YAY!"  Wagon wheels be like "I hope we're next"]]></document></documents></author>