<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RScottWilson @mattyglesias Seriously we over corrected for tyrant of the majority and opened the door for tyranny of the minority]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫I Think We're Alone Now by Tiffany, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/0yXmLjzfjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pokemon Then we should be able to use Persian to sneak up on unaware pokemon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpsNotesToSelf To Kim Jong un.. Thanks for Everything! code name: Putin Newmar https://t.co/V1kpfpRJtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bitflight_ @ProudResister @Fawful81 @FoxNews I don't care about your sick socialist agenda and I could care less a… https://t.co/s6KjcMQyvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Around 50 new users have downloaded the app in the last two weeks alone, and call numbers are already up 50 presen… https://t.co/1bc10Kt51T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HipsterDeadpool @HamillHimself I grew up in modesto myself. And yes, I can attest to this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I got back to my apartment after the event one of the homies sent me a message on AIM (r.i.p. AIM!) that said… https://t.co/Xs05Znc8ZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Divine Reserve No. 19 by @saintarnold @ Stouthouse — https://t.co/GO2u3LogQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m looking at you @alysmurfey @tayzerlayzer @pezfish26 @kirstiemulligan @aardnasssac @squirrelsteph @mariannegkc… https://t.co/Rb7928n4gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMutterBilk @saint_gert If there was a subway on 6th street probably.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Lo?? D-LO!  No. 23 drills big time triple that gave the Braves a one-point lead but UNI answered back with a ju… https://t.co/olIUCpYIPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL they take credit cards for Girl Scout cookies.  RIP health and wallet. https://t.co/mg7gbdT2Ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Señora eso de progresistas paso de moda . ustedes le llaman facismo al progreso al capitalismo .los mal llamados pr… https://t.co/5Tcl74FWNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drummergirl29 @RealMuckmaker Sorry they are words Trump can't comprehend let alone pronounce.   He is not fit for… https://t.co/gFlMKsEKid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dave_sills 400 pileups are a fact of life at this point. Seems odd we've made it to 2019 without reliable means to… https://t.co/ARqP8IddEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only people from Atlanta know how to navigate thru the Atlanta airport. if you know, you know 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇮🇪🍀🍺🍀🥃🍀🍺🍀🥃🍀🇮🇪 - Drinking a Guinness Draught by @GuinnessIreland @ Las Vegas (City of Las Vegas)  — https://t.co/U1L6jEUSS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta say today was a good day at the @globies game after the game I took some of the kids to meet the team and e… https://t.co/r6BQmVwAm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RPGTony same i've had to leave class for a few minutes bc of how loud people were typing lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[The proposed FY20 budget for the VA is bigger than any state, and is larger than every other federal bureaucracy ot… https://t.co/xV1NuzvOA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro buenos días señor narcodictador.  Ahí te envía @realDonaldTrump  una foto de tu futuro inmediato si… https://t.co/lUbFpEOpVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Godsgirl158 @hoppinmama5 @thursmat @RedLeg_MAGA @arkiegal411 @Badeye69 @rchlrql @Roger96203916 @OldVinegar… https://t.co/48Qo1AZY50]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hickory Ridge High School - @hickoryridgehs in Harrisburg, NC https://t.co/bRCwyj6Wfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesrucker247 @cwells52 Frank Martin is as old school as it gets in today’s day &amp; age of coaching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Samantha's Homestyle Cookin' in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/m2gc8FIV9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malakabdo96 You saying $4 made me think of this 😂 https://t.co/dco6pes3Nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #flexfriday  #scottishterrier @ Life Transformations Personal Training https://t.co/279wyOPZbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamfromSpain @Debra_McGill @PenPure1 @nycSassenach @newenglandgrl @SaraMD15 @KarramKaren @CharliesWhiskey… https://t.co/0ImOvtU7Yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on out and check out a great show, especially after I'm done with my solo acoustic set. 😂  3/4 @ 8pm in the Pl… https://t.co/lsbMxKLZJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJurss Half my first block is absent. We're going outside for a snowball fight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este morro es mejor DJ que alguno por ahí en Okc..... y no voy a decir nombres 🙊😅😅😅😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently listening to my daughter laugh out loud at literally everything...so funny! #LoveThisKid @skilarnmaddox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinsheehanDC No one will ever get close to this. His coolness and smoothness makes it great.... P.S. Whitney was… https://t.co/5G30gcxj3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure that hiding tweets is the full answer, but it's a start - Twitter confirms it's working on a 'Hide Twe… https://t.co/ec6cQb5BGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why don’t you call Russia? You praised their hackers during your campaign. https://t.co/pBYBJP3TlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are not in the process of becoming the person you want to be, you are automatically engaged in becoming the… https://t.co/pFlM7uUD4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @Stpolishook Why dont yall just get off Twitter.  If we wanted Twitter and Instagram stars to represent us, we'd get Kylie Jenner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Space show about how humans are awful and they try hard not to be but seems they can't help it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport He's on Strike Two. His ego wont let him stay quiet. He's going to really melt down when he can't shi… https://t.co/vHAf0yZafT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Heller for February 27, 2019 | https://t.co/eSMqRsQRgf https://t.co/FTo56QXvnE via @GoComics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Action shot of E1 headed to a fire on Monday. #lnk @LincFireRescue #smeal https://t.co/Ynre4zeoir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misspunk63 @MG62967 @LacySheila @Antoinotabot @SealeyGerald @Patti_Sc60 @Serremmy @jonz970 @MariMandy2… https://t.co/QAAzZauzsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Wow, bittersweet...Like my f*cking career.”  David Lee Roth on Joe Rogan’s podcast.  #DavidLeeRoth #JoeRogan… https://t.co/oxvTbUH7eR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridgetbhc @ktullymcmanus I know there are a lot of people out there that don’t understand how sensitive u are and… https://t.co/OiEPhKhVXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Major props to @FairmontHotels @FairmontDC for having a clean, comfortable, and private mother’s lounge, complete w… https://t.co/L52xIqsKUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColiseumNassau @Harry4naris @MNorman87 @CoachJMike How is that twisting words? It’s literally what he said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runningwolf1978 @Randy82257977 Yea same here I'm 1/4 from the lake and I can hear it roaring.  I've been listening… https://t.co/FHAevyUOJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/s0A3vBnaLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @gregrikaart Your Gonna Do #Excellent In @ModernFam On @ABCNetwork #ModernFamily #Sitcom 📱🙏😎🆒📺🏆🎬🎥⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️👍👍👍🕺 https://t.co/g8ww0gWtgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evulm0nkey @HeyScoops @thefamouspaul @SweetMattyD @SteamieWeenie The Peppermill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday Hockey Night at #GilaRiverArena in Phoenix, AZ. Phoenix Coyotes vs Toronto Maple Leafs. #NHL https://t.co/F3BmS5ASoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yanjizee @sawgee @tomidipo @lampidicsparrow @somadina_arthur Not absolute, but a good start IMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer God help us if a Democrat wins the White House. We may become Venezuela.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicashortall I’m VERY glad to see them going away. I’m still scarred from when I was a kid— we didn’t have a lo… https://t.co/eO7BjxNavn]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 16th 2019 at 12:46 PM – postmeridian @ Rockefeller Center https://t.co/HKZjNpjZCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMAGASteve The great social experiment of assimilating refugees into American society is a major failure, soone… https://t.co/Tdw7bc0cbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most people can't identify their top strengths, which ultimately means they can't share with others how they can co… https://t.co/ZbviPfapl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is posting pictures of their “Valentine” and I’m over here like...”Hey bartender I’ll take another Red Bull Vodka”.....🤘🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tebow gets it!! “Succeeding or failing is not making it to the bigs, or it’s not necessarily fulfilling that,” Tebo… https://t.co/gP8d5sulBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's your inflection point? A moment to which you can point, where if you'd made a different choice, everything w… https://t.co/6zGJc7ueht]]></document><document><![CDATA[They just made this classic original Xbox game backwards compatible for Xbox1. Star Wars Jedi Academy! This is me p… https://t.co/g7hG58NLoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mryclept Interested in learning the criteria used to rank top prospects. The #1 rated prospect in the Yankees syst… https://t.co/lNwsKQlWe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCarringtonUT You better put that Kings’ syrup on there! It’s golden! Keep it up, @BCarringtonUT. #KingSyrup… https://t.co/uW55sAmsSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newwarden @RotoCurve @APfeifer24 That's on me as well, thought it was a troll job. My apologies, definitely apprec… https://t.co/f2GMtTP1Ig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib Great job on CNN, you made correct call.. Stand your ground!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Razzbecca by Cage Brewing @ Cage Brewing — https://t.co/C76b5b0mih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardTBurnett Around 80 union leaders, local officials and business owners ask Amazon to reconsider New York for… https://t.co/XQED6QHrgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excelente triunfo fundidoreslfa #lfa #football #win #victory #nfl #cfl #sports #fundidores #gameday🏈 #sportsvibes… https://t.co/Z2Zl56D6Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is more of an impressive feat?  a. Women wrestlers NEVER exposing ANY nipple in the ring  b. Braun Stroman ALW… https://t.co/gHQKeGTNgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnorEdwards10 @JonRothstein Still. Having 2 top 50 wins shouldn’t be enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I was Capable of taking my lacrosse scholar so I could’ve kept playing:(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to two of the best that have played for @BHS220Football WE ARE PROUD OF YOU - BFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the chick fil a drive thru. It’s always busy but they get you the hell out of there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xio090876 Buenos días Xioma, que tengas un excelente martes 😀🌷🌹. Abrazos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apple dropped a -No Homo- emoji?????????  Say no more https://t.co/mZxP2THasr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmayfield1911 @joryoncew @riah_guerrero @kelsey_grider Leaving out lots of important details to this story. 1. Som… https://t.co/edDAKx4jHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[backstreetboys #karaoke #iwantitthatway @brian_littrell aj_mclean @nickcarter @kevinrichardson @howied #ktbspa… https://t.co/HJpEKoGEMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadian #familyday dim sum brunch with 3 generations. So happy to have my amazing #daughter in town for her… https://t.co/OLJKnCmr5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got recognized from my Steinhafels commercials by Linda at the gym. @ Preferred Fitness https://t.co/E54sgMMgAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway's husband blasts Trump in rare public appearance  https://t.co/UwLK71m5cS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth4158 My terrible arrest!! says Stone. A tweet to the threatened witness, contains, "Prepare to die." Mr Stone;… https://t.co/iAoEz5Ffti]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ARstories meet @anoizet if you’re free when you’re in Austin for #SXSW you should connect regarding a #health #innovation panel]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the Joes say what's up after Cher Tweets them  https://t.co/z4sdH5dEod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great game!  Go get the Minute Maid sweep tomorrow boys!  Gig 'em 👍⚾️🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s my College Lacrosse Power Rankings: 1. @Towson_MLAX  2. @NDlacrosse  3. @Kiywii  4. @HarfordCC_MLax  5. @BCwlax]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #Respect @kingjames &amp; @dwyanewade 💯! But #MJ Is All Of Our #GOAT ❤️! #SixRings 💍💍💍💍💍💍❤️!  #Winners ❤️! -… https://t.co/XYSbEJ8Rhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted the #BookCoverChallenge from @LauraKRoland  to post 7 covers of books I Love: no explanations, no rev… https://t.co/n4S6WMEGz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyBe13210748 The chances they do it to their standards are pretty good. The odds of you finishing it to your standards are better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s my DUDE! @lucasw2424 Great Story; it was fun watch you grow into a wonderful Young man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left-Wing Jewish Group Pickets University of #Texas #Chabad During Shabbat Services, Citing IDF Event https://t.co/pKNH4j2yiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost @UnforgetableImg Last night chillin after shooting. Rocking my @lazellc316 #ClassicMan skully. Make sure yo… https://t.co/9pN4yfMlS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiDadePD I want to thank all the female police officers who risk their lives on a daily basis to protect our co… https://t.co/nOSsUUxtQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m in the woods, I likely have my 270 with me.....sooooooooooo........yeah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Union Is Dropping Vans to Celebrate Black History Month https://t.co/I3L8VaNXjc via @solecollector]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nashville has just 22 games remaining in the regular season and are only two points back of Winnipeg for first in the Central division.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if this is how college students feel these days.. 🤷🏾‍♂️🤔 https://t.co/IJs7xqHEM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynwoods probably got some A1 pussy while ya shit trash @khloekardashian 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello from @TulsiGabbard's campaign event in Des Moines, Iowa where there is a band playing an electric ukulele (?)… https://t.co/hSkF1oASyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule “Area woman who voted for the ‘Leopards who eat faces party’ is stunned to find a leopard is in fact eating her face.”]]></document></documents></author>