<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Tomas_Verde I believe both of my cats are of drinking age. But I’m sure they prefer wine. They seem like they woul… https://t.co/CoY8ErxYzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so many feelings about this movie but here are two: 1. We need to see more Black joy. Pain and trauma should… https://t.co/o9uHOOnKpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheridigi @paulgreenemedia @hallmarkchannel @WCTH_TV @LoriLoughlin @erinkrakow @ChrisMcNally_ @HuttonPascale… https://t.co/xKmJXrOefh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday someone in Louisville was shot inside Olive Garden and today someone was shot outside of the meijer I shop at 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever have one of those weeks where everything puts a smile on your face? I have had so many incredible moments… https://t.co/VnNtwFuUTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypbenson @PolitiBunny Watch with the sound off. This is what the msm would have happily broadcast all day, every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkline56 Re elect President Trump #MAGA  RT/FB https://t.co/OAqBsvrQtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin really really assaulted that guy over a parking spot!!!! Slapping him on the wrist, that’s what they d… https://t.co/5zjSeYcZ0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapitaoArcoIris Well because I don’t drive I have limited options, I go to work, I get home and I can’t leave the… https://t.co/JReyvvcAXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FibromyalgiaWa3 @1120Eclipse @AmyCurt52463119 @Waybeyondempty2 @Hawkins65S @MartinG8177 @debsteele75 @PajamaDaze… https://t.co/NRWZlSIzQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOTS FIRED 💥💥 #BANG #BANG #EPIC   @jaketapper 🙌🏾 This is Why I Love You!!!! @TheLeadCNN @TheDailyShow @CNN and to… https://t.co/K0FWODB30o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long life is in her right hand; in her left hand are riches and honor. https://t.co/51uWUIMJsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big weekend for NWHL hockey 2 last games of the regular season ..2 games today 2 sunday..playoff spots will be dete… https://t.co/Wm5xYUJeN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking through MK and i already started crying. Today’s going to be rough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good mirror pic never hurt nobodyyyy @ Downtown Miami https://t.co/XC1GSs89Cz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious #bloodymarys #seafood #shrimp🍤 #mussels #clams #freshbread at @rusty_bellies and the absolute best… https://t.co/QvoTRVEs62]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more games. Buy me a 2019 Panamera Turbo @porsche so I know it’s really]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying, Blessed are they whose iniquities are forgiven, and whose sins are covered. https://t.co/EUxXHPbexN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurynsosimple well girl just hit me if you ever need someone to study or eat or watch a movie w! im down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laughinginside @darkestsatan @whatalieIlse I think we are in our own exclusive club of people who aren’t big ragin… https://t.co/6Vz8C08EKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We traveled 1.5 hours to get fresh local farm-raised meat and it was worth it! We plan to continue doing this as le… https://t.co/myGQAYQ9Fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  Anybody: Ruby you’re always drinking   Me: https://t.co/1kXYIZ4vp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LettersK Nice! 🙌 I’m trying to get all my chores done so I can watch Victoria later with no anxiety of not getting stuff done today. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women’s Day March 2019! #wearred #equalrightsforall #protecttheenvironment #resist @ Omaha City Hall https://t.co/aM13Qc5WGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how stupid these are. Did the Saudis ride their camels, jump the wall and head to NY to take down the towers?!! 🤔🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[So uh, apparently I’m over halfway there for the amount of promotion points usually needed to promote to Sergeant i… https://t.co/2PTORj5JPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a hope and a prayer that moms have that when their kids are grown they appreciate, love, and respect all you’v… https://t.co/Oh4YpbfTeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The insane are now truly running the asylum! That this person holds a Congressional seat is truly frightening!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why are you such an ass?  Why don’t you do something good rather than tear other people down?  You… https://t.co/MKEZsTOkXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheTruthTV I’m loving the one on one interviews! The Truth Team is on it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ETD51 When we lose on Saturday I am absolutely blaming you. It will have nothing to do with the plays of the game. Just you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewJeffCT @smoking_reedus @collette04 @reni_89 @kevkye @sachi_j @TinaBeaver7 @TinaTWD @leedusme1227 @OeverDaphne… https://t.co/LHP2vIJ9I3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResendizRamosA @OscarVega_MX Pobre !!! Que decepción se van a llevar! Siguen haciendo como que no entienden, están… https://t.co/WcIUREz6tl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend is seriously the best &amp; idk what I did to deserve him😩💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace Nicolle I continue to plan my day around you.... I don’t go babysit my granddaughter until I’ve wa… https://t.co/FsUg6px1Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Care to comment? @BreitbartNews @DonaldJTrumpJr @GOP @OANN @foxnewspolitics #MAGA https://t.co/1qRIEbuLm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning MKE once again single digits in March upon waking up but it’s #sunny #toocold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLQoolJB @HilareeBanks In fact, they’re bad for babies developing feet.  When they can wear them, you’re gonna wan… https://t.co/SBn6OQlddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@factorybasketb1 Thanks coach ❤️❤️ my community has done nothing but support me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklaureano989 I am so sorry for you and your family. That’s heartbreaking but hopefully he is out pain now. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Point! I agree! I THINK IT SHOULD BE RETWEET! RETWEET! RETWEETED!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askjimmycarter VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥https://t.co/vaAT1XmggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day of shoveling snow... . . . . .  #snow #snowflakes #winter #snowing #snowfall #wintertime #snowday… https://t.co/SYEdpXt7vB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i’m glad i didn’t fall in love with you; you’re a little heartbreaker.” -something my friend said to me today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I feel like everyone needs a therapist at some point in their lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always find myself randomly missing Jrod... I hope he’s happy. I will always miss having him as a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first face to face at Aurora Animal Control.  I think she likes me ❤️ #pigwhisperer #potbellypig #penelope @ Ci… https://t.co/1xDEgzlBGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year black history month only lasted for 2 weeks....🤦🏽‍♀️ and that was the beginning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump @POTUS You and Giuliani are great examples of old men riding on Tru… https://t.co/NIZNlKeeuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand wanting to talk about it and collect data on it and do research on it and.. and... and...  However thi… https://t.co/dcl4lYkWbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[a Security Council session that US, French, British and Turkish forces must end their illegal presence in the Arab… https://t.co/7akoE0kErB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hedhouseman Lol no trouble, sweets! If it’s for the good of the lingerie collection, I’ll travel an amount of time on the subway. 😽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy women’s day to all the ladies out there! #bachelornation @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/gz4tfLVr24]]></document><document><![CDATA[One way to stay warm is to stay inside... there’s work to be done anyway! #RITSM #RIT #Work #CollegeLife #Furniture… https://t.co/3vwmikneuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm watching Mars on Netflix, and it's kind of quietly brilliant. They've mixed in the fictional story line along w… https://t.co/GwnVCMJDsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyValentinesDay2019 #ThursdayNight  #ThursdayNightMood #ThursdayNightPartyMix #thursdaynightlivewithdrofweneke… https://t.co/Jx67Xdu4XW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still feel some type of way bc honestlyyyy the term thotiana has been used by me many years ago lol smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gl81274 @CBCMurdoch @JollyHarris Pepper jack and SNL skits on YouTube, who knew? Maybe it's our payback for the CB… https://t.co/IWOS7SUg40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my girl @danielle_p9 sooooo excited we get to ball together again next season 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGillycuddy @notelewd It has about as much to do with communism as Garfield Minus Garfield has to do with capitalism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0x2be3 dracanea marginata. I've had it for several years, but it got root rot last summer, and it's been declining… https://t.co/qOUDQBGKJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those goals match the personal goals of @MikeBloomberg. Changing the national paradigm from #fossilfuels to… https://t.co/qusnhOO1kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennzzzzdall Doesn’t make up for the fact that Viggo used the n word in an interview and the director is a terrible person]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the football crazed world should be entirely upset Pyongyang outdid y’all with stadium sizes. I’m not offen… https://t.co/eEi5M1kjdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a sudden impulse to dye my hair so guess what I’m doing... dying my hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RRidley11 It's politically advantageous, yes, but this kind of behaviour is also very harmful to our system of gov… https://t.co/LddbTRmF1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever is in charge of UX at M$ Skype team - you owe me a month of my life that I wasted figuring out how use simp… https://t.co/RZE0gww8tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Academy reverses plans, will air ALL awards live at #TheOscars - https://t.co/ys93Eh1zpF #OscarsOn2 #AcademyAwards⁠… https://t.co/Qofp2p7aPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinnaisua Yessssss soo good meeting you 😂. Sorry it was quick! I was on a mission to get food 😩😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream that I was an international dog walker in #Paris and #NancyPelosi was one of my dogs I had to walk an… https://t.co/P4cOLapDUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeymcintyre Words to live by #dontcompete #dontcompare. ❤️ So excited to see you Sunday with @88lester in… https://t.co/kxfAmSDCTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 años más ,que Wanda tiene.(su novia) - By Andrés Nara.  🤦🏼‍♀️ #LAM https://t.co/TxUCBLgq6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just tryna get/save money, enjoy good music , travel, and have as much fun as I can before I start having kids.… https://t.co/ZqxK585yza]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve gotten to the point where I’m too tired to even bullshit my homework]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustriaJ_ sooo you think the 14 year old girls who lied about they age, went with a man who already had this rept.… https://t.co/rhZPUKxnUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone taller than you is standing/sitting in front of you in general admission, MOVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[These days I feel like I do nothing right so come with me and we’ll go down the line]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost 281,000 people in Dallas live in poverty. About 83 percent are black or Hispanic https://t.co/Z8PVASHiRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having your stomach rumble during class is embarrassing but having your stomach GRRRRR through a class where everyo… https://t.co/xXmBgokAux]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big THANKS to everyone that attended by 1st SWIG + NOSH event in Dallas! I am overwhelmed with joy to have my first… https://t.co/gqA41caInW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all actually care about Valentine’s Day? .. tell me u love me everyday bitch fuck Valentine’s Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Replying to @ROSE IF you need somll Good Marijuana now?? https://t.co/uaiUBTPuWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought the drive to my bf’s was long, he moves even farther away from me 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many good shows in April, I guess I’m celebrating my birthday all month long 🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please stop lying to us, Mr. Trump.  Only 20k jobs last month, the lowest in a year.  If you’re honest, you would a… https://t.co/qfTHBzowmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los memes de los factoriales nunca pasaran de moda https://t.co/eWUDQNCHd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman His deposition will be in front of trained corporate lawyers not Kentucky priests. Game On.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please cold go away so I can have beer this weekend 🍻 https://t.co/m8IDnjZmFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love the special treatment my friends are giving me, although it’s only temporary lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right now my iPhone is attached to a 10ft cord charging, this is a luxury I had no idea I would experience in my lifetime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Severe Thunderstorm Warning for Coffee County until 7 p.m. @WFXL #gawx https://t.co/QiV6Gbk12U]]></document><document><![CDATA[McConnell, why aren’t you like Pelosi when it comes to reining in the Republicans to supporting our POTUS?  You are… https://t.co/7cjOxA7s6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatRU4USA @Hightailbfmc @HouseGOP Yeah,  I don't think he would be allowed to pull the idk card or i dont recall,… https://t.co/tbIExhCxQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ETSshow @brianchiong @aoglasser @tony_breu @liebschutz @gracefarris @cjchiu @thecurbsiders @FutureDocs @sargsyanz… https://t.co/DGh7iVEpiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's make hockey even colder @ Stadium Series Flyers Vs Pens Philadelphia https://t.co/Ufyv0riIIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @Morning_Joe Give me a break! I need to be on an antidepressant]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never get tired of saying/posting  I love Carlo so much, I am truly lucky to have him as my friend/boyfriend/father of my baby/‘s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen Batman and me in the same room at the same time? Just sayin. 🤔 #alwayswatching #promoshoots… https://t.co/kN7FyqXKtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[First STORM WARNING of year for @lakeeriebase - bringing the 🌪💪🏼 to Missouri for season &amp; @Coach_Skold debut!… https://t.co/3pCgUWiHbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPostCanada She deserves our respect and admiration for doing what was right]]></document></documents></author>