<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@T_raw947 @PitchingNinja @PitchingNinja my guy is leading the PBC in Era... I think his splitter might have something to do with it 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/zhGl5xFiWP 🌎https://t.co/nybi2t7T7g 🌎https://t.co/yeJ5Ge1ocE  99c 🌎… https://t.co/0LBkDkLdWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you have a great week....   Be a🦈   Just keep moving and attacking   #1Pursuit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHeatherEm Oh no! I’m so sorry Heather. Hope you’re on the mend soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting Physicians Association is hiring in AL! Read about our latest #Physician job opening via the link in our b… https://t.co/rPI7WEkozY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nahhh man @keliannestankus is so beautiful 🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹🌹 https://t.co/8F310uu7GX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are on break and I’m sitting with 7 big blinds. I’ve drug one pot and that was an all in for the blinds. Card de… https://t.co/xga4qg9I7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarsDorian @ImageComics @DarkHorseComics @thevaultcomics Look interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still on tv. Seriously no big deal. #humblebrag2 #guysgrocerygames https://t.co/7J9SEi573g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAOHARRY I hear @AAOHARRY’s voice in my head now whenever I read his tweets. I know exactly how this would sound i… https://t.co/NvpjdKSU1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithcrc All this talk about “green” this and that in reference to the environment but she’s just GREEN in the old… https://t.co/KKyeAIzxXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said this once and I’ll say it again this poll is stupid because it has preordering environment and climate ch… https://t.co/qnhORuOFmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I am.  Lots of 40 and 50 somethings here so I’m right at home.  Had the WWE live in Jboro last night and now th… https://t.co/pGYNiS5vmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. Those #WackoForFlacco shirts are even more wack than the first logo posted online. I'll make my own. Maybe chan… https://t.co/59GkdG3RJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you wont believe you wont make it then you wont. Its all in the mindset you cant go in to something with predete… https://t.co/TZHbteOMvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a Mistrail in the restaurant owner Sex Assault Case. What means--coming right up on Ch11 News at 5. https://t.co/B0rOYjWZ0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeronimobrat Daredevil and punisher were my favorites of them but Jessica Jones season 1 is very good. Season 2 isn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venus is a literal Banger, your guys’s sound is years ahead of 90% of the people on the platform]]></document><document><![CDATA[בהנחה שיוגש כתב אישום נגד ביבי, אני לא רואה מצב שביבי מחזיר אפילו קול אחד שעבר לגנץ לפיד ואז הוא יכול להביא את הקול… https://t.co/aGY4Yo7pZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished Dead Moon by @PeterClines today.  Wow. I went into it thinking it might be one thing, ended up being a who… https://t.co/tFNkdanM3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahahaha @BernieSanders #FeelTheBern2020? Yea how about #shallnotbeinfringed and how about citizens earn what they h… https://t.co/MT8TEWxd13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successfully completed a TriDot training session for running! Yay me! #tridot #sprinttriathlontraining… https://t.co/lJ84QfLBU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryansatin best part was you could hear someone telling her to hold the title up]]></document><document><![CDATA[They had individual mouthpieces to hit this with right next to it you don’t make contact w the same surfaces 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big @Region2Menbball win for the @redlandscougars at home 76-73 vs NOC Tonkawa... @ajmcneil3 with 33 PTS... Next ga… https://t.co/ps1tkWh02c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its something about a gorgeous red bone  woman in uniform that gets my attention .#winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcherTyrell @Szladesyn @LeoGarcia_1990 @PhilSzostak George Lucas  was at his best when he stepped back. Empire St… https://t.co/gm4AWksBw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxxTor3 @SnellW @AtheistVeteran I will be doing a Signature class which is an advanced class in Kansas City     April 15-17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealAssPodcast @luisjgomez Bill Murray!  Just for @bertkreischer 's sake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TelevisionApp Deleting a show on one device does not delete it on the other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaireBLang @bobpockrass Well, how do you like that?! I share a birthday with the incomparable and iconic Bob Pockrass. Made my day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBHSFalconFB @caffeyjbhs @RealCoachK @DucheneJerry Next weekend is st pats day 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look if it was an American who did this he would be considered a monster. The liberals have a double standard when… https://t.co/2ONJvH0t9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, now it’s done! Schnap! Forgot to roll it forward 🤦🏾‍♂️ oh well, gettin up early and going to sleep late while p… https://t.co/YDqS0Qcyxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffnbafan @Ben_Dowsett Are they trying to get in the lottery to include that pick for AD? However, we don’t want… https://t.co/HLzGZculbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethier_frank @mariannelaurens @PatrickDenis20 @coucou2225 @OBaillargeon https://t.co/e9hxaZYhgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the third and Serra is up 47-35 on Rocklin. Darrius Kendall’s turnaround shot that would have cut it to 10 again rattled out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShemekaMichelle I think his little friends just needed that rope and he was helping them out? Big hearted guy? 😆😂😉🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralsUpdates I didn't see that quote and if that is the case that's also a trash move. I saw the Hunter one and… https://t.co/EsaJB2oZyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like coffee so much I drink from the only container worthy of holding my coffee.  I am stealing this hashtag from… https://t.co/wPX9ucmfth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peak excitement levels. #rescuecat #catsofinstagram #catsofoakpark #oakpark #illinois @ Oak Park, Illinois https://t.co/kWb1pcVpcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonnell_8_ @showyourkitties No giving a fuck. That means no stress, no worries. Work out and eat fast food. Words to live by]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neontaster @WalshFreedom If chef boyardee is the best Italian food in your neighborhood, you need to move to another neighborhood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah and Vietnam just entered in an agreement to buy $millions wirth of GE engines thanks to President Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southwestern League QBs better hope their linemen been practicing! @MVNighthawkFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Listing coming soon !! #jamesmigues #listahouse #iconbay #miami #miamirealestate #forsaleinmiami #comingsoon @… https://t.co/5xboXcdh8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay out of Virginia politics.   @GOP should be more concered with the "Liar in Chief ".  The big question is wheth… https://t.co/BVUk7YRYjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrOfficial6627 @DonaldJTrumpJr Soooo... since we've already got common sense about collusion and knowing that's no… https://t.co/VrHXDdKLvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 Not on this fantasy wagon but Santa Claus wouldn't open guns or be a republican either]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate to do this again, but no choice,  Very big difference between RNC fake Majority and DNC actual Majority today:… https://t.co/tVPgxRtFKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angcould @we_r_Psymese Neither did mine until you commented. That is beautiful and I wish I could pull stuff out o… https://t.co/kcj4kvRwek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chattanoogarage @BSomers10 @BravesStats Which... sounds like a really good way to build a winner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming from architecture I hate to admit it, but not many architects are particularly concerned with exceptionally… https://t.co/2jbNqAReKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods She basks in reprehensible.  That’s all she has going for her. She won’t change now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorge_guajardo Preocupante…….en mi vuelo de ida y vuelta a CDMX ni un solo pasajero con un libro (sólo yo).  Dudo… https://t.co/veT1kDIqsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtenlow Presumably you've seen the weirder catalog stuff as well?  Two words: BRICK PANTS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMomNoms @phillee_58 Thank you so much! I think we will figure it out... I’ve been working like crazy at figurin… https://t.co/W15k3PyYea]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a video tour of my #listing 7473 PR 1465 #Centerville #TX  #realestate https://t.co/77F6aTffrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flint, Spark and Python base time series library open-sourced by 2Sigma optimized for panel and high frequency data… https://t.co/ROI6kEisal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mixcom Well that’s probably good for @nyknicks fans because the team has not been very competitive under his ownership!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also hit my shin this morning too. So it just hurts to be alive right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @Todd_Gutner temp in Topsham is 18 calm winds and cloudy skies. Hope you have a great weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @HowardSchultz @smerconish @realDonaldTrump  is an Independent that hijacked the GOP to get in and Drain the s… https://t.co/JWoXK2ZNOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPGA @ingeechun_dumbo @georgiahall96 @ThePCreamer @hondalpgath Such fantastic smiles, I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJRPatsNYankees @Patriots ENOUGH SAID!!!! ****** https://t.co/ygujXRqSFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyle_lucas5 If trea young is as good as Nash (2 MVPs, first ballet HOFer, etc.) I’ll eat poop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzipdamonsta @AlexHonnold I just kept saying “oh my god” - mouth agape over and over again...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raisafuenmayor Buenos días Raisa y feliz jueves tengas tu también saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScarizardPlays @Chef_Lu_Bu Unfortunately for me, I probably won’t spend energy or wings on it in the near future.… https://t.co/WUwRcmIvJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I forget that the events of Star Wars occurred a LONG TIME AGO in a galaxy far far away and then I remember and I’m sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acuerda Gobernadora @ClaudiaPavlovic movilidad de talentos sonorenses a España. A través de Red Global Mx que desar… https://t.co/EOeZnCmbch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sensanders @berniesanders who are you to say what a fair share is?  You just keep using that statement to get vote… https://t.co/5x98z6yuIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgjordan48 When it warms up, I’ll place them on my south facing porch. Right now I have mine inside under two ful… https://t.co/XHNaUtqEv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cubalondra buenos días preocupado x lo q sucedió en mi Ecuador pero contento xq té luce mejor el amarillo q el azul]]></document><document><![CDATA[S Epatha Merkerson (walks out of her office): Hey guys, come see this  (intense music, news is on)  Reporter: Roger… https://t.co/QHhvXXyJsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really can’t wait until the day he drops her 😂 even if it’s not with Chris I can’t wait to see her fall apart lma… https://t.co/TClXHMGLCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@othermattwagner @realDonaldTrump What about getting prisoners in remains returned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeniVilcatoma2 Como No,es posible apoyar a la Sra. Yeni.pero si pierden el tiempo en leyes de bicicletas. Señores… https://t.co/AvHLaix5kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen idgaf if y’all friends,best friends,lowkey fucking I just need another collab can we make it happen babies?… https://t.co/R77La0R4le]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackKingston @realDonaldTrump When you have a crook@in the WH Hack you have to investigate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Sean Hannity is the Joseph Goebbels of the RepubliCon nazis. All fascist regimes need a propaganda minist… https://t.co/543zvuLlcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ Again, just another stupid Ass Clown from my state of Florida. I know we are a popular state, but pl… https://t.co/llk5YnvbBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charles_watts It's called pressure. But @Aubameyang7 may have heard @BillieJeanKing "Pressure is a privilege". So… https://t.co/pWKfjRDA5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don’t go. God made you just the way you are. Jesus loves you but doesn’t want to meet you right now. Please… https://t.co/QcYzWZFFFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauferlaw @TrumpFrederick @LouiseBagshawe @CIA @jaredkushner @nytimes While I agree with you that Impeachment need… https://t.co/hKflztRnjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTammyGillis @AirCanada Good Luck don't hold your breath .you were going to Palm Springs ,ended up in Ontario C… https://t.co/9U8PAAucpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe @secupp Once again Lisa you so right. I’m one of the deplorables with a business 3 kids and a YouT… https://t.co/fKZ0aGaOwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PixieInktvis I am a big fan, first battle royale game I genuinely like! Gun play is great and legends feel fun to use]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fattenap @vmbrasseur Again, what’s “unreasonable”? I’m still waiting for hard (or even soft) estimates or expectat… https://t.co/XoKhFQCUut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsKB_hoe @YANIgotAChoppa I ain’t never been but I do want some crab legs 😂. Crafty crabs suppose to be good 🧐.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dotty_of_oz you rock I love your profile pic beautiful have a wonderful blessed day from John in Manhattan ny 💓💓 💓💓 💓💓 💓💓 💓💓 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday night! My first headlining show! #mondaythoughts #ComingSoon #FridayThoughts #locallaughs #ComedyNights… https://t.co/jbRaQpmLQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[You hit it well. But I have to put Steven Miller on any of my scumbag lists]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right on cue at just before 6:00! The early morning routes are already fast, but the morning weekend routes are SUP… https://t.co/58MGSA9GH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchlafon Both I can’t pick one over the other https://t.co/x8nOPFiLtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techdudetx My boss says, you know someone everywhere you go. Me: Yep, boardgame Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacksonNichols1 @BernardPereda I actually disproved this theory today by chucking two pair off the roof of my home, only landed 2 for 4 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muna_hers, thank you for following me. I am looking forward to learning with you. #Synergy #PLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got home from a long day at work and thought it'd be nice to lay down on the couch and have a nap, but it's the o… https://t.co/mVTla0ZFFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masonjohnson99 Gimme 10. Ion feel like spending money so im finna make a sandwich]]></document></documents></author>