<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MageModuleLLC @maierb @sherrierohde @benmarks @magentogirl @ericvhileman @magemojo @meetmagentonyc What date did u pick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tato_NK @SergioPMariscal @eldaamolina @DrogasMx @zarasnapp @elmemonoriega @LillyTellez @JorgeTaddeiB… https://t.co/2U838yYOkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pradeepraturi1 @realDonaldTrump Was he off his meds?  Or on something else?  He has the look of a toddler who made boom boom in the potty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are without a doubt an absolute piece of shit AND a traitor, @realDonaldTrump Where are the missing children yo… https://t.co/oUHR385mY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s not my responsibility but I just want what’s best for them... does that make me a bad person?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HVazez @eldaamolina @Luzmariagc Es cierto, Enero pareció eterrnoo... 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  @SenateGOP  @HouseGOP  @LindseyGrahamSC @senatemajldr  @foxandfriends @FoxNews @IngrahamAngle… https://t.co/pNb8yhyHnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWErickson Didn’t we just spend 2 yrs and $30M on the Mueller investigation of this????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Enough with your silly slogan.  You’ve been president for two years.  Are you saying you haven’t y… https://t.co/JgeIPTm3NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aangggel_ well I couldn’t be here in time for a goodnight text SO good morning beautiful !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go asshat. Disrespecting Women on #InternationalWomensDay  Why does she stay with you? @FLOTUS dump him. It'… https://t.co/WlF6HVnVaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME STATS:  Central Rosario 6 pts Ward 15 pts  Putnam  Hytmiah 3 pts Harmon 3 pts Martin 9 pts DeJesus 12 pts]]></document><document><![CDATA[at #NYC🗽 during #NYFW 📷 taken by @8and2  #YuFujiwara —————————————————————————— #FashionWeek #documentary… https://t.co/QKzHkoxMtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to sleep....just dropping it to remind you all I love this precious man right here. https://t.co/EeBFLxLWQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cturnbull15 @BearTavernES I’ve done this with art - it is so much fun no matter what the battle is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is a piece of crap. He needs to be kicked off any committee he is on. He wasn’t testing... he was tamperin… https://t.co/PWXBQn2HiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAR.2,2019  Made this Tropical Herbal flower arrangement from my #herbgarden recipe: #tulsi #chia #bougainvillea… https://t.co/j17y13Rp6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[do NOT watch the vampire diaries unless you want to cry all the time 😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DwyaneWade @KingJames Super dope🔥  #Brotherhood #BiggerThanBasketball 🙏🏾💪🏾💪🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IzabellaJumper @kwbates2 I love you girl just like I do your momma!! Im so proud for you and your team!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Piscean69 @nattyover A conspiracy theory, that, if true, would prove that the 1%, and their minions, are absolutely Evil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boot camp at 5 am: TRX, Core and Plyometrics! #fitsciencellc #wnbf #wnbfpro #rgv #rgvcommunity #womenwholift… https://t.co/RAlC8atN7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arjayneyra -13 right now, which feels like summer lol! It was -30 for over a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #OklahomaCity, OK #FacilitiesMgmt job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Housekeepe… https://t.co/AtteXtxJMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #internationalwomensday I want to take it back 50+ years  and thank all the fabulous women who have contrib… https://t.co/UPAX0rUcJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a tough week for our school community. And yet, especially this week, we have witnessed many ways our sch… https://t.co/xykfqUgfW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn .@w_terrence - you will do ANYTHING to get a laugh!   I hope you have enough fried chicken. Maxine said she’d… https://t.co/c57wj3dfC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkPR85 @columbophile The earlier episodes aren’t as great as the later..but I still love them all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[according to official MHA data. The refugee crisis following Pakistan’s invasion, pillage and raping of East Bengal… https://t.co/Cxg7kwQVlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Body of Young Black Girl Found In Duffle Bag Near Hacienda Heights, Calif. Hiking Trail https://t.co/4i9NcDCkkA via @ESSENCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ameristine @Racheltheroyal 6 months ago, 1 month ago, 3 days ago  each of these pictures were taken at a time that… https://t.co/WOwmQ37zx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[How awesome would it be if #Adidas gave me a pair of #ULTRABOOST to try out &amp; test!!! 👟🙏🏼❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[a lot of people don’t like me atm, i get that. but bullying is never the answer to it. we’ve all seen what bullying… https://t.co/IRfquleRm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christian_LTW you’re kidding. that’s unreal, shoot me a pic if you have one. I need to see this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelicGamer19 This is beautiful, little brother. You are good to be so aware and generous to share your gratitude. 🔥🤟🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateHipHopHead Yeah of course I am. It could happen... I said I hoped..]]></document><document><![CDATA[古の擬人化ログ | いさき #pixiv https://t.co/3fcggXkwoR We need more Tom and Jerry gajinka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HigherEdPoints talking about her success as a @sheeo_world venture winner in 2018 making a difference to students… https://t.co/St6kXxGGEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrssMorningstar Seriously, #Netflix knows what its doing, it's going to be great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zach and I are about the watch How to Train Your Dragon 3. I am excite!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustxnRobinson Fr???? On my mama I’ve never even heard of a blueface lol and still the only song I can honestly ma… https://t.co/oNweTEvrcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped at a gas station  on out way back to SA and instead  of handing me the keys to there nasty ass restroom the… https://t.co/RnXYedvnLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @coton_luver Well, I was thinking we could take this a step further and have this 12 day long celebrat… https://t.co/9AssXDJJAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madrevo1 @madonnarandd @maxfalletta @m_scrapbook @MadonnaBible @HOLY_WATER_ @MEDUSAS_BROTHER @madonnas_fault @ChiaraLove39 Great candid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure where to begin with @GlobalGoalsUN in your classroom? Check out a ton of free online courses here to help… https://t.co/mDK4PjSlPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvnewinfo @SassySouthern10 @Georgiapinecone @pcal4HIM @TeddiZaps2 @AnnThacker2 @MegaTJP @swehttamnhoj @mainwashed… https://t.co/vBYB2pIKk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pet peeve: when girls talk to your boyfriend and pretend you don’t exist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gutless hacks do nothing about immigration. Nothing but obstruct Trump’s valiant efforts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, is there really a serial shitter hitting studios in NYC or am I sleepy and gullible? #PoopGate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Kong crossed 10K. Time 01:09:29, pace 11:27 min/mile, est. finish 8:10 am https://t.co/ukzH8jQiWd #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ed_0892 @GenPenaloza Malparido payaso, cara de rata muerto de hambre, cuánto te paga el Chavismo Madurismo, el que… https://t.co/30gt6IO7Le]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MgmHumane K9’s 1. Scar; 2. Yolanda; 3. Jessie; 4. CJ https://t.co/EIiTG5YhZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at brunch with my sister, Beyoncé, and TC and I feel like I’m talking to myself :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mauidiver1 @EinsteinMaga @DrDeplorable60 @donnie_maga @DilaraEsengil @pjbowles4 @garway95 @ImabitcSumtimes… https://t.co/isfPnCldOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Balenciaga Dress X-ray print by Nick Veasey.   #balenciaga #masterofcouture #mtl https://t.co/3OjIJTMSf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tie a red ribbon on it. ❤️🎀 I love these ribbon and bow scarf accessories that are coming back for spring. I have q… https://t.co/Wq3GKMr5Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, a lot of Black men don’t like very opinionated Black women in fact we make them irate. I do think though they… https://t.co/sbbt46zXHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vazquezvic95 @looking4alexa I literally just said it wasn’t. Heartless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Plainsight2011 @GeeDee215 @DialogueOnRace Gotta think a little deeper, read more closely, and not jump on bandwago… https://t.co/CDiAINyCiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wendigrier22 @TinaTWD @AntoniaSchmitt4 @kathy_drop69 @NewJeffCT @Stef_Helen @StephanieMatne1 @TinaBeaver7… https://t.co/aFiP3ITtDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pekingduck #valentinesdaydinner @ Hong Kong Cafe Dim Sum Florida https://t.co/vzVMhKGRyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bettorhalf @TheeBigBrain Is no news, good news? 😬😬😬  cc: @EKANardini @stoolpresidente]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I don’t have a new show to watch, I end up watching One Tree Hill and I feel like I cry at a different episode every time lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to wear a hat...  #izzy💃🏻🏊🏻‍♀️🚴🏻‍♀️🏃🏻‍♀️ #rodeohouston @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/KATVKCGeCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t even experienced healthcare here and all I’m getting from this class is that healthcare here is brutal🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoMoreWeek #ChangeStartsHere If it wasn’t for the therapy I’ve had Don’t think I would be able to leave the house for work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be presenting at the 2019 @Tache_ista conference. #FirstOfMany https://t.co/9EQ8GOvVjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food, water and shelter are basic human necessities too and those aren’t free. Buy your own damn tampons lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is only in our darkest hours that we discover the true strength of the brilliant light within ourselves that can… https://t.co/gxE6wGmIH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarthaStJean @TeachersCollege @chrisemdin @unboundedu @KateGerson I’m here too- best talk so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful night of worship! #connect (@ Lakeside Villiage in Rockwall, TX) https://t.co/bRUtQTGhfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quantoidasaurus @mclduk @NYCuratrix @Grammarly Well they sure missed this one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ordered a birthday cake for my dog’s birthday on Friday. I really am that white lady dog mom and I don’t care]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost paperandleafwa (get_repost) ・・・ GG #4 shining bright on this snowy Monday! Kai'Dro killed it with this one.… https://t.co/w0z9eTJFUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toobad I don’t fuck with social media tho🙃🙃 @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/KA657bzRaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found this DVA hoodie look forward to me wearing this in videos #2020 https://t.co/DMnynunRIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Simple Ingredients for Nixing Dental Cavities  https://t.co/Lb9wqDXHHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrienneWrites That’s foul! He’s out. Knew there was something off about him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m available to go on the podcast next week to discuss this in more depth @BarstoolFran]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KIMBERL10021594 I used to be afraid spiders till I had to deal with Vegas roaches and these dudes!! This was about… https://t.co/NDBskJLCGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCanGo @TraficoenMty Así es Dan que tengas excelente día y que pronto se tomen medidas pertinentes antes de que sea demasiado tarde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come time for st. patty’s day weekend im going to most certainly need a designated driver.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidwesternMarc I mean, how did the Hawks not win. The Bulls were terrible toward the end. I hope the Bulls whip their asses in OT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockin' The Suburbs- Ben Folds https://t.co/fLv1VLLYO7 via @YouTube @RealCandaceO @benshapiro #HateCrime #JussieSmolletHoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monthly #chamberofcommerce #ambassador #meeting #sleepyguy #whereismycoffee #coffee @ Plymouth Chamber of Commerce https://t.co/LHMMos6rXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest @KevinMKruse I first read this as "babies." That might even be more loathsome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VealHeidi @FrogStreet @ConsciousD @IndianCreekES @hermelindasteel @MsFloresprek I love that they are meeting. IN A CLASSROOM! 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this is a fascinating question. Do we create#digital health technology that empowers people and gives them… https://t.co/tgHU8D7nfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBetker I meant INFORMATION,  not  invitation.   Seriously, sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola! @fenapoOficial Nos gustaría que tomaran en cuenta a @RioRomamx este año para la edición de la #Fenapo2019. Gracias de antemano☺]]></document><document><![CDATA[1986 Donruss Factory Sealed  Pop up Puzzle and Cards (4 pks available) $0.50 each  (Reply with how many packs you'd… https://t.co/R6iGlG3b1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selling off all my Twilight collection on eBay it's a 3D it moves when you walk side to side does anybody have it o… https://t.co/qlkzOPMeqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you thought I wasn’t going to post everything from THON to my story, you were wildly mistaken and don’t know me at all  #THON2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost brickellcitycentre with get_repost ・・・ Welcome to our tropical heaven, Miami. 📷 @miamimagazine… https://t.co/WlG1AMIhXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMooreLPM Keep on keeping on!  I really love to see the map when we study someone like Paul or David.  Allows a… https://t.co/pLbPZSkogX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then the ice princesses grew up to be   queen bitch in Pretty Little Liars 👸🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dem lie, Puerto Rico received 4 billion in aid from Fema. 208 million to the aquaduct and sewer authority, 22.6 mil… https://t.co/cfZv7UJhF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great panel discussion with our SLT @LynnRotatori @jasonbanks33 #WMSales2019 https://t.co/Gtb3iGspS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[wish I was there just so I could talk shit to her in Spanish while I’m beating her ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyyyCoCo @Jazmin_sanjose First time attending Beyond!!! I’m super excited!!! ♥️♥️♥️♥️]]></document></documents></author>