<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LangstonJessica @annefromthehub @imalizzzard @SalesforceOrg Time to celebrate!   Appy Birthday to you!!!!!! https://t.co/CRFAJ6c5aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watspn1013 @RealJamesWoods @ClintonPhobic @therealroseanne He should go to jail for trying to start a race war]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUYS I MEANT HOPE NOT HOOE I LOVE YOU JONAH @JonahMarais  Bet $1,234,567,894 that the boys wont notice me ever not in 1million years😢😭😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lgiesige_13 Yes but just the general point is what I’m referring to 😂😂 I didn’t notice that at first tbh 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kristen @ Crafts Galore-The Rebel Store https://t.co/3SCB295gc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we will talk about the OG of the Catwomen. Her unforgettable voice intrigued us all and kept us entertained!… https://t.co/vQvHYyMbUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the contrary, @aedwardslevy, this is the most impressively audacious methods statement I’ve ever seen 😂 https://t.co/mKGdWDzXle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficerMooken I cannot believe how stupid people are....if it was their loved one at risk they would change their tune]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine dropping a couple grand on spring break just to experience pmans but in warm weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1JonQPublik @RightHookUSA @DavidRM2A @foxandfriends I was being sarcastic, the left seems to think riots make A po… https://t.co/WXguMLVmVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Camden73573989 @TheDemCoalition She's not "illegal" as you so callously say. The woman in question is a DACA recip… https://t.co/Xvr4F2YQOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marykayconsult3 Ridiculous when their is 1million pain suffers that are the only proof he needs. Oh but I forgot w… https://t.co/Eyax7kTdNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how everyone is turned around except for the captain. If it works, it works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nomad sleeper exhibit A 🤦🏼‍♀️ the kitchen table 🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️ whyyy??? @ Starship Corkle https://t.co/QpB2YvSIS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I had a great time talking to some super smart students &amp; learning as usual from DouglasESchoen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradley1a What do you want to bet when he dies, Jesus bitch slaps old Jerry and has him escorted to the "down only… https://t.co/Dsvelvy9Fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have NO idea wtf “birote” is ....this is, has always been, and always will be “BOLILLO”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jfmedeiros3 @InComandante @aless_moro @Ferri3Joana @mtcosmo1 @linharesneto5 @leandroreis10 @flavia_lpoes… https://t.co/x5pktwmDnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnidMartinez @NABEorg Beautiful, Enid! I feel the same way. I was honored that you would be in my session. If you'… https://t.co/kMg50hLPJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federal judge Ronnie Abrams yesterday handed down an astonishingly tough sentence to U.S. soldier-turned-mercenary… https://t.co/VazPg7KJwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bec_christine is in London and we still managed to be on FaceTime 😂😂😂😂🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[really wanna see a season of the bachelor with super average people. let’s give the 4s, 5s and 6s a shot at finding love how bout]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ldogls @johnnysaygo @oldmanliver @EveScottGarner @HondoResists @ldog562 @gtlang74 @RealAntHen @Jessie092859463… https://t.co/WfGbbZgBSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article GG! Congrats on being invited to train with the Chilean National Volleyball team in March,)❤️❤️ Keep… https://t.co/xn2egxqi6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent 2 days reading and analyzing an article...... only to find out I CANT USE IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[📣Attention New Mexico baseball players📣 The first step towards Team USA 🇺🇸 ⚾️ starts with National Team Identificat… https://t.co/VyLHO7aAKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MILITARYMOM171 @LibertEendfed @LoveBling6 @HuckleberryHon1 The Podestas shipped people in crates marked artwork to… https://t.co/2qSdwCefZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quiet_Ka_Lang_ @IQdoubledigit @WlLDNATURE Thats not torture. I wash stuff off my body too. It's called "grooming"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stagelily @valleybkseller @chriscander @aeskens @wendywebbauthor @BerkleyPub .We are looking forward to welcoming you! 📚📚📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE LORD IS STILL GOOD.  HE IS GOOD YESTERDAY.  HE IS GOOD TODAY.  AND HE WILL BE GOOD TOMORROW.   I can promise you that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenwooddavis Flights are the only place we don’t fight about electronics! Use ‘em. See you when we land.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewRelease WHAT THE WIND KNOWS by @aharmon_author  https://t.co/LwbPApXFyj   "A story that beats with its very own… https://t.co/VKEEQB1DEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Afternoon Beautifuls... About last night... 👩🏽‍🎨👩🏽‍🎨👩🏽‍🎨I had a Blast with my Chica, Mrs. Angela Posey and eve… https://t.co/X6oJyaJvxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s GAMEDAY!! Conference starts today as we take on Nicholls State at 5 and 7! I’m so happy that these seniors all… https://t.co/8OcB39Vn2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with all that but for me part of the problem with Bernie is he has no detailed plan as to how he plans on i… https://t.co/cT3QQ5lMag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks. Always looking for good videos to use during coaching sessions. Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MannyMontana @lesshertmoreluv Can’t wait for Season 2, mostly because I love watching Manny.  Hot hot hot and an e… https://t.co/tnNIgfCxwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFPfaff 🤣 It’s an opportunity to promote  ̶y̶o̶u̶r̶ ̶l̶a̶t̶e̶s̶t̶ ̶s̶i̶n̶g̶l̶e̶ ̶o̶n̶ ̶S̶o̶u̶n̶d̶C̶l̶o̶u̶d̶̶ yo… https://t.co/DGFvnu1lsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGGrinch @wearewoodruff @smckc More Dog Days of Woodruff please! My pup and I are big fans 😍 https://t.co/LE8I8ya5a0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @SpeakerPelosi Where is YOUR money coming from? Taxpayers and lobbyists? If taxpayers, you listen to us.  If l… https://t.co/I3lkybcj1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissamcut and I have a shared love of great tv that is a pillar of our friendship to be honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kourtneykardash is my fav Kardashian. No BS. Just doing her own thing always. Love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took everything within me not to throw my phone across the room after watching this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Undone Braid + Blue Skies 🕊 #CaraJourdanTravel photo by paigeowenphotography @ Red Rock Canyon Las Vegas https://t.co/0KLJuyKW6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lombardidreamin @Fab_Mommy_ @ScratchPaper8 @hotmessheckyes @BabyGirlGrim @herprettybones 🤩🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost set my apartment on fire from trying to cook (again) so I think it’s just time to close this attempt and never eat again 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNatsFanatic @Nats_Source @scherzday @dcNATSHACK I can’t throw away 7 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking around downtown city life  Photographed by Me  https://t.co/wBuctiq7mP #photographer #photographerslife… https://t.co/NhOTWkElhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love nighttime so so much. There’s no feeling quite like being outside, alone, in the middle of a long, foggy night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does ANYBODY need a stay at home wife yet? I’m getting too old to work and need to retire right now. https://t.co/m4VaxWLN1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okayonion @rtrmntprty TYSM !!! still a work in progress got lots to build on lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[took Advil and my back is still killing me. Like how? Absolutely no relief]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may be why Apostle Paul is one of my favorites. He was born not long after Jesus died. Yet he’s so relevant to… https://t.co/JvrO9d9hgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa, @chelseaperetti speaks toddler FLUENTLY. This is ground breaking work, people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to cumbys in a robe and flamingo slippers and this woman behind me in line whispered “the crazies are alread… https://t.co/FWyGIS9zX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just how big of a loser do you have to be to hide behind a fake name on social media and bash every racer that has… https://t.co/nanCOGtTow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amado Dios, que hermoso es despertar cada mañana y sentir la bendición de tu obra. En esta oración me acerco a Ti p… https://t.co/nJR8K6FBuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERudolph514 @krassenstein You damn demoturd, whatl did Obummer do to earn the Peace Prize?  Nada!! Trump has negot… https://t.co/FMTdzXLgZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third Request - although does it matter at this point?  @benjaminwittes  @tribelaw  @atlblog… https://t.co/HRZ6qd05nZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@jncouncil .@seoulmania .@wonsoonpark @seoulcouncil Seoul Yongsan-gu, South Korea, Shut down the illegal dog meat… https://t.co/xB8XMhv3Tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chortletown Here's a senior..tried n true...perfect for an older person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome back @JoelEmbiid  We missed you!!!! #HereTheyCome https://t.co/JSAzhkoG6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 What we think about your apolgy-   Matt Gaetz is a licensed attorney in Florida. His Ba… https://t.co/T1ST6nLa52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayleyromano Right?! It’s so random and out of place but regardless she does not represent this city 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[This head in a jar gag is an easy prank to pull on April Fool's Day!... #mirth #tee-hee #smirk #humorous https://t.co/xJM2Khth6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE OFFICIALLY HIT THE 4000 WATCH HOURS WE WILL BE DOING AN EPIC LIVE SYREAMS THANK YOU FOR LOVING US ENOUGH TO GIVE… https://t.co/PbAc2rSsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I often forget people are normal and have 9-5/realisabilities/school/a normal sleeping schedule]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DallasColodny Oh man, sorry Dallas.   How scary!!   Glad you made it out without bad injuries.   Dang, drunk drive… https://t.co/ZhDnZF2o9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Wes Farno, public relations representative at @Dannon in Minster, for coming and talking to our studen… https://t.co/i3qX3X0zw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt Arrogant and flippant.  If that was supposed to be a joke it had a crash landing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fiji_taylorrr @_antoinesampah @BallCoach34 @NavyFB @CoachAIngram Congratulations!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sairdysue YES. More all the time now. So I try to pester them to query because I selfishly want to hold their books in my hands too 😂🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[May or may not have eaten over half the box already...🤫🤷‍♀️ S/O to my favorite coaches @11coachplunk and… https://t.co/oagCXlRsiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @indianarosemary Maybe they can share a cell at Leavenworth..... or maybe we can resurrect Arpaio’s… https://t.co/mnQaJphxn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jawofsteel2014 @krassenstein @LoveNOLA4ever Oh hell Brian Trump is terrified.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some girl tipped me tonight for my words of wisdom. She told me I was saying everything she needed to hear. Babe I got you 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something peaceful about wind and trees 🙃🌳🍃🌬 #sandiego #wind #trees #breeze #peaceful #calming #beautiful @ San Die… https://t.co/WxCKCSdoYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course because all the people who want FREE everything are willing to throw a few bucks at him. Too bad they are… https://t.co/C9dB75L6VQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i saw this scene on family guy and immediately thought of @katrinacrouch13 https://t.co/UexKc2CmFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Who hired this twit?  He doesn’t think about legality before giving legal advice and tapes his clie… https://t.co/9VVvGaCixb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Felizidane” no lo puede describir. Hoy es mas que eso. #ChiringuitoZidane]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we are going to freeze to death, it might as well snow. #snowangel ❄️ @ Upper Highlands Neighborhood - Louisvill… https://t.co/FWzRxqKfdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrRachaelF I think this is WIDELY varied. Especially in States that don’t require an MA.  My mother makes barely 4… https://t.co/PxQjSw1zhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[i helped you out of a broken place  you gave me comfort falling for you was my mistake]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is beautiful. Tia Ciata was a symbol of Black resistance. A precursor of samba when it was considered an activ… https://t.co/qWvMpfY7B7]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI chorizo is much better w a sunny side up egg instead of scrambled eggs bc runny yolk. Thank you for coming to my TED Talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorenvanzant @stopbeingfamous The greed of power can do many evil things. https://t.co/3yBNEPImnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the "REAL" #Seaworld that they don't want you to know about 😡😥💔 .@cnni .@MSNBC. @BBCWorld .@60Minutes  Plea… https://t.co/LACuVD7XqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chriscoffeytalk @crgshldn @Merleliz @LostInAmerica77 @goodhorsekeeper @JuliaManhattan @CentralParkNYC @nyclass… https://t.co/39jfyQWDnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Huskerfan047 @TheFrankOzJam All lot of us artists are hoping for it to change to STEAM. The arts are valuable too. #hoping]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love running errands😫 vacuuming ur car, going to the bank, grocery shopping, ALLLL THAT!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NA Girls Track 4x800 Meter Relay finishes 7th at #NBNationals in NYC.  Congratulations to Ainsley Dion, Abby Mastro… https://t.co/RtEw38N3Ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyfamilyday from the 'phews and I See you later on the #123shorncliffe #yourfavoritedriver #Toronto https://t.co/81Zjn0imNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign Jon Stewart's petition to support 9/11 survivors https://t.co/WtbacQhmaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[In response to “your favorite president” from Palmer Report @bunkybun @KittyBhagat @lilith2u @Dennis_Lintz… https://t.co/omE81j5Wwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great workout!! Out of gas and out of gas! Ha! Get it?!! Xo 😘 @ Orangetheory Fitness Plano https://t.co/76fxDPIDkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Severide's apartment is super nice...just saying #ChicagoFire https://t.co/ZdZhs59B1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great class today on alligators with a recommendation to visit Horton's pond for a siting. . .sure enough there the… https://t.co/Enu2UhoKGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vudoobird @thomaskaine5 1 term of Biden &amp; the we’ll have President Kamala Harris!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He hideth our soul in the depth of the rock and covers us there with HIS HAND!  The only safe place in end times wi… https://t.co/o1fC4e24Cu]]></document></documents></author>