<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jrandall15 @cjzero hah. We’ll see. It happened before he even tried to stop, seemed he was leaning back too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolRia Ria I’ve criticized you when warranted.  But fuck this guy.  I would gladly drag him for you.  😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joe_jjorgensen @chogenson If he goes pro, so be it. Not really sure why you would love him at this point. Nothing… https://t.co/VFnSnvl9x7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2020Vision 🔥🧡💜 @GPinkney3 @GBrown9_ @iv_shellman @MikeJr_2020 https://t.co/mZPllAe8ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[the next female i get she gotta stick around, i ain’t trying to learn nobody else lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMS_Arianna @BMSMaxContract @BMS_Derek You’re young! Sling that box while guys still wanna see it🤷🏼‍♂️ be safe and… https://t.co/dpW94onNfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready! Dating season begins this summer!  Compile Heart begins streaming Date A Live: Ren Dystopia teaser trail… https://t.co/yqeGQ45wbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearstownSox35 Noooooo Chicago hot dogs are good, deep dish pizza is overrated though you’re right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never seen this much snow in the ground in Eugene. https://t.co/1fSv7LjOaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Ts are here! I’ve restocked on popular graphics and made a new batch as well. Get yours through the photo li… https://t.co/ZAm6JCPpxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought chicks over dicks was a things and now that I know it’s not I better start to ditch my homegirls if Im tryna get my back blown out]]></document><document><![CDATA[This chum scrubbing bum in a work meeting (over the Internet) HAD to ask “do we need to have our cameras on for ven… https://t.co/OLY3gHnb32]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot over emphasize how incredible it is for the president of the United States to be saying that representat… https://t.co/8mKcmpsc1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you had to fight one of the M&amp;M’s from the M&amp;M’s commercial which one would it be?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerWa64103475 @DonaldJTrumpJr @DailyCaller He is a treasure trove of info on the Podesta/Clinton scam supported by the Obama Team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechLayDee Which is why the apparent Jordan/LeBron debate amuses me.  (Or I’m one of those people that can’t let g… https://t.co/f4qit8nbq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkmilton @ryancraigap @mzrascoff @pmfreedm @DukeLearning @rkniemer Glad to serve as moderator. Shall we set ground… https://t.co/EkDAqiVkAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realRickWiles I hear you like witches? We should talk. https://t.co/4s9ixYfAfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ I always thought Brittany Spears was perfect 🙄🙄 . . . NOT!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsTalkSkins @kevinlc555 @Powerbarz22 I know man. Can’t figure it out. Sports are almost as bad as politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALEX AVILA IS STILL ON THE ROSTER HERE, @Gambo987  WAS THERE A PROBLEM WITH THE LIMOUSINE?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMAjunkie @benfowlkesMMA @dannyboydownes I think @cainmma should have taken an easier fight after a long layoff fr… https://t.co/xuVayrIlA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nfergus my father told me to beware the "moles in the Knolls" and Communist sympathizers in universities.  Marxism… https://t.co/nfhf9Kl77k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jack_Septic_Eye What Jack said 👆👆👆👆  What I said 👇👇👇👇 https://t.co/Xqx71LBZML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonstreBete93 @EmoAnimeGorl LA Fitness forsure! If you want the hook up let me know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio Please vote for Taylor #iHeartAwards #BestMusicVideo #Delicate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pharmacokinetix @MiLB @AviatorsLV @sportslogosnet @LasVegasLocally @RJ_Sports @DICKS Lol that’s what I’m thinking too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanuckCognizant @AOC at least one murder investigation.  I don't want devices that are ALWAYS listening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just have one question? Does it mean if we go by the Socialist Regime Medicare for all, that all members of Congr… https://t.co/kJEuEnrTA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoniFreedhoff Me watching that movie (probably). https://t.co/qysPlh56kV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to play music through audio-out (headphone connect ) to line -in Sonos on iPad or iPhone. It will only play… https://t.co/gwXirM2kaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maca_puentes @jaimeberenguer @EspFP Zaaassssscaaaaaa.....juasjuasjuas 😝😝...pues hoy estás sembrada.... https://t.co/ESto4oIHud]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom has been covering baseball for decades. She also worked as the PA announcer of @leones_cbbc from 1994 to 200… https://t.co/PeaXwdqy8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Jesse Watters confuse Robin Roberts with Gayle King? Yes. Yes, he did. 😬 https://t.co/4ZVE7Hc6ZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s finally out check it out on ➡️ @facebook my first interview with @esthersitaaa 👑🇻🇪 #NewSeasonNewMe https://t.co/0bFtbYOz5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter You’re fine bro! Skinny guys should be just as confident, too, just as buff guys. Don’t listen to the… https://t.co/CxYvhZBI0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impudentearworm @acmills237 Though the concept is hilarious, it makes me physically ill to think about sorting through Drew’s tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current situation...  [Insert Lanwmower Man Quote Here] https://t.co/NeY8Ne2mUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀 Check out this NEW 🎶 VIDEO: Zazilla "AlreadyOn" Featuring @Baccwoodrillo https://t.co/YJixYNu3PB @Chino4real #MakingItHappen #801StandUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nordic_Scotty @perlmutations I have to see it that way...sometimes..or I’ll cry 😂😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Harper goes to the Dodgers he is the biggest Wuss in the history of sports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PointsBetUSA too late to name a bet for lakers / clippers?  Looking for Reggie Bullock under 11.5 pts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Milky Way by @Trophybrewing @ Braids By Jane — https://t.co/ZhNOSj1Ule]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm considering this a "proof of concept" wager...it's still going to take a while to sink in for me that sports be… https://t.co/GpfQ49cVZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeverNoire @marcushjohnson @RedTRaccoon It's okay.  We don't see it either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wxjay Glad it fixed it. Disturbed about how much has been breaking lately. One option you could definitely use is… https://t.co/dWndVgbkQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMJOY it was really astonishing to see a president of this country speaking like a 5 years old kid. Is this this w… https://t.co/ra7YU9US5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, dry February would have been a success if it ended on February 24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgyeiAbigail12 Thanks for Following! Bob Morton  https://t.co/mnEB9rwfGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OJessicaNigri I would love to wear an exact recreation of my Inquisitor’s endgame armor from Dragon Age: Inquisiti… https://t.co/i33tUcVfaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop I had forgotten we have had so many famous rats. Rats are awsome pets and have gotten a bad rap. Cohan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethedel @katieglueck @Bakari_Sellers Except they'd probably struggle competing at this too... https://t.co/sjqGixL9TN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC please talk more about the white supremacist Coast Guard person who threatened Chris Hayes and others in the media]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoddessGeek1 @calliesaurus @EmmaWedekind Nothing wrong with that! The world needs loving, selfless people more than ever. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concierto  #DevotionalDave  Depeche Mode experience  1 de marzo de 2019 Little Rock    #LuisFelipeGaspar #Concierto… https://t.co/RdYdQgv27J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven You also have to guard yourself against only listening to voices that agree with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate waking up middle of the night tired as hell but can’t go back to sleep.... this literally only happens when I’m off the next day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickatoni @DrSPff @RodneyDavis @repmarkpocan My lord dems just don’t get when they’re the but of the joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottydog57 @akkingon @Minuteman223 @44_rem_mag @teamregulators @pensfannc5 @Bearman1130 @mgaryhanson @2deere222… https://t.co/MhQGd0pxzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydnets @ODouglasPrice @jacob_mays @bradplumer @AustralianLabor @jmkorhonen Anyway, this is about general tendenci… https://t.co/q2KBmHLJeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YolaDibal @VictorMendozaL Que raro Yola, si es él, el personaje con más y mejor liderazgo en México. Más bien, est… https://t.co/SQGVt37tGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Under 50? OK.  Over 50? They’re kidding themselves, looking for trouble, or both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Wish you would go back to Fox.  You were ALWAYS fair and informative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn't even gonna mess around with a beanie after the ear debacle yesterday with Troy Baker. Brian Bloom totally… https://t.co/nXPAVrTVht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TheDemocrats @HillaryClinton @GOP @SenSanders @amazon @CBS @CNBC @SenWarren @SenWarren pushes for… https://t.co/i5XKqIkHlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[JOIN @nghtmre @hakkasanlv &amp; HAVE FUN 📲 440.487.5000 4 FREE ENTRY ON MY GUESTLIST OR TABLE INQUIRIES/RESERVATION… https://t.co/fbNjw1R38b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanSchachtel It has nothing to do with collusion even. There is no debate over whether Russia infiltrated our e… https://t.co/m3x064adZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m that guy standing behind you in the check out line at the grocery store or sitting next to you in church, or in… https://t.co/84BsPSRarQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FedEx going above and beyond in sub-zero temperatures.   @FedExHelp @FedExPolicy https://t.co/aU4DW7UEJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie I 100 PERCENT AGREE,JUST THAT ALONE IS SO WRONG ON SO MANY LEVELS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest on the deadly crash in #LibertyCity from over the weekend. Woman hit a killed by driver being pursued by pol… https://t.co/mVSb7Z1SkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EileenOttawa @bruceanderson Good question. I question the 15% but in any case every canadian should read the PCF.… https://t.co/galq4K0zCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeD44734654 @FabianArdaya @Buster_ESPN Yes but two 10+ years 300+ million contracts is different when you have H… https://t.co/lNOZSRG2tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REDFASU @BobbyEberle13 @RyanAFournier @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama @HillaryClinton @jack @TwitterMoments @Twitter… https://t.co/7sRJpR3Nhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshman Lobo Baseball team lost a close one to smithson valley 4-3. Proud of the effort and their fight till the l… https://t.co/AqIfOpIx6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then this Nigga was acting all weird and shit and then he start digging in his back pack I thought he had the thang… https://t.co/yN7XAvNYiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@alicecooper has a lot on his plate these days, but he's not losing his head over it https://t.co/E3mWZN5SrP… https://t.co/IM3YJeySLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEkidBECK Yes it took me forever to get on the train cause I was trying to hold it up against the office...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The commentary I am most looking forward to tomorrow is from @JohnWDean]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure they’re just pivotovating value hacked disruptportunities  #SXSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NakedAndAfraid the bear had absolutely no interest in Steven's shrunk junk]]></document><document><![CDATA[McConnell has shown himself to be nearly as dispicable as Trump.  He’s more sinister ‘cause he’s smarter and more d… https://t.co/NP0Inv4GQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KKeneally It is about time you were honest and said this is all about providing disincentives for people to be ind… https://t.co/heqlLfkCWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Plante @md_is_coding @parker0phil @_julesh_ @getify (.)(.)(.) total recall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genuinely happy to see @WWERomanReigns tonight. I never thought I’d say that. 😆Congratulations Joe! Welcome back!!… https://t.co/rybkjiUy69]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone that isn’t able to wear black skinny jeans all 365 days of the year is a fucking coward and thats why im the… https://t.co/zegRSAMFKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad the only 🔥🔥🔥I saw today was from “The Biscuit.” A nice hat trick to be near the top with James. And, nice to b… https://t.co/BJnY2SceUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MWObs @HayleyWMUR @KevSkarupaWMUR @joshjudgewmur @MikeHaddadWMUR  didn’t realize it at the time, but we caught the… https://t.co/xJCSiYrhrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjwil2303 @CoachAlbin @BrianHainesb @MarcGivlerBG @AllenTrieu @SWiltfong247 @BillBankGreene @BobcatAttack… https://t.co/ye4bAovCyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[One week from today sunset is at 7 pm with dusk 🌆 not until around 7:30 pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes I was there when they were (what I assumed to be) a rescue operation, here’s a clip of it from Saturday https://t.co/1KjmiI5uyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I changed a lot in the 250 days I got served so I'm gonna add cash to my debit card so I can accept her coll… https://t.co/OufGnSjaNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaand we're underway in Plymouth for the NHIAA ski jumping championships. Kennett going for a three-peat. Hanover… https://t.co/axTSjbBYfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw an ad for a new book coming out called The Making of a Manager by @joulee and after peeking at the list… https://t.co/zNo5hInmoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonnysun Bao was beautiful and made me cry. Such a beautiful little film.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people ask why I be lowkey, guess I’m too real for you to act like I’m your homie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnreggie @kimguilfoyle @EpochTimes How is the weather in Moscow, Comrade Republican. I hope you don't freeze from… https://t.co/B1yqMsWKk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyk1920 @benshapiro And if he doesn’t u will learn what ? Make me excited and wanna watch how this plays out wit… https://t.co/EoQa9gVlpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:44.1°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raptors' depth spoils DeRozan's homecoming #WeTheNorth https://t.co/OovZRVZ6vB]]></document></documents></author>