<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cynaragee Oh thank goodness you said this part because the trailers are cut to look like fat jokes a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation @PremierScottMoe @BlaineHiggs my tax dollars hard earned tax dollars paid for you to travel since when ru a govt employee]]></document><document><![CDATA[When correcting errors, don’t delete the post!! Create a new post correcting your error- deleting it right away doe… https://t.co/07dskgZBUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[El artista, Jesús Núñez, nos hace una cordial invitación!! https://t.co/4mNYCfLRf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way too pumped for another year of Soundset • • • Hopefully I get more pictures and better videos this year 🤪 @ Min… https://t.co/2AjldjmKwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got drunk tonight but bet I made sure to wash and moisturize my face and take three tums and two advils before bed.… https://t.co/Vl6vqUZSU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spot on. Hillary Clinton: 'We are living through a full-fledged crisis in our democracy'  https://t.co/IdNP1z0iOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the best people to be with 🖤 #emorap #seattle #snrg #aaroncarter #heesunlee #someneverreallyget… https://t.co/UrUAbEp2YN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two more favorite @pen15show recaps to share. The first is the show's take on race and awakening to prejudice. It's… https://t.co/GJP8XecPDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 If EVERY one of the Democratic candidates will have to ANSWER for decisions made in the past, why is it… https://t.co/7g4mT85xmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatstherukkus @j082298 @The_Acumen @LolaMotz @ai_jared Your comment only ratifies how much harm the shameful medi… https://t.co/j6iVcIeSFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad I hear this news. @AP Reporting Luke Perry has died following has stroke last week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[would anyone like to run my errands for me while I lay in bed with vertigo this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Cinco Minutos del Espíritu Santo: 14 de Febrero: https://t.co/fsIPn4aQ7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jesseniatrejo_ girl this irritates me 💀💀 it stresses me out bc i make a mess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkinKalmen @stamango22 @nowthisnews @AOC You have to consider the source of your info. The Washington Examiner w… https://t.co/qV5WRJtgQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beautiful,amazing girl has been there for me through everything I have been through and today and the past cou… https://t.co/4zfdZhCFbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling it a night ✌🏽😘 #tgif #goodnight @ Dunwoody, Georgia https://t.co/wAOELjkimG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sarm_ 😆😆😆 I feel pretty confident that  some of my 14 year old PSR students probably share the same sort of messa… https://t.co/pC4KM4j7dN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathyrinnn @MicroRose_ Thank you! I just submitted one myself, and I think that’s the only way they accept it I be… https://t.co/8bufySavOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump WHAT'S UNFAIR IS THAT YOU'RE RUINING THIS GREAT COUNTRY OF OURS! THE LONGER YOU'RE IN OFFICE,  THE… https://t.co/oFZ0JFU2je]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selinazawacki @hackaday @tindie @Regorlas @socallinuxexpo Much happier :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk like you mean it. There's nothing better than seeing adorable animals taking baths. https://t.co/jFaZyirlt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy bday to the most inspirational, incredibly uplifting influencer to ever exist, thank u for using your platfor… https://t.co/9CxaWQ2Q1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want to thank everyone who joined us at the Allied Distribution Services Customer Appreciation Cocktail Party, i… https://t.co/s7BJaEjuBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[sunny &amp; 75 here at the Texas Tulip fields 💐💗🌷 @ Texas-Tulips https://t.co/vuHmZYzXN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/yM9CxahqMt… https://t.co/Htisr5U5lI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews PLEASE refuse to let ACTUAL news networks cover you. It would save us multiple showers a… https://t.co/I2WCRsKaoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamCarp48 @VanityFair American companies did support Nazism but you're weaving truth into propaganda. Why?  Begin… https://t.co/pgpqiYsbYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[After an Extra long drive to get home my sweet Valentine had these beautiful flowers waiting for me!!! Love you Fra… https://t.co/lG5COQnAeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StampedeStanco I’m feeling your flow, so had to break out these... #MotivationMonday #MambaMentality https://t.co/0LOX5efeKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerleeValentine @politico Noticed the ex, if worse than Trump...you definately made the right decision to dump him… https://t.co/GjMnxuE7zG]]></document><document><![CDATA[just so everyone knows it’s @tedwards105 bday   just a public service announcement]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. I’m going to watch one of favs to fall asleep... #DevilWearsPrada 💋 #JaeLeighBoutique]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinnPatriot @randalthom .......this is way out of line......why do the Dems get away with such ruthless behavior..… https://t.co/8Gbw29oftF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celi_ahumada @MementoMori_est @davoespinosa11 Deberías de agradecernos que por nosotros México todavía es algo en el mundo. 😜✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait a minute @Brian_Eastwood, does that mean that you HAVE sat on a unicorn NOT in a suit? 😳🙈 #WTFHealth… https://t.co/QjpAE4jIOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow what does it take for Jailmart to changes roles within Walmart? Will we see a change in our greeters or just mo… https://t.co/qWhtDRSDXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can Melrose Public Schools just announce that there’s no school tomorrow like everyone else already??? 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huh. There might be an upside to this whole "morning" thing. #nofilter @ Lincoln Park https://t.co/9ql0CASglM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpCrimeFamily #TraitorTrump America is literally living through worst reality show on earth.… https://t.co/c0aqWqp4zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briankoppelman You do partnerships well. It’s s terrific skill. Bravo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CruellaCaloca @duckking2015 @MessMinchin3 @madmanalo @lee031886 Mabait lang talaga ako. Hahaha. https://t.co/Qp32QZ8ok1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Según Brayan y yo solo íbamos ir a cenar  y por un litro y todo termino tan pero tan mal 🥺🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s two kinds of people: •those that can tech-deck  •those who can’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerrjoseph reply with a selfie back if your wife is jenna joseph https://t.co/O2nRvgcQ9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve really been missing church every Sunday... can’t wait to be back home and back to one of my favorite places ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy ! @BlogChurchWork @Headerop1 @JustaSlob @amvetsupport @BlueGhost40_ @PreetBharara @B52Malmet @RepAdamSchiff… https://t.co/6wzSG10SDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Maryland #Conneticut #Missippi #NewYork #Florida #Washington #Illinois #California #Chicago #Vegas #LasVegas… https://t.co/CvV09LSv3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[You aren't a decent human being so I don't know where you think you can call someone racist because he said that. S… https://t.co/bfLtSKRbmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat Wrinkle-free clothing is clearly quite important to her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably the time I measured and sewed custom clothes for my two pet turtles and made the clothes in their favorite… https://t.co/ItpjhGs4Sf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building more buildings amongst the buildings.  #skyscraper #buildingbuildings #construction #progress ? #jenga… https://t.co/wZhBvGmRpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessPrian @msylvestre66 @Mx_Diputados @senadomexicano @lopezobrador_ #MiAforeNoEsParaObrador]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriennewhitma1 @SpeakerPelosi @RepGregoryMeeks The only abuse of power is Nancy Pelosi, but I don't expect her le… https://t.co/prUn01S8Gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woooow!  An HONOR and pleasure to meet and be further inspired by such dynamic leaders!  Thank you for your graciou… https://t.co/JdJMGP6ujw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend is playing his PlayStation instead of giving me constant attention??? How rude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best life 🌟💫  . . . . . #beach #workout #fitness #sundayfunday #blessedlife #goodvibes #mindbodysoul #activewear… https://t.co/oi9eZV7B3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt @AManddt That is HORRIBLE. I can not wrap my head around this. Big PHARMA is a huge problem for USA. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[4. Help us keep our self-esteem intact. Imagine falling down in front of a crowd and people begin to whisper that y… https://t.co/ZjhPbcyCHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saqibishaq07 @freeCodeCamp It was all typed out and everything! Just forgot to hit tweet 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Dallas_Girl @JamesCraigmyle @ladygaga Agree!!!  I’m just waiting to hear they’re together!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aveces quiero salir a monte o a la cabaña o a donde sea para bailar pero luego recuerdo q los de California no sabe… https://t.co/TH5Odu49TI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just took action on @theactionnet: Join the picket line to support Oakland teachers, students, and parents!. Take… https://t.co/mKuw1BnaQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeckJacob @MarkDice So sad... These types will take anything... Even an animal.  So CREEPY!   VERY DISEASED BEINGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣Open House! Saturday the 23rd from 1-4pm 41799 Camino De La Torre, Temecula 92592. Call Nikki James Giulitto at 95… https://t.co/L4tlQySKxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flesbcps &amp; @SWA_Tigers staff actively engaged in Youth Mental Health First Aid training Session 1 @BcpsMTSS… https://t.co/CNVHE8Q1vC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to remind bae who the mf boss is. https://t.co/rmsh6Hc1Kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyeamGoDD How so? Maybe this specifically, but there is this weird concept of men wanting a “down bitch” who will… https://t.co/ubHVMEOOqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday davethecoronas !!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ @ The Short Stop https://t.co/ZluLTspBnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women with money and women in power are two uncomfortable ideas in our society — Candace Bushnell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ddaian i was in the living room right in front of the tv. u not the only one sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadiandaws83 @shannongailmc @DoloresManley4 @cathyhadenough @ShapesBlue @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16… https://t.co/bv7aAv80pR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleased to be awarded the #1 Agent in West Central Florida again in 2018 for @CB_Florida Coldwell Banker Residentia… https://t.co/EbihHaaC4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csweeney121 did you go to a drive thru when i was sleeping or was this just a late night thought lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReturnOfDeeO @GLDrunkThoughts Bro is this shit fake, I want to be the d-bag that owns this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveWestly This needs to happen across the industry.... hello Central Market 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a sweater on + 5 blankets layered on me yet I’m still FREEZING 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna know if I have “dumb bitch” written on my forehead. Becauseeee that’s what these niggas be acting like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Midland, MI, check out this #CustomerService job via the link in our bio: Full Avail… https://t.co/Jd1dzWOLEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ti6awQGUYl  Make an approach Amazon phone number 1-855-431-5111 for precise arrangements  #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hey just as we’re celebrating our first full year in a Portland rental without the building being torn down our… https://t.co/U7hXFb7HNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfletchy has a great 3 act task that involves fractions. He uses the visual of a bowl of oranges. Great opportunit… https://t.co/BYS3KN3bMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop le Numéro Trois #omahabeerweek2019 @ Vis Major Brewing Co. https://t.co/ZpCO5tS9R9]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally heading to notre dame for free in march i’m feeling so 🤩🤩 god is GOOD y’all https://t.co/pfacehzs96]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: Yes and no. Yes more in a personal setting and its been around emotional and all around health, not using the w… https://t.co/1fRUp1rvfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are these Bibles? They look like dimestore paperbacks. Fitting, I guess. Like Trump, guessing no one who owns… https://t.co/BVHjnrdBgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump @PolitiBunny Why would we permit an anti-semite to run for office? She has made the… https://t.co/0tLWdt6QGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[asked driver for a phone charger in a silent uberpool and quarterback by thug started playing at full volume where is the emergency exit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @CNN misdemeanor, not a damn felony. Kraft has money.  Big deal.  Hell, there’s an Asian massage parlor… https://t.co/k7tXFMgMQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats on your new and important role @UCSFimaging Christine! I agree that the future of the dept is in great han… https://t.co/nFqG4tfJPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[CFHS Boys Varsity Basketball Playoffs vs Riverbend - Pictures are up on https://t.co/lUnb9Ng56w and Facebook 🏀💚💙🏀… https://t.co/YRXgw1F9ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[was happily thinking about summer and doin fun stuff, and then I remembered Ashley won’t be here to do it with me 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[*sees a teenager with a full grown beard*  Brain:  Don’t say it Don’t say it Don’t say it  Don’t say it  Don’t say… https://t.co/fdFJWj8qyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found this outside my apartment.   Don’t mind if I do! https://t.co/MhPBnhSvwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russellcrowe @shanedawson Cinematography is one of my favorite award categories!! That’s a lot of skill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great week at IWCE. If you missed us there, find us at https://t.co/kAGls7moo1 to find out more about our Mission C… https://t.co/NzrjsLW5jV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thompsonsfiles Jajaja todavía estoy tan impresionada con tu post y nota de Wilfrido Vargas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Socialsubtext @saradannerdukic @lauferlaw and it is Zuckerberg..and Thiel..and Robert Mercer..and the yes I still… https://t.co/XXsleWHPvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inkelasl @TheRickyDavila I agree there anti-clinton however just this morning I heard Joe saying wonderful things… https://t.co/v2nzdtpjFi]]></document></documents></author>