<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Kraft &amp; #Republican #Politicians are getting caught at string of #MassageParlors owned by #PresTrump Pal;… https://t.co/61hpQq4U7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darla Mears tells me about the latest products from @KodiakCakes at #ExpoWest2019 #oatmeal #graham #retail #grocery… https://t.co/dBRHYu1vWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother Earth Homestead Fair. Met many like minded folks. Like these folks. A Table Full in the Woods @ Bell County… https://t.co/UvNKqdKNrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeHuff @OFranklin74 @MikeEvans1043 @HootersCO Evans doesn’t stand a chance vs big O.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW: @campaignre poll suggests Torontonians overwhelmingly want more bike lanes, lower speed limits, photo radar, a… https://t.co/GNmIg6rvtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, just to avoid misunderstandings: There's no one I've met in this apartment building that I'm friends (or any… https://t.co/0jnRcOHQEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATerando @CaHSRA Don't be so sure. Gavin may judge that hyperloop can be ready about as quickly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ida_due! It’s only the first swim meet for the team, so Corey and @NRubke will be busy changing that reco… https://t.co/kqu8nlPJof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@griffski Tin Man’s San Francisco Stew! Actually any color peppers at the end for crunch and your favorite shaved c… https://t.co/0QDAjF2vfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a strong feeling that @Logic301 and I will survive. With his sick rhymes and my horror movie savvy. 💯👏🏻😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKBHD Know one even knows WHAT the race is. Some are in running shoes, some on dirt bikes, and some in F1 cars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He told y'all the wall was coming. You didn't want to participate so… it's still coming. 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[15u&amp;16u @WeareUTU working hard 🦍🦍🦍work @ Kenneth Hahn State Recreation Area https://t.co/nqjhhCtMlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fear: If I obey God, I will not be happy. This is the same lie that Satan told in the garden.   - Tim Keller]]></document><document><![CDATA[He and I have put together a study that we believe will glean the most possible infomation available to us through… https://t.co/1p2vU6XQJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungeateat Be real ok all people of color have black in them do your research]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaddyFitz13 @lancgal @jbendery @NRA 1st. That is the problem, you think more stringent gun regulation equates to g… https://t.co/QtCsiKpVYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy smokes. Wow. San Perlita vs Hearne at the 2A Regional Tourney. @hoopinsider #RGVHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagosFines19 Please don’t end it too soon. There is help out there. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wikedfun @TheUKBat1 @GrantMenmuir @Piech42 @ocean363 @sfw1515 @Goraji_ @AprilBecher @Lupita_ets Best book I ever read]]></document><document><![CDATA[there's Lexus, the corona beach house, people up in the top top parts, it isn't what it seems]]></document><document><![CDATA[SIGN @BoldProgressive's petition: No pardons for anyone implicated in the investigations around Donald Trump! Sign… https://t.co/mqmijmVO0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk @TheAAF The Crimson Tide is the only sports related thing I pull for more than this league. I real… https://t.co/VeFMqmNiT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TownesVanZandt #TheRitz #HarryAnderson  #poster #concertposter #backintheday ##Austin #ATX #tb #PiranhaRecords… https://t.co/EDf7uGYfzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just noticed I barley have guys friends 98% of my friends are girls 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayemcbride @WWE @USATODAY @BookerT5x @RealStevieRay Does this mean I can break out my old Harlem Heat jokes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/V2SR12BqJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get this. Otoh, minimum wages are high in Los Angeles and I think they have translated into rent inflation. I can… https://t.co/bOUwVrKacc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Perry24 🤣😂🤣😂 exactly your too young to be making babies!! #strapup #jimmyhats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k00laidIT It was good; I had fun watching @saintdle try to find the entrance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captains Sportsmanship meeting getting ready to start https://t.co/8FhD3OVw6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaLexicus Congrats. Fire On Virgo Jessica name with Someone. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Because they support foreign interference with our elections.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We meet Harold the Yeti when we where on #missionbreakout. let me tell you something, he is a hoot. Had to go back… https://t.co/kFNjsPFukC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itstatyannag You can eat more eggs than that and lose around the weight you want in that amount of time because yo… https://t.co/wkoOLED3xS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenFromUSector If only I had the same capacity for the stock market.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Penny_Underbust Yeah, zipping up junk is a valid fear of all with a dick]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MWE 17: still (embarrassingly) working on cant stop wont stop’s recommended listening  Keys brings tender and powe… https://t.co/3JPeS0xbm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Jimbo @realDonaldTrump @JerryNadler @DonaldJTrumpJr Lol your entire twitter feed is proof of obstruction you fucking idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenPozenWSB Happy Valentine's day to you Mrs Lauren https://t.co/t8atCDL2q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trade Carr for a first, trade the 2nd for Antonio brown, draft Kyler Murray]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Davidrwert Dem gaters better get me while I'm sleeping. If they try something when I'm awake, there in for a world of hurt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life can be a joyous celebration if we allow it to be and look for the good and each and every day…… https://t.co/lGMwjQlklf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost 4 years I have not eaten/used eggs in anything.... #eggfree #dairyfree #meatfree #animalfree… https://t.co/4ZGuglTs4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sustaining A Career In Journalism - industry leaders share their experience in how they've pivoted throughout their… https://t.co/lhTzY7Pwtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger This is easy. His support is not fragile. Hogan can try to make fragile only by making a strong comp… https://t.co/sv7h5V806o]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't talk enough about Penny Dreadful's deadly Nightcomers https://t.co/LyxqeOM4zU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys We could make Some BEAUTIFULL Music! Together as a TEAM,Not a PAIR!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLRaider @Chiefskc23 @2xRuRu @TheHumble_21 @Michael_Fabiano @NYPost_Schwartz and that's the frustrating part, havi… https://t.co/d5gNQXsPUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great weekend of learning the flex-bone offense from Mojo’s very own @Coach_Fortune Thank you to @deterball f… https://t.co/TW4ZUlzKsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO EL SOL SALDRÁ PARA TODOS, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/tXAHY7scOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDarlingBoo I'm a little hurt you don't have certain songs on here lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have one question.  why the fk hasn’t @RepMaxineWaters been on more shows.  she is a rock star.  @maddow… https://t.co/t0NRmDJMsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IronClawGaming @Erok8150 @Dblackraven1 @XboxP3 MS know they have the bull bull by the horns. They are not going to disappoint at E3. 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 #They look a lot alike , wonder if Kim is as stupid as his daddy ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Sunday service with the woman who all ways told me God Has A Plan son since I was a kid. It’s been a blessing… https://t.co/FFFcvm3haX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smittie61984 @DavidCornDC I'll open message snoodz https://t.co/1fG5MCTook]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty juicy, super hazy, tropical notes, thick. Canned on 01/02/19, happy to have it in Springfield - Drinking a L… https://t.co/5NJhmiGBhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdw_indiana @peter_masiakos @bschapiroMD @drmlb @ETSshow @MarkSeamonMD @meganranney @ThisIsOurLane @ResearchAffirm… https://t.co/jH4otUn9Od]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compartiendo con mi hermano @wasonbrazoban vainita corta vena TU SUPITEEEE YAHH ! 🙏🏽🎼⚡️  #SONiTAL #LetsEVOLV @ Miam… https://t.co/Nsa3dyuRa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ontsabres905 I know my guy. We are all sick of the misery, our lives have enough of that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaLindae9 @cspanwj @NatlPopularVote Please feel free to leave my country &amp; live somewhere there is a popular vote decides the leader]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOLLY__41 @hottonN35 @johnzellewalker @laceeey016 Did i say i support him ? No i said let him rest. Kelly is still… https://t.co/tlT6l3gKD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SOL_AGUSTIN Este congresista es un asco!! Si le meten en cana,la poblacion creera en la justicia por fin!! Creo que ya es hora,verdad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk I know you prolly won’t see this but I want to take a moment to thank you.  I’m a kid who grew up in the… https://t.co/TnCotQnNy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fijisac916 what do you not like? What "wants/needs" are you looking to fulfill? #asktherightquestions 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdMass @OfficialLivePD @Bran_Blackburn @dancesareo @BigFishUSA @LivePdFans @Bifflawson @MayorBillCarp… https://t.co/V3aopeGyvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huh? I literally just reported what she said. Good grief. Partisanship can be so blinding. Listen to the testimony… https://t.co/zf9MixBwV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dwayne Haskins’ chance is coming, Shaun O’Hara’s stance on Eli Manning, more https://t.co/4fbY83D76K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey nearly broke @BeckyLynchWWE’s arm in half! She’s a fucking a killing machine and it seems that many fo… https://t.co/6BU4cQFpcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PedroLema9 @Moseguello La foto de la vergüenza @PSOE que tristeza😔😔ver un hombre absolutamente desorientado😔😔😔y ho… https://t.co/o5HyK3nuOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanFurnessSea Nice job on the call tonight. Exciting game. You were having some microphone issues though. Would go… https://t.co/tMgHaVfJxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkjones21 @PGATOUR @chambleebrandel @MattGinellaGC @garywilliamsGC Yeah, but we are always aided by your world-fam… https://t.co/bVlvQCkkBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are watching Motown Magic on this fine Saturday night. Washed chronicles lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Know_More_News So true. The way south park rips on Jews you know it must be written produced by Jews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudanks WOKE, insecurities will make some fein for the attention of others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rindfleisch That’s almost as much as I heckled you in America for it, Joel Beef.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally just ran into josh wolf on east 4th and didn't realize until after the fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be a business decision for Tom. @Cubs now are "branded" as a tool of the right wing, whether he thinks… https://t.co/JFiCfSx6eX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @Moralesfor145 on winning the Special Election Runoff for #HD145!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@togray14 🏈💪🏾👈🏾@jetljj4  thankU 🤗@joseph_johnson7 804 @LifeChristianF1 🏈💪🏾✅ https://t.co/k3t7bxKPMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kool conversation #22 John Tavares... @NHL @MattBarnaby3636 @SiriusXMNHL 🇨🇦🇺🇸🏒🥅🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off our meds? “You’re not helping your case here.” You can fault me for being brutally honest. (S)he lied.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsRadioWIP @975TheFanatic @NHL @NHLFlyers My mother - "Dave Schultz won the Stanley Cup for Philadelphia with his hands!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nwaegbe_nkem @olushola_shola @FadaunsiAdeniyi Those guys lets be sincere how many wards did they WIN? Sowore, Mogh… https://t.co/rUysekue6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana si traigo mis audífonos, de haber sabido que en la chamba dejan traerlos no me aburriria así]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Top 10 de 🇨🇺 - 🇨🇺🇺🇸 mejores pagados en 2019:  Yoenis Céspedes $29 MM Nolan Arenado $26 MM J. D. Martínez $23.75… https://t.co/A1hos5aweR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordieabrams Good evening Jordan. The world definitely loves you back. Keep smiling champ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepPerlmutter If you could see fit to include Term Limits, then you are serving the people”. Otherwise, you are si… https://t.co/KUEXRj8t53]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Black ppl we’re with him. We see the tapes of them buying the ammunition. Its sad he had to go thru this for att… https://t.co/lz4L8Rp7iV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Lent @chadtough for every pound I lose during sacrifice I’ll donate a dollar. Sacrificing #Coke #fastfood and… https://t.co/CZxUQlo2Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do Juventus players normally do all this diving and faking being hurt? Ugh... Juve player was literally peaking thr… https://t.co/t4oRlSWjOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #NHL sure loved giving the #SJSharks the shaft in these 2 Games vs Boston! But I guess an Original 6 Team is a Money Maker!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Microsoft Corporation (LC2) in Irving, TX https://t.co/QtVzDRBUSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on my Brother Jesse.  He sent me a message this evening and said he is feeling good. He actually went to wor… https://t.co/2qdVmfm8HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that a new ride I haven’t seen before: Porgress?  😄 my spelling is no better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoeticDevotions If you spit on the cake Elizabeth... I’m going to smear on the ou first befor eating my piece]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abcWNN c'mon Keneth grow some hair.  your head is tooooo pointed to be bald.  We just got rid of a baldy and @ABC… https://t.co/DMfTMiPDfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s very hard to be laid off from work, especially when you’re so passionate about your job and the people you hav… https://t.co/78beDfMvDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The work I do now has give me a revived purpose and it keeps me awake sometimes. Seeing how we can be affected by u… https://t.co/v9D3ByZLQN]]></document></documents></author>