<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheBlackChannel @JussieSmollett I listen to the Tom Joyner Show and they already got the memo of blame the police… https://t.co/ZRJbxqXthk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@upnorthbliss @12nighthorror great answer Sarah. the best i have seen so far. congrats. points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, so the @verge just published an article about how the author would rather play and look at butterflies in… https://t.co/nlr3Vd4NKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is laying the groundwork to de-legitimize the 2020 election #Topbuzz https://t.co/c2oPlFEU6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockiefresh That "Must Be" is #1 pop charts hit material!!! Its a forever song! Never gets old!!!❤it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTrex48 @pkligerman 2/2 Caution filled races for wrecks does not equal good racing in my opinion. I'd prefer to… https://t.co/Wm01HY0pVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @MobileTrakMike - pic of ACCIDENT on 270 East after the twin tanks, east of Sawmill Rd.  #traffic #Columbus https://t.co/fdjMBtxv0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamElizabethan @Mar_e_o17 Bernie : fuck the rich they don’t need big houses  Bernie again : buying his third estat… https://t.co/qblXdgjPqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stevenson MS Band students have Hearts of Gold and Wills of Steel.  @HISDFineArt https://t.co/SST5aJ8LFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scrawni3_RonniE @Wrekonize Im partial to  windows down as the sun sets to church road.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really want to buy a 16-35 buuttt don’t want to drop the money for it right now. I feel the only way is if I sell my 17-40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Sonny on being selected as our Safety Associate Of The Year! Thank you for helping us Drive a Safe… https://t.co/RfnhZGc2uj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtomase @SVcallahan22 You owe us a brew dude ! Putting up with your narratives can be challenging!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wild crime spree ends after a man ditches a stolen vehicle for a bus ride, leaving a huge mess and injuring a Tua… https://t.co/DA8XPKg9Kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @BreitbartNews Maybe he can get more money from his father-in-Law to continue running around compl… https://t.co/LWlao5OM2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just another of tRump’s Criminal buddies. How long before his scandals break?  #PornStarPayment  Y… https://t.co/yypCZk0t3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BramletteEileen Oh you mean like almost everyone who goes on this show? Including Colton?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeanHeadAFC @DDayCobra Yeah, that's the under privileged girls that the GoFundMe paid for them to be there and see… https://t.co/0UXbgF7SkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeunderdog55 @intheknot @chrisramsay52 Michael, the difference in though between you and us is that we don't thi… https://t.co/S7L5gAZwDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrecursive No - I see it in there. It’s fun to try and screenshot it because as I zoom in to crop, the high freque… https://t.co/sX1MI6Eg0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday alices_wonders. You can’t possibly be 14 😱😱😱I love you!!#hueyfamilyphotography #hueyfamily @ Cary, N… https://t.co/7uxsdX2oJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@candyinabowl @vancemeek @joshearsley Crazy super nerd libs? Steal that from Donnie’s drafts? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst part of writing is those moments when you have to actually read over it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um dia memorável 😍🏃 #pennrelays2016 #4x400 @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/fyrrORkzVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessir!! Just ordered @BigEmoney87 and I the Pinstripe @Bharper3407 Jersey! Let’s go @Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[The list gets longer. Avoid the following: Youth pastors Scout Masters Lake City anything Downtown Jax Neighborhood basketball games]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianzelizer @CPAC Does the Right know how to operate a mirror...without instructions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of both worlds. @wendys x girlscouts #TagalongFrosty 🍦🍪🔥 #ThankMeLater - @jennbinspr kandelm clairemalia chipy… https://t.co/F89boAZXSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will never understand the randos who crawl out of the woodwork to defend billionaires. What do you gain? They dont… https://t.co/vbEJpVa7bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @TheLastWord @MSNBC He’s very impressive although I would not vote for him because he’s a Republican]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmelgar09 @TPPF I’ll allow some others to chime in to provide data to support the claim that government contribute… https://t.co/tU9FzjhfO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Valentine's dinner last night:  A. Pride hurt because wife won't eat 1/4 of her filet because it's too rare;… https://t.co/PPaSglMBnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @SebGorka On what planet? Ever notice it’s never liberals that come up with these wild conspiracy theo… https://t.co/qPnYSS33Hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dale84June *i smile and gently take your hand softly kissing it giving you a loving wink* first time encountering a human Miss?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colbert: Steelers won’t trade Brown unless they get the right deal - https://t.co/V7AcQIR7Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorkoutNirvana Yes, I’ll be seeing It tomorrow, Saturday and Sunday in 3D. Can’t wait to hear what you and Lil Nir… https://t.co/tAYRhQXhdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexBorstein @RachelBros Stupid question here, but were those supposed to be bug bites that Susie got on her face… https://t.co/Ne7odIA6fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deesnider I wish you would do another horror radio show like the Fangoria radio show. It was the best. (@SIRIUSXM… https://t.co/647KhNQLn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbowe84 @Buster_ESPN He does not wanna win lmao. He entertained the Giants and Padres. If he wanted to win he woul… https://t.co/Df0wDtsolh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSzoke @CrankageGames Oh yeah! The Brewers, Cards, and Cubs will be in a massiv dogfight for first. The Reds an… https://t.co/SWBFz0QNqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPScott19 @DrawPlayDave @eomrules That same game, Frank Gore 11 carries 14 yards. Kap 11 carries 130 yards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want your vote! #Yas or #Meh on Feiendly’s All New Cake! Let us know in the comments which one is your favorite!… https://t.co/0PHzil1yuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani Notice how White Evangelical @OhioGOP @Jim_Jordan GRATUITOUSLY INCLUDED AN ANTISEMITIC JEWISH SLUR IN… https://t.co/gaLzj8aTDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rocionahle @SENER_mx Cuando se presentará el nuevo proyecto de energías renovables ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Papa John founder Schnatter to exit board in settlement https://t.co/Upa7kNLSbJ via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalKathy @PrisonPlanet Oh look, this snake is back. Crawl back under your rock, Kathy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Potential To3 w/ @Pureless_x and @CrackHeadGio for Fort Worth   Teampass ✅  We need a Main ICR and Main Saug   Have… https://t.co/T1RAoD3rzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeltaLife22 @RE_Games Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/NLDXFMrz0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gupta_MD @SidakpalP @ReddyTheRobot @moiz_hafiz @DrArgyle @aelsab @kashishgoelmd @EleidMack @rajivxgulati… https://t.co/RCCZUD99Qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealroseanne @ReelMFishman a Video Reflection Letter you both need to see..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidwebbshow here’s a good one David. #idiAOCy https://t.co/IMcGDaW6Gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAPD vino hoy a @cartasmesatv Atentos a nuevos episodios desde Los Ángeles pronto por actualidadrt #losangeles… https://t.co/HNi8KNZSCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t rip KState folk if I didn’t like ya. Live up your Big 12 Championship!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god @JasonWitten is going back to the @dallascowboys and out of the MNF booth. Hopefully @espn gets rid of @ESPNBooger to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLAurora63 Why during Obama administration did you never have a budget? Isn't that against  the Constitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtpm 47 months - 9 months served - 15% benefit for good behaviour = 32 months remaining]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of the day! You can tell he’s watched me cut a few trees down.. Got some pretty decent form already at 2.5yrs… https://t.co/GDT7yPzipP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I waffle a lot — this is one of my favorite Chrises. https://t.co/PoeO5Ny6MD]]></document><document><![CDATA[13.1 miles done.....13,000 calories to consume! 41st Half Marathon complete!🏅 https://t.co/vRUgJabdV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RepostPlus @luminouscitysd - - - - - - 🎉🎉MARCH 2nd | 3-7pm @quartyardsd • Come celebrate the up coming grand openi… https://t.co/r13Ald5Nrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuySuFrida El Pasado 1° de Dic. el presidente aseguró que el Ejecutivo dejará de ser 'el poder de los poderes'; ga… https://t.co/ov8bQhpLby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canalway Partners invites you to The Towpath Tappening on Friday, March 15th from 5-10pm at Forest City Brewery. We… https://t.co/808y0GoLv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thejessicakorda late nights w nelly. I have a friend who is watching. Go Bradenton! Can’t wait till ur back]]></document><document><![CDATA[We do not exist in, any other instant, here in this dimension, you and I are meant to be 🎧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanWolken 10 here in MI in summer. Golfers rejoice! Once got 63 holes in in a day. Spring us forward I say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron is now in the top 10 all time in points AND assists. Only player in NBA history to achieve that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dominik04187978 @PureSportsTX So proud of you CJ!  Keep chopping wood!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGS_Capital @bopinion "There are none so blind as those that will not see"]]></document><document><![CDATA[6_living_6dead_girl_6 friday 3/8 at gothnightatcityclub it’s ST. PRACTICE DAY specials on Irish whiskey on beer ! o… https://t.co/Tu58aF9cNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Shaved Biggie . A few photos back I posted another photo of this Biggie mural where it had a mess’a wires going a… https://t.co/471S1avyj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campbellsoupco should allow The Lit Man to be the next spokesman for Chunky Soup.  I'm a fit. I'd be good.   Let's… https://t.co/HvR437FyvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyCarlsonShow Would you rather be nibbled to death by ducks or stomped to death by gerbils?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dusirt @SierraWhiskey9 It wasn't out of spite.  I'm a father.  I'm outraged by their stupid waste of money, when i… https://t.co/wbePlmdtxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisBeEdgar @ShawnLaVie @Complex @Bucks Lol bro, of course I’ve seen Friday!Just never seen that gif before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are at Mar a Largo! !!! But there   is an emergency  déclaration , you should  be at WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad (Chara) is angry again, haha he was just barking at Yanni Gourde who is exactly a foot shorter than him (5-foot… https://t.co/XQuZbO2bnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[And tell that worthless one that he is not welcome, and his service is not wanted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cougsky @TheoLawson_SR Will bench at Pro Day, I heard.  Strained shoulder.  I wonder if that affected his 40 time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to have a kid ! Tired of getting back 100$ back on my tax return 😪😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy REAL Washington’s Birthday!  Our first President was born 287 years ago today on February 22, 1732.… https://t.co/cjS8BFJc29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateDems To the Senators running for President, that voted against helping babies. Give it up, you people will l… https://t.co/TwQC2bllKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy Adam Raised a Kahnle better pull it together soon...We could use this guy at his best...]]></document><document><![CDATA[top 7:  Constantine is relieved by McAllen Rowe alum Ryan Jackson. Big ovation for Constantine for his efforts to h… https://t.co/ZnEalcQvXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubanitoenCuba @juanes Ustedes hablan de países en Latinoamérica, olvidando lo que@sucede en Cuba por los últimos… https://t.co/Bd8BWSNQdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBridenstine @ulalaunch @POTUS @NASA Only works if Dear Orange Leader can put his name in 50 mile high gold lett… https://t.co/jdMNuLAUqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realkareemdream @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Hahahahaa! So blind to the racism. You are all being playe… https://t.co/ZFG6iHJNSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[One quarter in the books here at #PittHigh and @DragonActivity is on 🔥🔥 🔥. Dragons lead @KCKStallions 19-4. #SubStateChampionshp   @kshsaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baltimore officers planted gun on man after deliberately running him over, indictment says https://t.co/7WxIpdFkXW via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s done at 1:15, he’s done with the prepped speech.   But then he’s all like, “You know what, actually, I’m not d… https://t.co/6JPvrev1M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlreiner We have been very lucky and thanks God that this immature has not gotten America war conflict!!! https://t.co/SQkv9Cen7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RatLeagueXtreme @PNWHoneyBadger @RefAubrey @ImThatTylerGuy @thedevildrexl @rockinrickyg @drkliever @Ravenousrandy… https://t.co/Mzxnt3gMaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[They need an undercover https://t.co/g0y1JyEgyq hard can it be to find a coven in NYC?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessica_dills What will happen if this wall were to go away?  Just be sure in your faith in the almighty that no m… https://t.co/c3wPaf0Gzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Contagious Jerrold Nadler, a known Democrat carrier of political venereal disease.]]></document><document><![CDATA[is #ctscantuesday a thing yet? @ University of Tennessee Cancer Institute https://t.co/XHgSpfETs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dinkydudd Ya I remember. One of the funniest. He couldn’t lose if he bet like $1 but he moved all in right?  Classic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another must-read from the great @BillPlaschke. Now, if I can just stop crying in the break room at work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinSolidus THAT FUCKING TURN AFTER THE MONEY FLIP https://t.co/E9eVj0kAmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MY_BORDERCOLLIE @Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @EMluvsPibbles @msmorgan1968 @ChaliceGarden… https://t.co/ysnaYPw6gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a fan of Tyson Fury interviews. #boxing  #ReturnoftheMack #Gypsyking]]></document></documents></author>