<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of Sunday is when I lay on the couch and it’s real quiet and Corey, aiden, and I watch grace and Frankie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my sparkly glasses fixed 🤓🤓🤓 @ Kaiser Permanente https://t.co/LAz1VJWEIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton That’s so sweet good job your family is amazing such big hearts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@errrcaxo Haha! I actually just read two articles about the Cambridge Analytica scandal! This is why Facebook is be… https://t.co/VVeeHsyOyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[impromptu @Dickeys #rootbeerfloat snack with my second sweetie! #timmy2019 #boymom❤️💙💙 #cityofcoppell… https://t.co/zptOfAMFGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish it could stay this green forever 😍 @ Hwy 46 Overlook https://t.co/3WEtEbUw78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got my chipotle comped because I was wearing my @discordapp hoodie 👀 wut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heARTISTatWORK @Bill_Huber_ @ChristineBemis2 @DrCaliGrit @LindaEdwardsi @MaireCervenak @MelissaRathmann @mafost… https://t.co/ZwtbxILeZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[NCW BABY is a local maker of these super cute BABY ONESIES and TODDLER TEES with a North Central Washington agricul… https://t.co/9pSP4GGUsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[EdCampSTNY is fast approaching! Come join us for a fun, engaging and learning filled day!! (Did I mention we have g… https://t.co/mQ2fHoGX1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC you did an excellent job yesterday!! So many of those Republicans make fun of you.. But you go girl you got th… https://t.co/1DMRaR6atQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW THIS is a viral trend i can get behind. couldn’t choose which fit i love more @rihanna https://t.co/a0c2HbmNAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[More of this! #InternationalWomansDay #girlpower #DoGood  https://t.co/CYrEq121EM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going a week without talking to the nigga you used to talk to everyday is hard as hell 😩🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimeVanderG @BreneBrown @brenebrownteam Sounds good!  Let me know when you finish and we can debrief.  We drove t… https://t.co/g66dUnzAal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madison and I are staying in tonight and I’m so happy to just watch netflix 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Country is in a crisis! We can’t sustain this anymore. All Republicans need to support BORDER SECURITY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I'm minding my own business messing around out there! Somebody needs to get in business and remind me of this… https://t.co/BBFl6BkAKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josytheriveter Glad you did! Thanks for coming to hear my take on #rehearse4realtime]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amooo el #downgrade kk como@dice @flandivar iban x todo y terminan aplaudiendo a #zas a zassss atrasan medio siglo… https://t.co/KZqQEOFKCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALSO THE WOMAN I WORK WITH IS A MIND READER AND IM SO EMBARRASSED🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree! I am not against border security or even a wall in places, but diverting money from our military and victims… https://t.co/nKYeRVyL2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[If an unpopular opinion tweet goes viral, does that still make it an unpopular opinion? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a lovely fun night celebrating Sara and Jonathan.  Much love and congratulations to this beautiful couple. @ C… https://t.co/rSE85g6gFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love being around my parents, if i go to grad school out of Texas idk how I’m gonna do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[God better have some real good shit coming my way because imagine losing your family &amp; your partner in the same week hahahahahaha fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think a vacation is very much in order. Come back healthy and refreshed and up another solid rotation player in Keef! #ThunderUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexlancaster_ Little humans are seriously the greatest gift to work with every day 💜 Peds life is the best life… https://t.co/hGXsLxnlZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw Phylicia Rashad walking into the happy hour I’m about to attend at #SXSW nbd 😩 https://t.co/MH1kJnZPJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF GRAMMY AWARD WINNING STARS CAN CREDIT THEIR PHOTOGRAPHERS YOU 👏🏼 CAN 👏🏼 TOO 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganRobertson @marybschneider True. Sometimes I forget how long things take — especially when the arguments are so inane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@publiceyestl @UffdaJen @chryssi @Schweitzer88 She was really pushing the lip balm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDrPhilShow @john_walsh @CallahanWalsh @DiscoveryID Love John Walsh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardLeeCres1 @NYPD34Pct @NYPDnews @ChicagosFines19 @NYPDCommAffairs @NYPDChiefofDept @NYPDONeill @NYPDnoticias… https://t.co/7YC9qh3Hfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to go to sleep, but I’ve stood outside Ronnie’s door every night so I can walk in and wish him happy birthda… https://t.co/inkzQVfxPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @TracyPereira20 @jillianne_gray @Fiery01Red @TheSavvyChef1 @Julianna_glass @DivaVinophile @CorksConcierge… https://t.co/b8qWdnbXiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[𝒞𝒽𝑒𝓈𝓉𝓃𝓊𝓉 𝐵𝓇𝑜𝓌𝓃 🌰   • • • • • #foilyage #licensedtocreate #balayage #redkenshadeseq #redken #redkenobbsessed… https://t.co/OisEi69hWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eandb1122 Thank you so much! I’m having a fabulous weekend! How have you been?]]></document><document><![CDATA[River Place Canyon hike this morning with @lakeaustinspa #bethtbday #niftyfifty #girlsspaweekend #lakeaustinspa https://t.co/MnuQ4TtwXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HausOfEse @streetnoodle @kellycloonan @catiepetunia @MaddowBlog Look ma. I larned how to close my brella.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjoseph7777 @dscc @dccc @realDonaldTrump These are the real enemy of the people and the country, lock 🔐 them up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustKristi It’s all about expectations... many people don’t truly set the right expectations... or have an awarene… https://t.co/LDQK4Q89cV]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PequeaElem having some #minutetowinit fun at the February House Assembly! https://t.co/VYwg5O5Fho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hosting the show tonight! Come see me and the rest of our fabulous lineup at @AVLOdditorium tonight for risquem… https://t.co/ytQRnceug4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extrañandote sinceramente.. asta la cima del cielo Paco❤😢 https://t.co/7QtJSEvoTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah... i’ve been in standstill traffic for 15 mins on 43 because the road is so bad, cars can’t get up the hill bu… https://t.co/AK60C3gSbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WednesdaysAreForCakeToo #WednesdayFebruary27th2019 #FoxRacing #Happy15thBirthday #sassycakeladyamy @ Modesto, Cali… https://t.co/zjDIfU6WtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now Rome’s thinking about having kids. He wants kids and Regina doesn’t. I feel this struggle. #AMillionLittleThings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrisMathew1 @politico Well if you don’t believe in climate change why are you applauding that? And please don’t no… https://t.co/LbwYyAmqp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really made a Facebook account just so I can watch Jordyn’s Red Table Talk tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went for an interview for my 2nd job &amp; she was like “you know you won’t have a day off” I was like “that’s the point”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump You claim to be a man of God yet you call people, GOD'S CHILDREN who cross our bor… https://t.co/2zRFnQRNtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy DST I missed you! #redsky    @MichaelPageWx @NBC10Boston @MattNBCBoston @StormHour @DeniseNBCBoston #seacoast… https://t.co/m9Um397CHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Princess of Wales Theatre https://t.co/25hror9qRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time of year that I never get my suit case fully unpacked before I’m packing it again to head off to the next place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen I saw this video and heard 'freedom' by Beyonce running in my head!!!  Hahahah!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two hearts that beat as one is more accurate when talking about a mom and her child in her tummy than of lovers, partners or spouses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is always on the alert, constantly on the lookout for people who are totally committed to him. Chronicles 16:9 https://t.co/1Ur0WlsevQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[[...] Il n’a jamais vécu ce qu’on a traversé. Jamais qu’il n’aurait le courage de se mettre dans nos peaux. Dire de… https://t.co/Czo9h9b9QN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielal5697 @poshboy221b Did you guys climb to the top of the dome? I was too much of a hight-baby to do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Sacramento International Airport https://t.co/cRJLc0V0dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cuphaed Not for two years they aren’t. Not even the characters.  https://t.co/C3raEomsWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 AM Meditation Becomes 2 AM Motivation.  Under The Super Snow Full Moon Sweat Meditation Workout 🕉… https://t.co/fDXZ9lm0v8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHandelman I bet you could do it..I’d need it to be warmer..but ur young 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper missed a rare followup with Pompeo. P said "trump didn't say there was no risk, he said there was a sig… https://t.co/xHSD41JMiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Global Scholars makes a great presence at Broward Water Matters Day! They said, “ATTUCKS had a lot of students here… https://t.co/ThCpWlu5H0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote this down!  @SteveScalise @GOP @senatemajldr @Jim_Jordan @DanCrenshawTX @RepMattGaetz  please stop this nonsen… https://t.co/deJKQq4ogT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This backroom where Jim confesses his inner feelings to the tv production crew is like the closest so many dudes ha… https://t.co/mKj5sBdbcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoubleAUB @WrestlingInc That was the first thing that popped into my head!😆😆😆😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milfhosh @netflix Omg. I can only imagine what my face looks like. The hell is going on here???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the United States and I’m more stressed out than I left, UGHHHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAFilmFestival #directorscloseup up. Beyond amazing @bandrybarry boburnham tamara._jenkins @bootsriley… https://t.co/zsbdBeKfJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida Anise is found in the panhandle (https://t.co/OS2mU5RUzP) but FNPS President @suscarr2 and member Mark Whit… https://t.co/8PqVGvivp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edtechjay Just signed up for your seminar with CITE on 3/26! Look forward to learning about the intersection between #edtech and leadership]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like now that I’m less stressed I can put my energy into self care like going to the gym or eating better????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinaANDMaya An Amazingly Beautiful Friendship of Love and Graditude  To give Love, He gave Life, When Life would o… https://t.co/ZR399ZaI3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalm 149:3 KJV [3] Let them praise his name in the dance: let them sing praises unto him with the timbrel and harp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamscicomm @SerpenIllus @TownsendAnnette @ThreeTailArt @BasiliskosArt @laurelmundyillo @koalafruit @PhDoodles… https://t.co/fM5PnSyqIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThoughtsOfRally @WillietheBT Me too! Half wet half dry with a handful of veggies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckeyeCuti @Lori1080 @LobsterBFFs1 @birdtracs @Katie_Elaine012 @lizheileman @tnormandeau22 @24loves75… https://t.co/6VBfASVIeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraSmithFox Can't wait to hear your spin on your buddy @TuckerCarlson . Do you support misogyny? Read the… https://t.co/x5o6OGmg2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just felt something wet touch my back.... it was my dogs nose. I forget I sleep with him sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALT_uscis @FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids Shelter and clean beds yep potus can walk and chew gum as can his wife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet I would never buy a pillow off of this crazy man even if it were the best pillow in the world and guaran… https://t.co/bfbsPX75HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyBringingHope I should also state Civic Works is at 4pm and is televised and available to watch after the fact.… https://t.co/J0P8qRracc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer Congress worked against President Obama from start to finish! You idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics @realDonaldTrump   Look in the mirror.  THAT is the disaster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queersian I’ll always do what I can for y’all 💜 https://t.co/eqOmo8CQfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficeOfSkip @adoannie Sadly I’ve been blocked by The Skipper. Please let them know how they’re doing at the satir… https://t.co/BdKe7r9o7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get your order in the mail on the way to your car appointment, you rip it open ASAP and get your flawless… https://t.co/94DyPhRIFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[News studio digs at @c3lab_charlotte . ❤️🎨🖋✏️ #sharondowellart #sharondowell #c3lab #studio #artstudio… https://t.co/SP9fmGrA04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kickerbee “Come on in guys!” “If we’ve learned anything from this tribal council it’s that...” “Ain’t nobody playi… https://t.co/ingBjqKZdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of Carmen and the other Quiz Bowl Team members . https://t.co/TO1JUYrQTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are followers so whatever Trump spews they lap up-no thinking is needed. A true cult following.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nose/sinuses are so swollen and sore I can't breathe while I'm eating. Maybe a hot rum toddy would go down bette… https://t.co/uUDJoFCVLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por que me haces esto sodexoooo!!! Ya no me acordaba de él y tu diciendome que le llame 😢 @SodexoMx https://t.co/0XduufUo7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#365diasdegratitud #Dia46 hoy agradezco los paisajes de LA, la oportunidad de ver boxing en vivo y las cenas con amigos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today a chaotic day was turned constructive by embracing the importance of the day to middle schoolers. We did a Va… https://t.co/vQvtjfrJ0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Stay the fuck out of my state, California.  You are not welcome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thankful for the people I have found 🖤 #nonewfriends @ Leaky Lifeboat Inn https://t.co/JFod94rvMf]]></document></documents></author>