<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JulieSchlebusch, thank you for following me. I am looking forward to learning with you. #Synergy #PLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rem143A @brianhprobert @chad0525 @washingtonpost @yorkshire_dales https://t.co/P9X9F7sWAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[gif of the night is gonna go to @lisarinna w that “to the table” handclap! lol queen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alisand3 Thought you might want to know that you’re on this list: https://t.co/5EW2Fm24F4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little Monday dinner with these two. #MondayDown @ J Peters https://t.co/DBTEPiy0V3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteWheatTweet @KMMcCammack Gotta be honest at first I though that tweet said toast. This all makes more sense now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExOnTheBeach2 Maya and her zombie eyebrows needs to shut the fuck up and get off the show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great morning with the incredible #RoboPandas of @PS94DavidPorter and their "Into Orbit" presentation. I wish them… https://t.co/muJwUcaRm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The "Johnny Cash Eating Cake High in a Bush" photo, is the best photo available on Earth IMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERobinson I was waiting to you to start dancing with Truth and @CarmellaWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaceyEvansWWE It’s pretty sweet you’re hanging out when Clyde Drexler and Hakeem Olajuwon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No wonder NYC couldn’t land Amazon, they are too busy with mindless policies and ordinances .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday @jetrotter For those who said yes, why??? What did he accomplish? If you plan on answering with a refere… https://t.co/s9sYW0xKuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TvilleNole @gonzowins Yes. Buy a PS4 for the Show. Absolutely worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEWALTtough even though she look CHONKY, she's been through hell and has me a DeWalt customer for life. Many great… https://t.co/cR0dNKkRL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get sucked into convos you know you should avoid but cross the event horizon anyway.. https://t.co/KdwPuTjFuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interludes and Outros betters than the actual records. Anyone else have any other favorites? https://t.co/0cq6moWzrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in the Coast Guard has made me a master at “holding it” and waking up the middle of the night to be awake for… https://t.co/qE3bXBT4hK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our president just used “Sorry Haters” in a tweet god bless https://t.co/m7UCc6hY1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunnelFiasco @nsj Yes, please! More sunlight all day would be awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 I think a lot is doing this already😂😂 Dat iz all @ Sioux City, Iowa https://t.co/ifvSl0FvGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cranberry juice 🥤 There’s a lot of benefits. It includes improving our Cardiovascular health. I know some of us are… https://t.co/cI5himYSc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glenn__Kenny @joe_dante @TrailersFromHel @charliehillart6 @ArrowFilmsVideo Maybe it's not as bad as meeting people on Tinder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #PurpleMante sporting new shoes #lamborghini #lambo #huracan #huracanperformante #amazingcars247 #pghcnc #pias… https://t.co/VZBy80RDOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever laugh at the people from Hamilton who act like they’re from Toronto, just know there’s a man from North… https://t.co/3rh0cGOU5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 805 Blonde by @FirestoneWalker @ Pour House Bar And Grill — https://t.co/WC8weFe6Jg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada que digo que quiero comer más sano vale queso :c hoy me comí una hamburguesa y media, 1 litro de jugo, unas sa… https://t.co/lKL7AkVsoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i share my location with you then we 110% have some great memories together]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing job by our 4x800 team last night, running a time of 10.57.44 with really solid leadership from Triniti Spur… https://t.co/T2B7hZ8J6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gonna say this once: all y’all that were outraged early about Jussie Smollett need to be even more outraged no… https://t.co/pcQeINTNdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look at the White Sox and Phillies if Harper signs with the Dodgers https://t.co/pcHb6kqxHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a blast to catch up with college buddy Keith Free today. @ Fruitland Park, Florida https://t.co/PRI3yKNmcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBCSN going with the “tell don’t show” approach on that replay of Kane’s not-goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how I got here but I was thinking about Mewtwo and how he’s way more interesting than every other Pokémon and t… https://t.co/UHmJpmMrIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JbrownESPNKY Owensboro wins 3rd Region Crown with a 63-57 OT victory over Breckinridge Co.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Is Said to Have Tortured an #American Citizen - The New York Times https://t.co/MvcJtdpeQw by @kirkpatricknyt via @nuzzel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait until he discovers Imagine Dragons @jefflangan. Also, he’s representing Illinois.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I, the Lord , search all hearts and examine secret motives. I give all people their due rewar…… https://t.co/fiO57Y9MW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[tomorrow starts 8-10 work days. 14 hours. i should be hella asleep what's wrong with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudasCane @amahnke So after your previous arguments get rejected by basic economics, you resort to a misguided vie… https://t.co/qEamvpYgRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadVictor3 @EricTrump If they’re substantiated then say it in front of congress like he is and try him on perjury… https://t.co/y1aFuhJ3q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cxltmatic @Jaywop6 @D0MXNXQUE Shit the first bar of the whole tape fucked me up when I went back to listen. It jus… https://t.co/z1W1xx0mGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisCharminManc @kthalps Or they don't care, because those policies will protect them against the Poors; they feel… https://t.co/e40Sn3vpfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX Good work keep helping be a Statesman and thank you for your service my family goes back to the Alam… https://t.co/HN0UcGELHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICHINOSE_CRASH You ladies are looking fabulous after a well played gig😊💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report of 5-6 teenagers in Yukon "busting beer bottles in the street, yelling at passing cars." At least they aren'… https://t.co/XMaTeroVa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluRadioCo @IvanDuque Desempleo, Inseguridad, Líderes sociales asesinados, más impuestos, un fiscal corrupto, Bogo… https://t.co/jyV5qL6Ypu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePostman68 Good race but lets see what the rest of the tracks offer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[74 years yesterday! - "FLAG OF OUR FATHERS" #iwojima #1pilgrimstudio #americanflag https://t.co/rOvkQMvJPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eb peace reduced to one lane til 6 am for construction in #DowntownRaleigh on Peace St at Capital Blvd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A back and forth first half between Keenan and Bishop-England. 17-15 lead with 3:59 left in the first half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be like this guy. Be like Bob. Bob doesn’t cut over grassy area as to avoid being stuck in traffic during win… https://t.co/XUPMscm8b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think they just used the phrase "next week is hometowns" 6 times in 2 minutes. A record. I'm already annoyed. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSOPIO @Twit_for_Droid @NationalSheriff @BlueWalkPoconos @PolicingNews @NatPoliceAssoc @GoodNewsCops… https://t.co/iXepVRAGwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougGorman1 @kyle_patton @ChrisFisher247 I’m real, 558 points in 12 1/2 games. I don’t think anyone else did that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: I’d pay more for madden if that meant they developed gameplay better when they came out and they… https://t.co/2medma5MIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahencyclopedia Is that for wind coming from the west or blowing in a westward direction?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @KateUpton @ashleygraham @HatchingChange @PatriciaHeaton 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcybelle424 @CynicXyz @silael1 @AbdulElSayed Apparently reading comprehension is difficult for you because that… https://t.co/VUBeK1xYUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachclark My favourite leaders to follow: Bold and humble.  Thanks for a great learning experience! @RENEWANATION… https://t.co/95xuot7Mxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrotTop1023 OK, I will stay warm, and you stay warm too because you will need to when it gets that cold where you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallCoyne But, he can really run. PS- I hope your kids get his height!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scheftic @MiaFarrow @realDonaldTrump @MattGertz Lmfao. Cute meme. Not at all true but cute. https://t.co/oU6XAzvFLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't want to be alone the 1st night in my new place feat. Ms. Vivi Vex ------------------- Helping a friend mo… https://t.co/UIiJlhmKB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class Act. I feel there aren’t many left in professional sports (especially the @NBA) anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hacks4pancakes @clappymonkey @etjossem What context is there... beyond the thread itself? If I say "fuck you black… https://t.co/JqhnQmN6gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadeABC 🕊️🌹🕊️Praise God thank you Jesus Christ for another wonderful awesome glorious day good morning my Super Qu… https://t.co/f6hvlkSncb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoKhaLatte I just hate people who don't respond like they are celebrities or something, I always unfollow people l… https://t.co/ZSrRHo8EEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make that 2 in a row for @KyleBusch at @ISMRaceway!  #NASCAR #WeekendSweep]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Seekonk a Save A Pet auction is fast approaching!  https://t.co/uxc6OrY22Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riiickymatthews Damn. I hope he doesn't sing "I wanna fuck a dog in the ass" to her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewBledsoe watching sports center and seeing the combine from over the years...nothing like seeing a young Bledso… https://t.co/pZdTMiJgMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cluadiacano Es por proteccion civil.... Para salir debe ser empujar....por las emergencias]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_Traina the end of the podcast cut out for me this morning 🙁 ended as you were discussing what you’d seen… https://t.co/FapiaBcBVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you do to pass the time until the @CUNA fb live keynote by @Nussle at GAC?  Review the @CityofWaukee  Compr… https://t.co/S5FVMu2aIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN VACCINE CRUSADER BILL GATES CONTRADICTS HIMSELF Says Vaccines Save Lives AND Reduce Population!… https://t.co/Wovd83rMDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Esquire lost the Bryan Singer story https://t.co/KPhnVHiDBL via @cjr This happens more than people realize.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 27 - MSNBC Daily:      Cohen on upcoming testimony: I look forward to telling 'the American peop… https://t.co/plGRzKbETs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llego Mr Swag ... dilo!!  You better watch and learn!!   #miami3050 #superheros #newmiamisound #miami #wynwood #art… https://t.co/n6fSvMa7pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JalenElrod My argument is not that fixing class problems fix racism. My argument is that if you racism disappeared… https://t.co/3Z0PhSPtNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Twinhaven Reception Hall in Twinsburg, OH https://t.co/icsWtQaPTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SouthwestAir ever think about hiring more mechanics rather than sue their union. Oh I guess you value those at… https://t.co/Y9zms63w7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeRaaaw01 What about guys who know nothing about mechanics.. construction.. plumbing.. electrical.. you know, man things?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asulawdean #DeanKaraoke could get you there. Sing only songs about the law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @1010XL for your support of @UNFOspreys! Swoop! @Frank_Frangie @1010XLLauren @HaysCarlyon https://t.co/b6pKLycoGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tampering time for NFL free agency means it’s time for me to add “#Colts + LeVeon Bell” tweets to my mute list]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckBell4 How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/URCt9OBsKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMAStormChasers @ChasersGM   Ya’ll still accepting these?  (and did they mature with age?) https://t.co/hGcRtAeaXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is amazing how I've not fallen asleep during this snooze fest. Made up my own Anti Kyle Larson song as a parody… https://t.co/xnfAncBcSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GFJE4Animals @SethAbramson And “the media” covers a lot of ground. The Washington Post has just obliterated Trump,… https://t.co/vXoOIOs0pP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DcRisingforsure Nobody is worth that much so let him go if philly is that stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ONE OF THE HIGHLIGHTS OF WORKING WITH BRAD PAISLEY was getting to know his dad, Doug Paisley, who was out on tour… https://t.co/E0g1J46Tgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll never understand Baptists that think that the KJV is more correct than the original Greek and Hebrew texts. A… https://t.co/vVeNVWbWQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MynxMisha I’m a big fan of urs baby from Toronto Canada love everything about u😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larakate That little smile Gaga gives Cooper is everything. Find yourself someone who looks at you like you’re the… https://t.co/ZJhxkBQeqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever skull fuck a Mexican Airline...do this for my buddy that's stuck in the motherland please   @BarstoolBigCat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marytaylorfrye Was that the time he was getting on Airforce One, and couldn’t figure out how to close his umbrella… https://t.co/YWk0OvHORy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump I think he will be hanging out with #FakeMelania. She seems to like him much more than real Melania.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biden’s playing hard to get. The reluctant hero. Except it feels like he’s just playing the part and fully intends to run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen some “outside the box” press release but this one for @Meghan_Trainor us absolutely the craziest I’ve seen https://t.co/poksPFA4Fd]]></document></documents></author>