<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AOC 👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻👆🏻 What happens when you put a son of the president, an evangelical leader, and a mistre… https://t.co/TlUonswxRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhonda_A_2011 @rocketmanmovie We saw the previews when we saw Bohemian Rhapsody. I am very much looking forward to… https://t.co/Jj8WGmqZ8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicvega422 @mmpadellan Seems like these kids know a hell of a lot more than these dumbass politicians. #Kidsrule]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Victory at Sea by @BallastPoint @ BB's Pub N Grill — https://t.co/j82whOEV0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re rolling right along with Safe Spring Break week here at SFPD!  Today you can catch us at the SF Perry Center… https://t.co/7CnWg5Nhhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF #DatelineFriday #InternationalWomensDay @SdBWorking @patterport @kimt205 @Browneyes_2060 @BonnieDee3 @skijoey… https://t.co/ylX0B00SYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump You are not a smart https://t.co/2Ng5O6k6Lf your eyes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[dm if you’re interested in getting my private snapchat 😇 i’m very flexible with pricing lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us come together during these divisive times and defeat the real enemy of us all: Fluorescent Lighting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wykkd Exactly, I seriously freeze up totally and freak out if I get sticky ; ever since I was a kid and I have no idea why .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2ChillFor_theBS LeBron already has a show in this format that comes on HBO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #dreamteam at #QualtricsX4 for dry cleaning my jacket that was covered in coffee. Now that is what I call… https://t.co/gi2ySN7G4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why, in God's name, is the President signing Bibles?  He a politician, at best. You're letting a politician put his… https://t.co/ea6vxiZSck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isnt it funny that Dem. Liberal media is losing viewers CNN MSNBC and helping the Dems implode because of the SPIN… https://t.co/pJm9FrjVVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doodleattack Frustrates me too. We should be praising her for not wasting money on hearings. Do I want to see him… https://t.co/TPdjbrUtVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebJHull Sounds like you are talking about Ttump. AOC is willing to learn. Trump thinks he knows it all and want… https://t.co/04OkQv0gYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelly2161 @hshaban I admit I don't know very much about this subject. Just my experience that whenever private in… https://t.co/DHbkFwJ54x]]></document><document><![CDATA[This music makes me dream of being on my Harley!!! Good tunes and the wind in my hair with my Moto friends!! Harley… https://t.co/9jwQrVuMgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Won’t you be my honey bee 🐝 Giving sweet kisses all the time? Be mine, be mine, Valentine.” ♥️ @ Carrabba's Italia… https://t.co/qJ0NfXDEYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorrachaelme @nbcdays I told agree with you. I don't want Eric with Sarah either. I'm just not feeling it. I'm… https://t.co/ZDPkfw6VGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[found a cafe celebrating yoongi’s bday &amp; a girl gave me and @elena_yip little photo packs uwu 💕 https://t.co/PZ4ERXW74b]]></document><document><![CDATA[:Chuckles in Latin: #rideo   #bacchusandariadne #reni #lacma https://t.co/q4mDWeohdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy rico !!! 😋 @ La Asuncion Oaxacan Restaurant https://t.co/umORjqK8X7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FunFact On the pre-event soundtrack, Sympathy for the Devil has repeatedly played ... three times so far ....  @RollingStones @WPLGLocal10]]></document><document><![CDATA[so tomorrow i have to wake up at 4:30... ask me if i’m dying. #clinicals]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a very long day of school and work, my day ended me with hitting/killing  a deer 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your doing a great job. I love ya 💛💚💛💚💛Happy Valentines Day! Sr.♥️💚💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YareliVIAN @brendagmartell @germaniaco1 @WatoPatson ya te pusiste chingona!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamrodneysmith You deserve a day off. Do something for you today. Enjoy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the love of education @jones_flora @Hobsons @kmoppelt —- is the perfect landing spot (always) https://t.co/0PQcjryenD]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 is gonna be an interesting year. That’s for sure. I’m both excited and scared lol. Let’s do this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hemultiplyus @shaunacoralee James 4:12. Read it. If you need more info, let me know. It clearly says "Who are you… https://t.co/u9nLYLcbdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round two of our #BeaverdamBookBattle finds @TomiDepaola’s  Strega Nona moving into our Elite Eight. https://t.co/lGp2g3g9RF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheezburger A lot of ppl need to look in the mirror before going out anywhere. What you may think is sexy isn't al… https://t.co/TA7JnunVf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @DonaldJTrumpJr "Entirely debunked"?  Have you never heard of circumstantial evidence?  Ask any judge or… https://t.co/p2UVa7tSCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[No water on my street or the streets around us for several hours. No ETA as to when it will be restored. We went to… https://t.co/ZpxThYyiCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth  #pamkennedyfitness #runnermama #fitandover50 https://t.co/Mll6rPSNrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOWZA  loved that Julexis scene today, but I just KNEW it would turn out to be a dream....it didn't ring true with… https://t.co/APGXqnx3A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly can’t even remember the last time i was even remotely interested in the women’s division, at least on ra… https://t.co/3D1poUuMiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arranged my schedule today to go to Zumba bc I finally found an instructor I like...and there was a sub...who was n… https://t.co/If5uQl4EIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashtonpittman His no vote on the ACA is costing people $30,000 a year in Pennsylvania if you make over $66,000 as… https://t.co/RTELoM68mR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaSaidBye @IversonKwan I'm actually liking GH more than Days right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Artists and Fleas at Chelsea Market in Chelsea, NY https://t.co/AqYr4Glg6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing peer-to-peer discussion happening at the #COSMA Annual Meeting! Love speaking with other State Museum Assoc… https://t.co/eEHLY7HidG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you wouldn’t know racism if walked up to your big #cheetoface and smacked it.  You handling of Cha… https://t.co/LsmBGOoNTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman was such a bad ass. Non-binary. Civilly disobedient long before Rosa Parks. Writing about Jane Crow...I… https://t.co/RIoeK66Rfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidneyPowell1 @l_ylvisaker @realDonaldTrump @RealJamesWoods @LouDobbs They are trying to take over from within. As… https://t.co/vzxvvLWHxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just WOW! And all because he can hit and catch a ball? What message does that send to the rest of the world, those… https://t.co/IBk5kMrsAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have GOTTEN MUCH LESS than you could have gotten. We all know you have NO CHOICE but to signt… https://t.co/BIu8fdKtJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally political didnt watch cant stand Lee Spike Lee’s ‘BlacKkKlansman’ Wins Oscar for Best Adapted Screenplay. https://t.co/EocopSfLkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see you all letting Trump and the media defining the campaign already. Don’t. Don’t let us on Twitter do it eithe… https://t.co/VNet7BGgnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then the king sent, and all the elders of Judah and Jerusalem were gathered to him. https://t.co/8AP6KyInn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think yun ung nasa wreckingball si menggay, ginaya ni Pao dahil daming nagreact nung pumasok sa eksena si stalker… https://t.co/N5Tgg8Cup0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a Mango Slushy tonight with our Maple River Mango Rhubarb Wine and our new Magnifico Mango Slushy Mix. This mi… https://t.co/lIIkyDsFCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[can people who I haven’t talked to in forever quit messaging me?? I don’t want to talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland At least it ain't something serious like the Hatfields and McCoys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArleneKowalczyk @RosaDeliadelos1 @DavidHarris707 @d_ast777 @SeptemberJulie @satribesman @despodanielhugo @Jj051301… https://t.co/VZloGMPovR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimwitkins @WisconsinStrong @wisgop @ScottWalker @repvos @SenFitzgerald and it can never replace the homes that were ruined.]]></document><document><![CDATA[92% of cooking is just chopping. #FactsFirst #Cook https://t.co/0ojB9S7lz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sailorgirl2017 @oectagovernor @JustinTrudeau He's a teacher himself. It was a brag, not a slam. I know, hard to tell somerimes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast throwin’ some axes tonight #wdfowlingaround #SoIDateAnAxeThrower #soiworkwithanaxethrower… https://t.co/4SzZIj5Oq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three people were seriously injured in a car crash along Rt 1 in Brunswick Sunday afternoon, according to Brunswick… https://t.co/phmd5fvow4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is how the traumatized take power back: They go on the record. They take on the hardest of moral challenges.… https://t.co/zJaSrjGRpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly one year ago we met for dinner here.  Ironically, here we are again.  Never enough catch up time but always… https://t.co/A8ptmBhr9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#allurebeautybox  February 2019 $15 per month ~ save $5 on first box! My link is in bio and comments ❤️ In my Febru… https://t.co/PEttzxyCvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can bank on that room is being bugged by N. Korea and Russia. Hope karma b. slaps DJT. Deservedly so...]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta ask yourself do mfers check on you mentally to make sure your good ?!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hurts when I see this and when it affects kids. None of those things matter to a child. https://t.co/aE5kDLOFyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream (nightmare) that I woke up and it was Sunday at Bonnaroo and I had slept through the whole festival]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a @theactionnet petition: Northstar Train to Saint Cloud. Sign here: https://t.co/WczjJo75Qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my episodes of #BeingMrSmith that I didn’t get to post here. I love subbing especially in my hometown! https://t.co/3AHKR2dDhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFoofinator I live in Chicago and am part of a HEMA guild. Most of us have to carry our gear on the trains and b… https://t.co/fi48ODLBm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snow may be gone but the COLD is here to stay! 🥶🥶  @amichaelswx has more on what temps you can expect for the w… https://t.co/01FbmQKOVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnaterrell_tv @LittleRockCity @littlerockfire @FOX16News I hope they find that loser, and bury him under the jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup! People want both relationships with doctors and convenience, but if they have to choose, convenience wins...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing for warmer days with pretty pastels spent toting around the cutest barringtongifts bag. 💕 Carried this cuti… https://t.co/f6fS1i9wkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found some ears I was willing to spend 💸💸💸 on https://t.co/TxtBiQ1XIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Omar is pure hate! Omar anti semitism, needs to go! Democrats must remove her, she… https://t.co/uqGBE13dPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s not your potion, baby girl..  your healing is permanent in Jesus name 🙏🏾♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I definitely overdid it by going to Disneyland when not fully recovered from being sick. Cause today, everyth… https://t.co/BKVlU6iMiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍🐾🐶 #Mondaymotivation #dogsofinstagram #labradoodlesofinstagram #timberino #odidoodle #boys @ Sauvie Island https://t.co/Bb0VBhxi0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where can we get info about the nationality of those caught crossing the border illegally? I am interested to know… https://t.co/euRxEoSAIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fhsaplucy @franklinlorax I agree! We really need to start changing our ways do impact the Earth positively. @franklinlorax #apesland]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady who made us compliment her in the bathroom also tried to fight us 20 minutes later and told us we aren’t… https://t.co/lSBoBdsNRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just tell them that you can spot a guilty person by measuring the distance between their eyes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Susan I am ashamed I was impressed with your mind. Now I see you’ve lost it. Now you are a traitor Dem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day for some #baseball 💙⚾️💛 #ChampionshipSunday  Let’s go Knights!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The approval came despite problems in Kushner's background check related to potential foreign influence.  Kushner h… https://t.co/iHvzOJUfCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight!  Come to the @VarsityTheater and see February One.  Film starts at 7pm.  @dwocnc @CHCNAACP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked 7 blocks from my car to the office and realized I left my keys in the car 😩 Come on Friday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morganalissax @MeyersJosie Lmfao I was about to say... 😂and Josie tell me about how you know... last time I checke… https://t.co/q3GQ1tju1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[But all that glitters isn’t gold, I was blinded. I should have never gave you my heart consignment]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Kristen Strickland as my NC School Hero. You can vote daily. don't forget to share! https://t.co/yvHUadW3FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @NickSmiddy!! i hope your day is just as amazing as you! miss you :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msmillymango I moved back in April. I’d love to see and catch up with you. ☺️ I was just asking about you too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gru0407 Don’t think that will happen; we all know that Franco didn’t do this, so fact that he’s being arrested for… https://t.co/EfvUpFuHjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deepez @SnackSafely Interesting. Makes sense as you can get sick the same way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PehsNahs It’s looking sooooooo good - can’t wait to see it on Monday.  People are totally geeking out about them!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving under the rain #kristianmedinadocumentary #rainseason #californiaweather #vacaville #winter2019… https://t.co/zMcvNsDSSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their smiles say it all! Memories made at the color run family night! @LebanonR3 @TheLeaderinMe @rdjennings3… https://t.co/KUDLiv6PEa]]></document></documents></author>