<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Frank’s private 2.5 hour lesson helped him with...sitting more in the front of the seat... weighting his outside pe… https://t.co/GPgNTo213O]]></document><document><![CDATA[It isn't jobs the will decide Trudeau (and some females ) dates! It's because he acts the part of an idiot, a total… https://t.co/BlS6WMTlKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CP24 The way to do that is to remove the barriers to development; make it easier and less expensive for builders t… https://t.co/gqIOrvlqVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OJustice80 @AdamKnott16 @johnmatheny20 @RBReich @AOC 👆🏼Your poetry, not mine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considerando que están pagando el avión SIN USAR y el hangar NO ES AHORRO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlstoscano @vannahsnana1 @YouRelax @KamalaHarris Think we agree any Effort to avoid nuclear war is worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themaxburns @MalcolmNance isn't this like, exhibit number 5 in any lawsuit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evansweather Whoa did I miss your sendoff? Have been wondering. Wish you all the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews This is Beto....."President?"....yeah....no.... https://t.co/RAoSc8nPkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Never been more tired of politics as I am now. Investigate this President as much as you want. Path… https://t.co/UvzOxcyqEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog It's interesting you fail to mention that his eight year old daughter was also killed in a commando… https://t.co/kvK4JLsskE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuck1one @2ForgetUs @OotyMac @BklynGM @eski225 @TMal761 @RTaylor2283 @TruePG718 @AJTheManChild @goknickstape… https://t.co/HQlhK1eLZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liam's spiky colorful cake @ O'Laff's Sweet Shop https://t.co/QKbhyONFnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to pet my cat at the exact moment he was about to jump up on the counter, I wasn't really looking but saw hi… https://t.co/QjYxYqjZ9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Sears; .@JCPenney:  Why not stop this incredible rivalry, and come together to create ONE store?  #JCSears… https://t.co/DBsKrv7IHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteHegseth I need your response to this because I know you have a really good one. I will go on the record as say… https://t.co/0MYQkbCZJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Grayson, you expressed what we were all feeling Cohen answer by Cohen answer. Thanks for the silent “color comm… https://t.co/RcO65vjl6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #CentralApex on Williams St &amp; Hughes St near Salem St #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenFeinstein should learn that true leadership doesn’t end with listening to voters, donors, or people with the p… https://t.co/jYLOq0lIfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff You are a scammer, and all you are good for is standing in front of a mic, like all the others in Co… https://t.co/07mmRzfNZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barcelona #Spain #Brazil #Japan #HongKong #Portugal #Italy #Finland #NewMexico #Philadelphia #Pennsylvania #Follow… https://t.co/T6rWKtD0Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[We r heading 2 @PrairieRidgeFB @jackson4willis and @CGTrojanFB @BradSeaburg @ben_mcd19  😎🎙️🏈 Great way 2 finish off… https://t.co/tpsUnPgIV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fettuccinem omg I was on campus the other day and she cane and to me hi and have me a hug 😭💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is starting to become a hateful person.  He is no fan of Carolina.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgreget @TomSilverstein @AaronNagler The competition committee is meeting in Indy this week, and Murphy is on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump what the hell trump think that his wall is superman, I guess it's just going to leave its foundati… https://t.co/WXcza9LIIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly the woman's tag team match just reminded me how truly underrated Bayley is #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Nothing will happen to her because she is a member of a protected class and therefore above the law and be… https://t.co/7Dj8PAUtWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrycrews What’s said is not the same thing as what people read/hear.  People are going to hear what they want to… https://t.co/qy84qNVyjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time my car makes a weird noise i just turn my music up and now we’re stuck on the side of the road 😬😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheLLbeLL_xo #SequelstoSongs "After We Unbreak Your Heart, Let's Work On Your Carburetor" @gigirules7… https://t.co/VxEfICOgWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay the course, work hard and believe.  Front row, first in line, lead every drill, know the playbook.  Go get it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC Lets be clear then if u are going to play that game there is no clear evidence the idiot was not born in Kenya!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jen_Royle can’t wait until dinner Thursday! We have been to brunch which was amazing and I haven’t stopped telling… https://t.co/DnEHYUB2VP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taraustralis @shannonmstirone So you don’t make the same mistake twice? 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sky_warr10r @GeorgeTakei I hear you. I have a few that are recognized by some people. But to most it's just a tat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenAlexander #JNJ $JNJ sold #pelvicmesh devices WITHOUT receiving @US_FDA approval! Women with irreparable damage… https://t.co/ZjWZ1YkyQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching Anaconda right now and this movie fucking rules. John Voight’s character is the biggest asshole on ear… https://t.co/Gnd8wsXm7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeronicaTellsIt @ABC Why inject infants with 3 combined vax that we wont inject in pigs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t get more #mapoli than @AyannaPressley talking about patriotism in front of @dunkindonuts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalzonaKerBear @_Chad_Haskins @NBCSCeltics @NBCSBoston I agree with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[She had me wrapped around her finger from the moment she was born. But now that she’s wearing my old concert tee-sh… https://t.co/5x1N6GbrTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is honestly amazing how good this podcast continues to be despite it being on its third wave of co-hosts.  There… https://t.co/OkrYJLAStj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbsoluteLe @SportsCenter @ESPNNFL @phillydotcom @DanGrazianoESPN https://t.co/Y6vwl16Hvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dylan Jones to line to make it a 1pt game for @Waukee_Hoops. Only diener 43-42 vs DBQ Senior. #IAHSBKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[These full band #acoustic shows at @tavernonbroad1 are always a good time. Come hang with us tonight at 9pm! https://t.co/GIauZv5Cg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huh, exactly what i said last year and repeated several times to several people.  I guess i really do know what the… https://t.co/5WtYoKlC01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth What you mean?  Every democrat candidate are gonna burn them to the ground.  Lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalAbsintheDay #LaVeeVerte #TheGreenFairy #HenriMarieRaymonddeToulouseLautrecMonfa @JohnLeguizamo… https://t.co/mtyjLmN6To]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bogotá #Teatro #ABC @caroramirezquin #CarlosTorres https://t.co/yyMkOaQO2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[And payouts *to faux-patriot Republican politicians* so that they can get even more tax cuts, deregulation, and imp… https://t.co/gfBg9ILqsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[To me, "Medicare for all" is Uncle Sam walking off into the abyss trying to be good to 20 million people. There are better ways to do this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodsGift2uWomen @GivethNoCareth Hardest I’ve ever been hit was by a Samoan. I couldn’t see out my left eye for like two days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laishawilkins @MarthaTagle @lopezobrador_ SOLO RINDAN CUENTAS DEL DINERO QUE LES FUE ENTREGADO, ¿SABEN? ES DINERO… https://t.co/uInhVFeOvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ate one too many @insomniacookies this afternoon and have stopped being productive. Worth it! 🍪 https://t.co/RraVSGAboS]]></document><document><![CDATA[In some form of fashion, do what you love! #photography #art #meme #Oscars2019 #SpikeLee #SamuelLJackson… https://t.co/PvaP6tqoQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else feeling the real beef between Twelmman and the other guy taking this #ATLvCIN match?? I've heard commen… https://t.co/MHdX5eeZg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devilslake79 @GI_JoeK @AP Wow a U.S. diplomat. Who would have thought!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ucf_marcdaniels @UCF_MBB @BJTaylor_1 Encouraging sign that Knights have gotten Tacko Fall more involved on offense in the last few games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, I've done some investigative work and I've discovered that the blue one DOESN'T EVEN HAVE A NAME. He's new an… https://t.co/hVyxhfIcLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[A torcida promete fazer a festa no campeonato mundial de estrada em 🌈 @Yorkshire2019 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁥󠁮󠁧󠁿  Esse dia vai ser louc… https://t.co/9lpywStjcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another course done with @CPKN_Online about #cannabis and legislation of it. #study4life #opp #brainfood https://t.co/JgFncJT4Fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseGavin1 Probs presteamed or pressure cooked reassembled magic white meat a la McNuggets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews What you mean is, “Scandal: The Acting Director of the FBI believed the pres… https://t.co/FdWPzdnxqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many incredible women in my life at work and family and friends around the work. I never cease to be in awe of h… https://t.co/7RsFNsD6YU]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡Yard Sale! Inside!🏡  Come buy our stuff! Nice stuff! This Saturday from 10 to 2pm!  1835 Rayle Farm Road  Pleasant… https://t.co/Qa5VBleA8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MohamedMOSalih Not really a thing, stolen from everywhere else, and made way more unhealthy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to do your taxes? I used @creditkarmatax. Check it out! It was super easy, totally free and 100% awesome. Swee… https://t.co/QyzuNqTPWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBJ_DRW @FlyingMonkeys @ottawahockey @DrunkPolkaroo @Paul__G__ @SudburyHomebrew @david_buist @heatherington84… https://t.co/kMd7TAjaMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrometheusAM @jfc_3_ I tease Jamie a lot, but I love seeing him succeed.   I've always believed that young people… https://t.co/0Fu9bgWCnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @UHCougarMBK current 12-game winning streak is tied for sixth-longest in American Athletic Conference history. Th… https://t.co/1OVjl3oTPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @RandPaul Because @RandPaul is a flaming leftist like most #Republicans.    He just loved supporting Mitt… https://t.co/LsEH2H8uOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe #Joe how can Y'all believe anything this man TRUMP says, when it has been Proven time after time he's… https://t.co/oDK3761Tgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever is the tallest wins🤠 @ Shortville, Wisconsin https://t.co/D3msCi1hrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrowand @RickPetree @ProfessorShaw I was musing about saying Trump is "cheap." Treating honesty as if it were comp… https://t.co/tGznMZ5Ws6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormaLevin2 SSport only bought the TV rights for the ATP Tour I believe, hence no WTA matches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston fans have been all class and respectful in my mentions. Every single one of them. They have a great team bu… https://t.co/Fn52QYACXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't mess with Rebelión Amarilla 💋 . . See @bestia666tj March 13th when @wildkatsports presents ¡LUCHA LIBRE! In D… https://t.co/tDSW9yfR0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not ashamed of this. She distracted me but I’m about to fucking rage. The come up is always better than the shit storm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson, @BretBaier, @GovMLG, @SenWarren I wonder  if this is what we can expect from Medicaid for all. - Ca… https://t.co/vFzhBNnqyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[buddy burton photography: Iowa City-Iowa Interstate https://t.co/1lIoAYlcaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dragonball #dragonballz #dragonballsuper #dbz #anime #goku https://t.co/VwgbNmp9Dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time is Money $$ //  I ain’t got time to buy a new heart of mine. 🖤 @ Troubadour https://t.co/q4XXNzs2xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theMikeRow It’s just a hypothetical. Who wants to move from Hoosierland?!? https://t.co/4u0rpGnWfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuevaGonzalo menos mal que está retirado porque eso significa un idiota menos creando mentiras y adulando al dueño… https://t.co/PG7mJwiBkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Coast Elite Final 4 Experience April 4th 2019 Minnesota.  Passes starting to go out today.  #westcoastelite… https://t.co/qToDzzP8EZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHSAA Semis Standouts: A.J. Griffin’21 Moussa Cisse’21 R.J. Davis’20 Joe Toussaint (Iowa) Ryan Myers’20 Jaylen “Juj… https://t.co/MuujDbtIif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad you are spreading the word @locricchioa! @midatahub is a great example of collaboration to improve data use in… https://t.co/rc8kvDjzQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had that happen to me a few times on the receiving end with Asian men stereotypes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hearties. I think Twitter realized I’m not going to stay out of jail. LOL.  #Hearties #WCTH… https://t.co/U5HT9YBuKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richthekid If you're not gonna drop the album drop the song with Thug I need it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Los Venezolanos en el exterior GRITAMOS:  QUEREMOS REGRESAR🇻🇪 QUEREMOS REGRESAR🇻🇪 QUEREMOS REGRESAR🇻🇪 QUER… https://t.co/HEnTDZhxgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suchitjain @SOLIDWORKS @Dassault3DS I’m ready to start on my Solid Works projects. What an inspiring day. Thanks f… https://t.co/jAryY0z7j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @CoachJimWeeks on getting Auburn to the finals. Looks like one of the best high school coaches t… https://t.co/fx3CKThn7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamie_allen Spent my night walking around the building with 50 keys figuring out what they all went to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 1.0 mph SW. Barometer 29.871 in, Steady. Temperature 35.8 °F. Rain today 0.08in. Humidity 96%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Savasana might look like a nap at the end of our yoga practice. But it’s actually a fully conscious pose aimed at b… https://t.co/lOl2B8XFi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@punker_irl @fistvoices “Talk about Your Abortion” by William B. Turner https://t.co/ATczNrl57B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always liked the Myrtle Beach Hurricanes incorporating the letter design of their parent @BlueJays into this cap… https://t.co/bLaWVqv9Gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Halgrenj @JayEllGii @AmishAbe37 @bikesalsa @McAllisterDen @RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi So much… https://t.co/S6ux3LDO7b]]></document></documents></author>