<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Southborough, Massachusetts https://t.co/JU4MOoJrXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤 why 🖤 isn't 🖤 there 🖤 a 🖤 brown 🖤 heart 🖤 emoji 🖤 https://t.co/yAeVEzK1N3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatchingSean receiving the award for his Dad #oliverstone #chinanights 👏💥💫 I remember Sean when he was 10 years ol… https://t.co/1ezmXxxXv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at the good old @AllstateArena cheering on my 2nd home hockey team, the @GoldenKnights through my home town… https://t.co/Rrdd3IlDLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why are you so obsessed with Hillary?  Don’t you need to deal with all the accusations you face?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christian tried to balance a cup of coffee on my head in the middle of Macy's even tho I told him not to and that shit spilled all over me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mingberg @XandraXandraBX @muttslikeme @PrezesPan @Chicago_CES @SandraSBreen @DavidLogan2020 @DanielBrasilia… https://t.co/Ww3O5SMiGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanSkornia @JamesRambin @austintowers My general thought is that if a PTMD wouldn't make money, then an RPP pro… https://t.co/fMFO8U7owc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off the @ACOG_District8 Legislative Forum with a discussion on Maternal Mortality! @ACOGAction @acog… https://t.co/I7f5Z494HX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my video also please like and subscribe ☺️🌮  #tacobell Taco Bell Dollar Menu Taste Test https://t.co/pLiwCQBwcW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spot of tea with milk #yummy #likethebritsdo #warmthforthewin @ Edmond, Oklahoma https://t.co/06qvgKQv8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinaperri once again keeping me company at work ..... is it 4:30pm yet? Lol love you girl ! Happy Internation… https://t.co/oJ7CD9GwXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vickivbreezy @pam_brundige @eddsmitty @MystiConnolly @ninampls @JustMeDeeGeeLee @ShelbyKStewart @hippy_patriot_… https://t.co/8bQ8HOreuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wish that anyone who was hurting would reach out but the reality is that no one wants to be a burden or a bother to anyone...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lotaypark Nelena for life. I made a windows movie maker movie and a PowerPoint about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hayyyy!  Muje rona aa rha 😭😭😭😭 Merae tamater 😂😂😂😂  Burger mein kya daloon gi ..  Coward  &amp; Toiletless nation!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealJenCandy @ChrisCandy4u Hi Jen and Chris, I’m with CP24 in Toronto. Hoping we can chat about a possible Skyp… https://t.co/HU9PTr97FD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished meditating and I just heard country music playing loud but faintly in my ear. I listened for a good… https://t.co/nzTpnm8Oj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[go vote for @oleTmoney_14 @JackRoubiikk and @Wi11Aiken !!!⚾️https://t.co/8M4r1w41YZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barrel_time @RealMuckmaker Not in Norway @ least certain records.  Some available only after a certain time period… https://t.co/TQBwVa8t84]]></document><document><![CDATA[4) I didn’t realize until it was too late, that not only did these men bring wretched smoke to a festive day, they… https://t.co/sLqZrEtJ0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelly_simonds @CityofNN @sistercities_nn welcomes our Sister City Taizhou, China celebrating our 20th anniversary… https://t.co/Wv62fLE3Jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prichardsonla i want the state of california to press hate charges against sagaftra for blacklisting me on lies an… https://t.co/iWTLN9hsox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hen_helper @deogratiasfilm @itvlondon @samholdertv No he hasn't "paid  like 20 victims"-#LiarsWillBeSilence🤥🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's Birthday Month Appreciation Day 20 goes out to a strong group of women in film who showed how successful an… https://t.co/yz3kYjSPVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Feisty_FL You are probably right...she meant “Dems” not “country” dementia medication strength needs upped]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, as the artists gathered for a group photo. Mingled with new friends who make wonderful art Thanks… https://t.co/npUWfxZqf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 15,000 counter Trump Event with El Paso Rally to reject Hatred and Bigotry #Resistance! - https://t.co/EjemUcCsgZ via @commondreams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EHCMcKee @realDonaldTrump I am proud I voted for Trump and I am not a criminal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️💋 Happy Friday Jr. #loveyourself #selfcare @ Co-op City, Bronx https://t.co/Zoz6QKSizF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This stall is killing me, maybe if I stop sneaking pieces of bread 🤣🤣🤣 #epicfail]]></document><document><![CDATA[SET GOOD!!!! Another Sunday spent with a room full of baddies 🔥🔥🔥 . 💃🏽: laylucha @Kiara_Castle (tag the other lovel… https://t.co/JUM2MoC2M9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once my kneecap popped out at night so forcefully it broke off shards of my tibia. My insurance didn't want to pay… https://t.co/6eGW28rU0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnDitullio Pained me to see that on paper the Steelers had one of the best teams in the NFL.  Had such big hopes… https://t.co/6PwEHJUjs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[To learn more about the Commission’s findings, as a state companion to this national report see… https://t.co/2hgyr9eTQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman The show did not get canceled. It went on without her and it was a success and its renewed for anot… https://t.co/5PjRpB4F83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I’ve followed you for 2 days and I can already tell you’re hella toxic and judge ravers but claim you’re the be… https://t.co/PboY3XUECF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vegan #mexicanfood #veganmexicanfod #heaven @ Nacho Daddy https://t.co/dvvLAbstNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellierich80 @bunsenbernerbmd So, which way does the water swirl? 😉 Looks like you guys are having a fabulous time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be my 14th flight give or take in the past few months and now little things make me mad at BWI bc I’m too… https://t.co/xJUtgyLZfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at this gorgeous city 😍 Been there 3xs and never been able to enjoy their warm weather.   ...That changes this… https://t.co/3CDQOUwwsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels @NJvoter2020 And a bigger question is how are these freshman getting on these committed in the firs… https://t.co/vl2I1S3BQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a45cooper @marcosanchezorg @Sean_C_Larkin I do!! I make a plan to take time off in advance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So honoured to be at the International Women’s Day Breakfast of Champions this morning ! A Dynamic group Of incredi… https://t.co/tvIn1xElFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[گفت وگوی مشروح فارس با خجستهاستیضاح وزیر صنعت در دستور کار مجلس قرار گرفت/ دلالان در حال مدیریت اين وزارتخانه هستندhttps://t.co/P6EAYYUp48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeDeVitoComedy @AnnCoulter I'm basically down to home improvement shows and Fox news.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Be careful using the word imbecile... Twitter puts me in jail for using it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Threw on a RANDOM episode of How I Met Your Mother and there’s an “emotional moment” and Jersey Girl by Bruce Sprin… https://t.co/uy8hFN1ynk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could just walk away And I know the reasons I shouldn’t stay...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you changed your registration to D yet🙏⁉️If you run in FL you would win...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liinakaro11 Have a great time. I hope you get a chance to meet Tom and get a selfie/autograph. Very exciting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Book is worth seeing. How the segregated South affected musicians traveling there. Also a good article publis… https://t.co/AxnY8atRXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristineBemis2 @HOWareyousmart @peterdboland @hayes_melisa @EvelynCorrea7 @cpoole27 @heARTISTatWORK… https://t.co/vqQCR6A7aX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andygaarza @pepevc2 I'm basic bitch JAJAJJ desde ayer está ese mame y leí el hilo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do better putting him on the breast then pumping right now but I want to do pumping long term]]></document><document><![CDATA[#c3conf was such a great experience! So thankful for our amazing team @livingchurch and looking forward to… https://t.co/xbAiRTB8LM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need a haircut but idk if I want a trim or to just chop it off to my shoulders 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s an idiot!  Colorado would have no voice in elections. This is stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mte_detroiter @hotblondtrouble @StevieRayHubcap @DonnaRa46455182 @DonBrown54 @sappermartin @EdwinLo31339753… https://t.co/t49p7w2ZhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is 100% my dad. When I told him about my miscarriage last week, he was nothing but loving and supportive even… https://t.co/Njm6NWxQRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goals #armsworkout #crossfitmom #motivation @ Lake Mary, Florida https://t.co/O8B0oAp9Fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gweeniee_ Sending all the raise vibes! You definitely deserve to be compensated for your work and glad you asked for one:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[rude ass hoes don’t even acknowledge me but wamna try to ask me to work for their funky asses . BITCH NO GET THE FU… https://t.co/e9AuYCoD4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a day trip to the #PhiladelphiaMuseumofArt and the #FabulousFashion exhibit had me swooning! 😍 Not pictured:… https://t.co/Xm26iczYUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did my kid turn into  this outstanding woman? Oh wait I raised her! ❤️ ❤️ High five me! ❤️ I might of been a fu… https://t.co/EHg2rUd0Rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild love, a little rose, + some booty grabs in the Oregon wilderness. https://t.co/BgzBkjDiyu https://t.co/urADpuE8RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing I love more than traveling and experiencing new things #SPRANGBREAK2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildeAspen Yeah he seemed a little sheepish and was a little embarrassed that he had no idea how to take apart a d… https://t.co/SOB0YT4YZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for my Sunday jacuzzi #lushbathbomb #chardonnay #metime @ Prospect Place Apartments https://t.co/S22W6YJOnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGamradt Have you read this?! Another favorite of mine!! https://t.co/xshTvo8FTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wifemomcpa100 @moniqueswansen @MeganTarnow @madelinekpratt @helm_twyla @KathyGrosskurth @accountantcindy @FLOWCPA… https://t.co/sZjZTGmpQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In your goodness give and preserve the fruits of the earth, — so that each day there may be bread enough for all. Lord, we trust in you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con Sue Photography and Design  🚚 Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚛  This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/unHtyIT8Fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckECheeses @AllPowerisHis Can you explain why the toppings look how they do though?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @imore: Every character confirmed for Mortal Kombat 11 so far https://t.co/J2fa2BgJCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate getting stupid triplet questions when people find out I’m a triplet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTW if you ever need a new boomerang of me and my dog Henry being adorable at @PygmyHippoShop, I have at least 210… https://t.co/crTF6G9xe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdyBarkan A cousin of mine lost his battle to #ALS a few years ago. His name for the disease was the ‘phantom’. No… https://t.co/lzPtSoxm5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m an hour &amp; a half late but it was my perfect baby’s 1/2 birthday so enjoy my beautiful baby Twitter 😄 https://t.co/RRbzXLzZq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you imagine a pink jumbo though you’ve not seen one? Creative imagination intrigues. What do you see -- a duck… https://t.co/e8E8R78Evr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mangosocks_ @DMazzeti I’m pretty sure Jesus wouldn’t care if they are Democrat or Republican. I can make a pretty… https://t.co/WCYAiBMbSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvdsgl Ha I read this in @FortuneMagazine @thetermsheet today. She is holding meetings with filmmakers about her s… https://t.co/quBAtQXgKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Chilly and cloudy in West Mifflin Pa https://t.co/TdgNclDYxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sudneu_ @b0yzdntcry @NataliaSalcid15 @abbeyruns @z__e__u__s__ @Ibelievthehype thank you. this is what i was gonna say.. throw a PAIR.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody combed Max’s curly hair back for his school pictures and he looks weird and now I’m not gonna buy them smh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ruffcutspurrfectstyles has monthly specials that you can add as a package #kandileday got her a $3 toothbrushing t… https://t.co/G7zIZW22iV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soggystella1 @Twitlertwit @philosophrob @KeyDecision1 Notice how Clinton is keeping her 'public' distance. After t… https://t.co/GmfOdNGIxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @senatemajldr @SenateGOP @HouseGOP Ditch Mitch selling out the American people proving he's the real De… https://t.co/kDZhne9v8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Džungle Pilsner by @kingcongbrewing at @RoCoWine — https://t.co/RwbiRoTy51]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep just randomly seeing things blow past my window that I think are supposed to be attached to the apartment. 😅🌬🌬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student designs growing flower mandala pattern in my Gr 2 class #math @ChildrenNature #SpringForward https://t.co/bflbzky4wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC #NicoleWallace check this out. He bullied the parents of Parkland murder victims and now he’s threatening a… https://t.co/vaW01cmSxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[From winter feels to summer sun 🌅 Sunset (1972) by #andywarhol, from a series of 632 #screenprints commissioned by… https://t.co/bc9xHGo2uF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenidraRWoods_ First it was called white privilege, the came the birth of Affirmative Action.  AA will be the answ… https://t.co/HYb8nLQrZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyHighFootball @ad_dlaw Looks like Chapman. They are up 25 at the end of 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be thankful if you didn’t bc this network is full of a bunch of liberal cry babies]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s days that are extremely high &amp; days that are extremely low, and today is so low that it physically hurts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are YOU FUCKING KIDDING ME? FUNNY YOU GOT YOUR MEMORY BACK WHEN YOU COULDN'T GET ANY WORK!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy belated #nerdwednesday! This weeks new comics are on the racks now!! (Thanks to the snow for the delay!)… https://t.co/svusN5UVxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your word of the month is Patience...and you know by the end of February, all schools need it!]]></document></documents></author>