<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX @DaleJr THAT WAS TRULY RESPECTFULLY  DONE .TRULY HEART FELT AND  TRULY REAL .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tan asf, got my white toes, finally got a consistent gym routine &amp; my butt is getting bigger I’m such a happy gal ((:]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to take my pants off when I get home https://t.co/bHnDDkEwD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyPapworth1 @linalan96 @iowamamaof3 @BMNY_DeadCast @leedusme1227 @TiffyLaw3 @planetpakua @Jamadon26 @ilove4paws… https://t.co/DYqE1fqscG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Human and sex trafficking is not an emergency?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bearmyheart1973 @NLL @stevepriolo23 @NLLBandits @NEBlackWolves @CurtisDickson17 @NLLRoughnecks @DLintner14… https://t.co/i18wRoZPDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando algo tiene que suceder, sucede. Por favor que suceda rápido 😘😍🤩🤞🏼🙏🏼🌠✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyK @Twitter @dickc @bohan @TJay @stephanied @ju2thalee @mooreryan @evanr @semurph @LiatBycel @LK Congrats love… https://t.co/V5ATaIVeQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahh_yo same. i’m moving next week on top of it. 😅 but we’re splitting an airbnb to save money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realphilhendrie @JaySLeach @BigGameVanPelt @AnnCoulter Got destroyed ? Do you know what you're talking about? He W… https://t.co/T0Qhb05I7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realize that no-one pays attention to me, so I will be sitting in the corner doing needlepoint 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is probably how your commute will feel starting tomorrow through NOVEMBER on Peachtree Rd. in Buckhead.   Why?… https://t.co/T4HtmVV31E]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Ways to Approach a Standards-based Mindset in Schoology https://t.co/ty86hxFWoq Helpful visuals! New word: “decay… https://t.co/tdsC4BeULQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nintendo eShop Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Bel… https://t.co/tHcnfcdepv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you guys want a raise,  I can't think of a shittier say to ask. Just sayin' From Discover on Google https://t.co/1a4Er6BVqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like you Leader McConnell - you don’t put up with trash you take it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[People still watch his movies and adore him and hold him up on a pedestal.  So I see nothing wrong with the true na… https://t.co/VfRXOqeulw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been through some bad shit, I should be a sad bitch Who woulda thought it'd turn me to a savage?  @ArianaGrande hit… https://t.co/YmTGljM5Xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[In her @mainedcm blog, she said that she has never been in a relationship? Come On!.you know in your heart that is… https://t.co/p02Jg4LUv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[T Qin Shi Huang W 1.4 billion T Cantonese F Hong Kong  BloodDrive @SheehanLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting the beautiful Mirage today!  We saw Lions Tigers and Dolphins #vegasedgerealty #shawnasonnenburg https://t.co/uIKvctFppL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phantom4203 The question is why do you have to ask?  It's as plain as the nose on your face. THINK ABOUT IT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @lehimesa Wish Twitter had edit...I meant FLAG not flat...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimikry_ Maybe we should do a prize for the first shot? I have merch coming soon....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Life &gt; Internet  S.F. will forever be unforgettable❤️  @russdiemon #iseeyoutour https://t.co/y9UcfVbpXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunny_bbw How do I like something more than once.... lmao this is sooooo spot on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us this Thursday for the most fun you'll have all week! #TigerHeatLA WATCH: https://t.co/YdLm57zvFN https://t.co/tWF0fGi9ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[#9 -I’m good with that😉 for now! #wine #wineblog #grapeexperiences #cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠👶🏻⃠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judgejeffbrown @Augoosetus Congrats to the newest Brown Eagle Scout. Few people achieve that great honor that will… https://t.co/XPVQxM3UbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bestbrewdeli @BrewDogUSA @MichalinaMack this is the brewery from my home city in Scotland!! Please visit it! MT @BrewDogUSA #craftbeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[edward made garbanzos today and wow i miss guamuchil and las garbanzadas :((]]></document><document><![CDATA[My neighbor is snowblowing directly outside my window. It’s 11 pm why is he like this? I suppose I should be thankf… https://t.co/6KEXII4HsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland He was born in Witchita Falls TEXAS.  That's Tornado Alley and (the armpit of the Air Force). https://t.co/nSRHhH2oen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sptxo Try you belong to somebody else by dej loaf and Jacquees, whewww chileeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza You don't even have a master's and he has a PhD and is a full prof. Also you went to prison. Everyone is laughing at you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@90sSlowJamz @ravenmaster1 i once saw one in SF open a bag of doritos the way humans do: grabbing one side with its… https://t.co/lOqoMZHI10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting baby brother 💜 (@ GSR @ The Castle in Urbana, IL) https://t.co/le5YUtUZCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@footyDoc How sad is that thought “the expectations of fatherhood have been so low..”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Pharmacy Technician" at CVS Health? Apply even if you're not a 100% match. You mig… https://t.co/c12iQABS6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mountain West Statement Regarding Nevada at Utah State Men's Basketball Postgame https://t.co/yWIMlFxQEp #Weak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Sam heughan Instagram story @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/RhkCzQayYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've got nothing to show but I'm trying my best  https://t.co/4EMJ5qdN20]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously LOVE having  crockpot. It saves us from eating out at least four times a month 😂🙏🏻☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics Did you see the gut on this guy, he's as big as trump! He is having quadruple just like trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly You know what's even more tiresome?  Trump's bigotry and hatefulness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flea333 Is Andre 3000 still a part of OutKast? He was missing from the super bowl. Legitimately asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OleHenriksen @jolucky1 Jodi knows how  to get stuff done in our organization.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvokainKrieg @lilith2u @BlakandBlack @mariecountryman @bunkybun @ChrisFDonahue @buell003 @Dennis_Lintz @KatG4… https://t.co/oDM3aylWcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigFreddieG! Hello my dunking friend. Thanks for entertaining us right  when we needed it. Do it some more 😆#SicEm #SicOSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[En un juego, alguien gana y alguien pierde, de eso se trata una diversión.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReadMoreScience I credit my mom’s support as the #1 reason I got into science. Her parents (one being a scientist… https://t.co/kWuiONrlW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t be friends with girls who think like this at all cause i know I’m a real bitch period]]></document><document><![CDATA[#home #clouds #sagebrush #Utah #saratogasprings #stormisbrewing #winter #lovethatcolor #enjoythemoments… https://t.co/JgtUTnS25y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_Indy_Pendent Almost everybody did.  Bad 4th quarter killed the year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏛Con Sue Photography and Design🏛  ☀️Like our photos...Follow our IG ☀️  🏛This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🏛… https://t.co/ku1h1y1B4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerBuddy22 I’m excited for you! I think Battle of the Bastards and The Winds of Winter might be the two best back… https://t.co/j1rI78wZSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revisited our engagement photo gallery today and found some new favorites... want to post them all but trying to ha… https://t.co/G36vxN4Oqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to be attending the #InternationalWomansDay panels at SXSW this year! Happy Women’s Day💖💄💋👑 @sxsw https://t.co/VwL1ZGMS0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar is on her way out, just a matter of time, this is America, we can't have ppl in our government that makes hate… https://t.co/r8mm5nDumk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elianapintov Jajajaja tranqui mi mamá la revivió, no sé cómo pero still alive 😊❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who make disciples together thrive together.  Thanks, Highpoint Church, for bringing courageous love to the s… https://t.co/QBcMlwnqWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I broke the 8-minute mile pace with a 1.27-mile 7:54 pace run. . . . .  #running #trailrunning… https://t.co/2kOVXTK0KB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A skunk has arrived at @ABCNews4—he’s snaggletoothed and just the cutest little buddy! https://t.co/Ewpg6k7Xjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AthleteTweetts LOL Normally its an offensive lineman but a guy like @MikeEvans13_ hitting you is enough Lord know lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#expertdojo #californiamedicalmarijuana #laoceanave @ Santa Monica, California https://t.co/xAs2OHWhXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early this morning, filling in for my buddy Ed @wtob980 Y’all give us a listen on the air or on the app!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4boysnanny @rodeo_man32 @cockyrascal @IminHisbook @mymynags @Sherrie75527742 @monkeyMagaKAG @dpsgpa @OrenIShiKiddo… https://t.co/NKyaasLGxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalAnt @IdahoJankinsMOC Did you see how she called out the legislator who carries his gun? And his punk ass… https://t.co/eg32wdpTKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc13houston This is as low down &amp; dirty dark money made off this poor girl’s death😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡‼️‼️‼️‼️‼️‼️‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Black Excellence. @KidFury @crissles 😍#TheRead https://t.co/QQ41dO4Rmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cutest guy walked in to the shop and I had to be on my best behavior 😞😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tlax_3 I’ll never forget the OG insomnia group we had with @danielchung14 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new mattress topper has me sleeping so good all night that I’m always wide awake and ready to go by like 4am lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinBrauns literally no rush, and definitely not when you’re on vacation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmilesbyPayet @destinyleigh221 Because the vaccine makers and doctors aren’t liable at all. It all falls on the pa… https://t.co/CIBgVRKOoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[LSJ visited the GTMNERR to learn about their work at the education center (so many summer camps coming up!). Then w… https://t.co/NVdIeyupLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of my team—and our partners—for bringing these amazing speakers to campuses around the country (and, i… https://t.co/Mdp8hL6RbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah breakups hurt but y’all ever study for a test &amp; still fail it? that hurts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ajdin_Rondo @neontaster The birtherism thing that a few on the Right were into is not racist.  I don't agree with… https://t.co/T0dUIO0Tpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just put out a mascara wand donation bin! There's one in each bathroom :) #bauernhauslikesconservation… https://t.co/McdCblWJll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTBus Why do i have to dig for this? Or tweet out of frustration? Why does the regular schedule say that preside… https://t.co/uJ0ohpG8tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hibillyby This donut shop is the cutest! I'm glad so many people ended up stopping by. Congrats on the grand opening! ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t find my cat. Open the front door and she’s waiting there like “please help. I’ve only been out here for th… https://t.co/5vvHh2hILn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtfcoo Either Crunch or Lifetime because I believe you will find better success being able to Squat, deadlift etc… https://t.co/b1Mnk7L3ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo I'd be right behind you...I say those who abuse the helpless should be treated as badly as those they… https://t.co/GV6fZs6RgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[John it's not as if they only care about money they do only care about money they're mentally ill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerzcourtney HAHAHA I LITERALLY ORDERED A PRINT OF THE PIC TO GET HIM TO SIGN TOMORROW 💀💀 im still in shock]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest gift I made myself was selling my Xbox and getting creative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @RepJerryNadler The world new he was a crook long before he ran for president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re ever trying to get un-horny just watch some white lesbians porn. 😂 they stiff asses]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump supporters, take notice.  This is real and will affect you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s happened... am I an ome?! @lizakoshy 😂 am I?!? 🤣 also what happened to her head?? https://t.co/nxowdr4QVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me why i’m sitting in the bath with a cup of water next to it and Lucy just comes in and starts drinking it..... can i live?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited!!!!!!! Long Week!  Glad it’s OVER!!!!!!!! #finallyfriday https://t.co/QTCy9c4O81]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s too early to be having a whole convo with the Uber driver 😩🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bohemian Rhapsody is not the movie I want and if it's the movie I deserve well then shame on me for whatever I did to deserve it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikkilynH If you get any more skinny you will disappear.  Just keep eating healthy.  And there are only 2 people y… https://t.co/qnzBInmBkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unsponsoredgeek @justinjm1 ... a person who voted illegally in Texas got five years. More criminal justice reforms needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unyenbomb19 @GrahamAllen_1 It’s called adoption! Or maybe we show women they are stronger than they think! They ca… https://t.co/090XceO0Pb]]></document></documents></author>