<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Just turn your range hood on. 50% of Americans don’t run their range hoods.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WouldntWantToBeHandcuffed unless it was by a super model. Hello ladies let’s play rough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#power in working together every oar in the water pulling in the same direction moving #forward as one power in ser… https://t.co/cgnRj70Z0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s one thing when Trump makes us cringe when he’s here at home. It’s another thing when he disgraces America on t… https://t.co/bK63M8aGWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido una de las cosas que más me gustan es que los que en este momento diriguen el país son Vzlanos jóvenes y l… https://t.co/0j6NQb1JZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like there’s a huge shortage of good B2B growth/marketing talent out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TheNICKname_ @JohnBrownPJ @Pioneerloft @JakeKUTV @KUTV2News @NevadaHoops @USUAthletics @MountainWest… https://t.co/7J0sC9UjBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGiesenschlag Over/under on lights hit tonight? I'm setting the line at 9. Holy schnikes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebosays Emulator? I always wondered how people did twitch on old consoles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh look The Uso’s are champions for the 2000th time #WWEChamber https://t.co/iJu4REN79a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maythediamond Asuma hurts but seeing Shikamaru turn into the legend he is eased the pain. I’m still upset about Jiraiya tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Migo_Jacobo I stay missing layups. If it’s not 19’ 9” it’s not worth my time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@no_pullbacks ??? @CNBC says  "Stocks post 5-day losing streak, notch worst week of 2019 after anemic jobs report"… https://t.co/w6VDX2yD5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manny_III And Scottie literally said he’d take LeBron over Jordan on First Take.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTChelps both presto reload machines in the paid area of Broadview Station are not working https://t.co/PXiFY5FhSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeannieG40 My mother would jump and shout and say what's that noise about, Rodney put it back on the station....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder that our state is currently run by criminal co-conspirators in the 2016 Russian interference of our electi… https://t.co/6XL3adwgnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may not be your dad but I sure do love you as if you where my own little one❤ #donughtswithdad #imadadnow… https://t.co/yGV2Uv7JP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGlassman312 @marty_lederman Agree that’s possible/likely, except that Congress won’t know if they don’t comply… https://t.co/5wDmLe6txK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to take a breath, then laugh because this world and Trump are so crazy that fantasy has become reality and re… https://t.co/dQDa8FFw2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sermon is over. My Realistic Free Agency Wish List comes out Tuesday and here’s a Heads up, it involves a trade… https://t.co/G4ugdtpCxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si los soldados estan abandonando al Regimen, uno a uno y ya son mas de 23 y no hay una Fuerza Armada al frente, so… https://t.co/vXkHnNw8Gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Herring_NBA That looked like a play Pippen would have made. A whole side of the court you could make easy passes on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Celtics Garbage 1st quarter. Garbage Coaching! Pure Garbage. Lakers are just going to the rim every time to lay it… https://t.co/vzP6gEv0gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[About 10 minutes to tip as the Rock Island Rocks are warming up to face Edwardsville in the Class 4A Normal West Se… https://t.co/7qMGtj42RH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Dirección de Auditoria de Obra Pública in Monterrey, Nuevo León https://t.co/ioEUxG64Yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEALED coverup! I’ve had some cancellations and reschedules this week and have a TON of free time to tattoo whateve… https://t.co/unFAc8tdXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett And waiting for your tweet condemning the US coast guard member who was planning a… https://t.co/E9PAGtWZkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to point out that in the midst of the madness that my boy @JavensWorld was nowhere to be found. Probably w… https://t.co/IXbAi8gSMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aoakley33 I think we should be able to win both of those games without them. Come on now ... still a great group o… https://t.co/6AL0rtOjEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoover looking sweet: not the John Edgar, but the altogether pretty good one, the Herbert Clark… https://t.co/EmaF1XTRKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final day of Men's Invitational! #teamwork #lightendoftunnel https://t.co/EIBTeH4cSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a mass media major means I can filter baseball into all my class work. So for my technology presentation... I… https://t.co/7XUkKUgbOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got second place in the tournament today. ☺️🥈🏆 @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/9FVcRe1jjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesbos @KeyFrames Then I'm going to blindly go with animation-duration, animation-delay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mancode1972 Your not a good riter, Rightest. And man you are a silly person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope everyone has a great week! Dont be this guy! https://t.co/pe7sLk5Anz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give the gift of warmth this Valentine’s day! We’re thrilled to have had the opportunity to donate over 100 pairs o… https://t.co/gFEZM3ehK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ABC13FCO Update: Phoebus leads Northside 28-20 at half of Class 3 state finals. Full court press of Phantoms force… https://t.co/ImFEXJbYSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even South Florida loves “The Whale”. Available for sale in the concourse at BBT&amp;T Center @NHLCanes #NHLCanes… https://t.co/4M9fZjz90S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even in Mississippi, one of my (three) home states, Confederate monuments have now come under attack, from students… https://t.co/xODeCnkLQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoingRight1 @gaye_gallops @POTUS 🤢🤮💩💩=@kathygriffin Get a job  last month @POTUSTrump reported 300,000 new once’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyWoods Are you down to make a hype club banger for all the thotties that love you? #DropThatWood]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the NAM hasn’t changed much over the last 24 hours. Giving downtown 4”-8”. And a bit higher for the NW burbs at… https://t.co/wuPraoZHoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Why wouldn't he take a murderous despot's word for it? That's a man after Trump's own heart. https://t.co/32fGqPSv6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randbrown19901 @TheQuartering I was referring to the original computer game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully in the next 5-7 years, expect to see my name on those bookshelves, or even as a New York Times Bestseller😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[But. Your takeaway should be - your partner's orgasm is not a duty and your worth and sexuality are not based on th… https://t.co/Nc9Wl2ugua]]></document><document><![CDATA[God I hope he tries that tuff guy act in prison! He will someone’s bitch for sure. #LiberalismIsAMentalDisorder… https://t.co/DLIMJnmnkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_vladeck The Second Circuit rarely goes en banc—like once every two to three years. It doesn’t seem to matter how important the issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aku_gang I want whatever this guy is smoking or drinking what normal or sober person comes to that conclusion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@razmajak55 @NYCNavid I'm not saying Biden is the best candidate. He might bomb on the trail. I'm just saying that… https://t.co/h5TWb8ycnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than a spring training game #redsox @jameswcarras https://t.co/Fm9klzGRp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, we do not want four more years of Donald Trump. We want six more years of Donald Trump and eight more years of… https://t.co/HWdlhDk8sV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't care who this offends but fuck fortnite 🤣😂🤣😂 this game is my shit @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/afB3n0I03n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn Uber was taxing on #FatTuesday. Had to walk 25 minutes with my luggage and got lucky and found a cab for $36.… https://t.co/DsF2L4EY45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VonChing_ Both of you guys continue to raise the ceiling. Keep that grind up in spring ball!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing about being the Tennis Bus Driver is @Wendys the Bus Driver eats free!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This move has fucked up my gym routine and it sucks 😪 I need to get back to it ASAP! lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@farmermegzz I meant you no disrespect by mentioning what happened to you to @Victory_shriek if my mentioning it ca… https://t.co/JLEyBlU8lM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! Seek the truth, tell the truth. One ♥️! 😎👁️☮️ https://t.co/3cvOtGUMhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMVivancoHRW razones que obligan a dejarlo abierto 1- gente muere porque alguien, via accion de las armas, evita l… https://t.co/neNCE5ksEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a discord account don’t know how to use it but feel free to add me on here https://t.co/XMXiZoisdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re boycotting the #oscars over their decision to give #editing #cinematography #hair and #shortfilm #awards… https://t.co/1bzFd3BmrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ValentinesDay  To the best wife &amp; friend ever!! @JRRestaino Love you! https://t.co/zhl7qVJ5eH]]></document><document><![CDATA[They better not bring this Bullshit ratchetness behavior in Florida City 💀😩😩😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_segura My first superhero comic: Jim Shooter and George Perez on Avengers 162. https://t.co/xAASXzzJgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice juicy , citrus/lemon notes, clean smooth mouthfeel - Drinking a Figure Four by @LockCityBrewing @ Rose's Famil… https://t.co/IVbkZkJHbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in the music biz would something that was $20 in 1994 be devalued to $1.29 in 2019. SMH… https://t.co/REw4tzA7qW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President, while this seems logical, what are you doing to her child?  Probably better to allo… https://t.co/qmGGVa86Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[it really fucked with me to see that twitter chose THEODORA to be the face of “remembering the women of history...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you surf 🏄 🏄‍♀️? .. .. .. .. #surfers #surf #surfing #surfer #waves #surfinglife #beach #surfboard #ocean… https://t.co/pd2Xj3kIRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, mom! (@ Rocco’s At The Brick in Newtown, PA) https://t.co/9CnfCXT8V6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude....you're my friend and all, but you have got to do better than this. It's high school baseball season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Broussard If 2 negatives make a positive, perhaps Melo and CP3 should go play together on a team. Of course… https://t.co/YGaEaGO83T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeerCanInTurn4 @bdheelfan @InsideCarolina @SportsCenter @CollegeGameDay That is why I watch mostly @FS1 @CBSSports… https://t.co/napmCNjwDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The business of float production is fascinating @MardiGrasWorld ! https://t.co/yFQ4jIEClG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President, get that money back from California. Thank you...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arisroussinos That’s interesting , however , it doesn’t address the thorny issue of investigating criminal conduct… https://t.co/svBP8vKyg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting a sentence with "lmao" and ending it with "haha" has become my brand 🙃 ¡lmao someone stop me haha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hungry_husky69 @DDJ384 @davisontigerfan @TeeHodges @steven_edbrooke @WFXGFOX54 Literally the funniest thing ive seen in 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsradiopd @sjgoldstein @BrandonContes Agreed! Have to outline a relative advantage...continuously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would so do this! I’m pretty sure I have in my dreams! #manytimes #😂🤣 #👻 How about you? wickedclothes Thank you S… https://t.co/xz2CI2mRn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!!  I cannot even put into words how proud I am of these boys. No quit in them and they believe in us! Bowen wa… https://t.co/n4fF8nkAlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Divine Reserve No. 19 by @saintarnold @ Flying Saucer Draught Emporium — https://t.co/6YPdHwxRpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Calhoun32 🤔so wld we have announcers who often criticize play calls and decisions during games? What abt spo… https://t.co/to86yOyj0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MySportsUpdate Johnny Manziel shouldn’t be here. He was just plain bad in the NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOING AROUND THE youtube BUILDING SEEING ALL THESE STARS WAS GREAT AND IM BLESSED TO BE IN THAT GREAT ATMOSPHERE...… https://t.co/HbBltYyc2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Famez_vv @Alex_Houseof308 @_Dr90210 @Tife_fabunmi @mrmikerezzy @Mister_Judah @iamvictor__ @motivatedgeorge… https://t.co/Ers4zUVgOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel spoilers without context #GoosetheCat https://t.co/TgWssZmjSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost every ruling from this kangaroo court is overturned by SCOTUS. They are  A SICK JOKE Trump has started repla… https://t.co/am0YuiDPWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neil Armstrong’s space suit 😱👨🏼‍🚀. NBD... @NASASocial #NasaSocial @SpaceX #CrewDragon @NASAKennedy https://t.co/R90ooS68pE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt I don’t remember what I said but titusssawthis thought it was hilarious. #unbreakablekimmyschmidt #netflix ell… https://t.co/gJG7zgT3bR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please come and visit us anytime at   WYNEMA RANCH WILD HORSE SANCTUARY https://t.co/r5zfsAq1NX and HELP where you… https://t.co/KmBxrnpedm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX19Tricia @MikeDardisWLWT @WLWT @ToddDykesWLWT You need to charge your phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyrstensinema @mcccd Ms. Sinema have you attended any of the events, and are there any that you recommend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeTheMessenger Salvation is found not in religion but only in a relationship with Jesus Christ. You must be born a… https://t.co/4kHdlLGZyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been really interesting to see how the Methodist churchs in DC have reacted the anti-LGBTQ vote. Many of the M… https://t.co/2DeQlfgsRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[A LA CAZA DE ROJITOS ESBIRROS ENCHUFAOS Y DEDESTRUCTORES DE VENEZUELA... TODOS SERÁN JUZGADOS POR LOS CIUDADANOS DE… https://t.co/I1mrYKa6iT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotThatMelB @rbnearthesea @_waleedshahid @AOC @justicedems @sunrisemvmt The tax on those with income over $10m is… https://t.co/y72w2TE2rf]]></document></documents></author>