<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Heart shaped grilled cheese and milkshakes with my Valentine's, what more could a girl ask for? ♥️♥️♥️ #myboys… https://t.co/GCL8YBJ3h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashvntid @danghanggg Fruity pebbles are NOT on the same level as licorice and raisins !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SWPSwansea I’m puzzled by this sign.  Do you put it out to promote awareness?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasinAlfredo @CoronerCBC @AdrCMitchell @SerindaSwan @therogercross @EhrenKassam @the_actor_nick What do you mean f… https://t.co/CDXcBmq2tw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PickleAndNancy Happy Whisker Wednesday Pickles and Nancy beautiful sun bathing,all our love Debbie and R.I..P Cinnomon!!😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure my family is trying to kill me with the amount of shots they’re forcing me to take. 😖😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #OccupationalTherapists I know would have something to say about this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Jonas Brothers AND one direction were both making music at the same time i think i would have to quit my job… https://t.co/rF3Z99uZFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[￼  "See us cuddle and hug," say the Pleiades, "All six in a ring: it keeps us warm: We huddle together like birds i… https://t.co/DlSkYo8lCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see how this all plays out when the season ends. We will see what Dazzling Desiree decides! @DRFrancois1 #unlvmbb @UNLV_President]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forget OUTBACK for me. They're in the restaurant business, not politics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jelle_simons @eurog33k @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Don't fret now child the Democrats will protect you ! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The days of December ... @ Staten Island, New York https://t.co/B6MnZmrVqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Friday! Whoot whoot. For 2.3 hours this week I felt caught up. Success!]]></document><document><![CDATA[how can one be so happy but feel there heart breaking at the same time ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating World Music Therapy Day @CHNOLA #musictherapy #worldmusictherapyday2019 #AMTA #musicismylife… https://t.co/mBbbpAqus4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuckyDaPuppyCat @RhondaHendee @lathomas_lynne @KeighleyCatCare @crosseyedollie @RealCatAttack @Jinksandchewie From… https://t.co/2J6GWwFlir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeroyFarley @ChiawanaASB @Chiawana__FCA @Chiawana_RHawks I can see the similarities in your comparison picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seasons tickets since 1971 and today they got court side seats!!  #Dayton6th https://t.co/RaUjhFbhHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to celebrate these awesome @SBISD teachers at the @FirstCommCU and @HoustonTexans Stars in the Classroom ce… https://t.co/dnkcrgSj8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BayArea #sf #blackbabes #piscesseason #bdaymonth  #queerstakeovertwitter https://t.co/1zKX6sNpjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[goodnight. don’t know how I feel about the gmail app re-design but perhaps I like it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Anything you can do I can do better. I can do anything better than you.😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @SideHustleWino @DivaVinophile @FionaMorgan79 @GailBenzler @joneill55 @Starofthesea007 @hmgivingsoul… https://t.co/SEiMmuWkwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[For we through the Spirit wait for the hope of righteousness by faith. https://t.co/5s2Zq7vloF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started eating healthier this week. I’d planned on doing low carb again because I’ve got a weight loss goal to meet… https://t.co/eMTAKcp0rH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiecouric Thanking complete strangers (to 99.99 % of the viewing public) is hardly my idea of entertainment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this man joe just did a backwards somersault in the back of my car while i was driving]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been at work for three hours and I work a double today and I already want to kill my self. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everyone always think something is wrong when someone puts a period at the end of a sentence in a text mes… https://t.co/8CYPVayjen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tessgarman But how many photos did you have to take before this art showed up? XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign the Letter we need peace ☮️ not war https://t.co/Q1vlDYBY1T #SionaSurvival via @PuebloZiobain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StumpToEmerald And dont get me wrong, I can get down with casual and flip flops for certain dates...but 2nd date,… https://t.co/E4CAJWCWBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbarbuto_Ledger @LoriMcKennaMA I ❤️ that song! I worked w @LoriMcKennaMA’s sister 7 days a week all fall... we tal… https://t.co/ZJjzqMmfd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait until my mother wash my hair. Omg. The new growth i have under this sew in is incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why go to 1 drag brunch when you can go to 2 in one morning?! 🥂🥳 #bottomlessmimosas #weho #Drag Brunch #saturday… https://t.co/njrGOG8U6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheetoBandeeto @SonySantaMonica @iamchrisjudge @Sunnysuljic4 @corybarlog @StudstillS @rafagrassetti @mattsophos… https://t.co/3P7nHhouIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christimothy_ @HubSpot Does it work with Zoho mail. I have trouble connecting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinaag74 @Sifichick @chickalea @MattLanter They’re just a bad human. No need to group them in with anyone else you have beef with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my @jamescharles palette is so pretty, I don’t even want to touch the pans 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an absolute treat it was to spend time with @Gurpreet2015 today! Such a generous and humble teacher. Thank you… https://t.co/nCX0p5ur95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Henny!!!!!!!! Coronation 48 is done and over!!!  Here are the looks of the night!  First Look:  👑: #ThorinCo 💇‍♀️ i… https://t.co/7h80Kyissw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have been living in the #House of #Sick for the last week. Between the #flu and whatever other #germs are runnin… https://t.co/qbgB4kqpCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know someone looking for a great #property in #Orlando?   #realestate https://t.co/ic9sH7b7Le]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister, mom and Abuela 81 years young. 💕 . . . #abuela #abuelita #tx #texas #family #familia #blogaboutitall @ T… https://t.co/t5opg6HjZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nike nails it again. Show them what crazy can do Ladies! https://t.co/lhKFz0c1re]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know how many times I’ve been at work and I’m like LMAO DAMN SOMEONE SMELLS LIKE WEED and I feel in my pocke… https://t.co/8GIdod5utQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will leave my bloody drops behind for you to find me into the light again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need a webpage, logo, flyer, brand package or much more... the place to go is @designerjcrosby ! #logo… https://t.co/de0uCJ51Ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Bethany losing her dad and then not getting picked for a solo #ThisIsUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Golden Girls #funniness #snicker #grin #laughable https://t.co/VSgXNlOFYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well. I am new to this Twitter stuff, but I am here to post, show, share, and tell the world who I am. Some already… https://t.co/kPRzmjDq9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that #MichaelCohen has had his chance to spew more LIES, he gets to look forward to a life behind bars! Advice… https://t.co/pusIr8RG5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been watching @TheAmericansFX and it’s been oddly relevant with all the Russian’s cyber action happening today. #historyrepeats]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still nauseous with the chills and my body is shivering. This has been awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 “Give me some more Vodka....This Land is your Land....this Land is my Land.....from California.....2 the… https://t.co/ujYJ33ufHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, white women think drinking wine is a personality trait as well.  “I make wine disappear. What’s your super po… https://t.co/gmxmzxvTRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russellcrowe Hey Russell thought I'd post this. Hope you have a great day. Hope it's not too snowy for you. I don'… https://t.co/EJIa26oDnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta make it through the day hopefully it’ll snow enough and we be off tomorrow 😫🤞🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel @MikeNiccoABC7 @JorgeTWeather @achs_fred LOL. Even at his age?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usatodaylife @USATODAY Why would your editor approve a  writer’s lazy summary of tweets as an appropriate op-ed (o… https://t.co/K5qK3Ews8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 million people live in North Carolina, 9.3 million pigs are on farms in that same state. There are almost more pigs than people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[_wadeiv puts the @raptors905 up 45-43!! @ Raptors905 https://t.co/ymK03WLezY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mood moves in waves.  Happiness to heaviness. Feeling weak to gaining strength. . .  When you think about it- Li… https://t.co/7Q5NOkpdbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevelackmeyer Buy some metal straws and use forever. Dishwasher safe. No shame and cold liquids actually taste colder and better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In which the amazing @221Bcrow renders me in the immortal medium of coffee cup. ☕️❤️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnLong85 I mean don’t get me wrong. I’m a fan of your work but you literally made a video accusing them of fear… https://t.co/GM3dtP0ynI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda crazy how Monday is the beginning of my last nine weeks in high school #wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I log on to twitter one more time and see another tweet hating on @khloekardashian I'm fucking done. We are wome… https://t.co/fHFquqvgkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, legally by law they had a “NON-DISCLOSURE” agreement which she defaulted on! He’s not the only one to… https://t.co/PqLRZ45h5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Henrik is channeling his inner Joe Pavelski today as Captain America. #proudmama #sjsharks #sjsharkie… https://t.co/q7I8oF5OKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta Mission 5k (@ Pemberton Place in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/jHRQ9RFNX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonnniicaaav Los guamuchiles son como bolitas y tienen una semilla adentro idk they’re my fav though I’ll be there next weekend 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WRFG and #AP are Pan-#America Pan-#Russia Pan-#African Pan-#Cuba  #Communists https://t.co/TXZHt5dNTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaaaaaaay estaba comenzando a ver The Favourite y solo ver que esta Emma Stone, hueeeeeeeeva, next.  No hay más actrices ?????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamaiah_Kaleah @rollbluntss thank you bitch because she just wanna be the size of a house by the time we graduate]]></document><document><![CDATA[A tax subsidy of $3B to actually get $27B from Amazon over 10 years.  Why doesn’t AOC understand?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeDHernandez1 @nbcsnl @IamSandraOh @tameimpala I was wondering then same thing myself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You qualify for senior citizen's discounts. #SignYouKnowYoureGettingOlder https://t.co/MFIRJQOaHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad the kids got mad at me. I’m glad that I will always have common courtesy. I’m glad that the adults respect… https://t.co/sW0mViwN50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun mall!! #fox valley mall #dupagecounty #naperville #napervilleillinois #midwest #mall #malls #stores #80small… https://t.co/da7gJ1rf2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Crush a Culture of Entitlement DON’T: - hand people things they haven’t earned - lower your standards - tole… https://t.co/3FWTCeKrey]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do they warm up those #school buses in these #cold temps? I've got the details next on @KOAA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djrothkopf @GrainOfSands @DavidCornDC @MotherJones @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/a05z5CergC]]></document><document><![CDATA[نماینده ولی‌فقیه در سپاه:اعتماد به آمریکا و اروپا هزینه زیادی را به مردم تحمیل کردhttps://t.co/DxiKgWth8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oficialmente el FC Barcelona tiene otra nueva casa: https://t.co/wzD3QpROTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming July 2019... hi roomie👋🏼 czoller05 📍Blacksburg, VA @ Blacksburg, Virginia https://t.co/TmfZVD9tHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send it HDR III App Launch Event.. This app will bring much needed awareness to safety conditions for ATV/Snowmobil… https://t.co/F3RUJNZ9Or]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night a random dude, in random conversation asked me..   “Well how are you gonna do comedy and have babies”… https://t.co/oFB9gUv0uS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SequoiaTreee @kitcso @Solmemes1 @greggutfeld JESUS WAS NOT AN IMMIGRANT.... He was conceived by God in the womb of… https://t.co/1t4wW3Vl4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erika is going to go to the state competition ❤️🎊👍 (@ Westlake High School in West Lake Hills, TX) https://t.co/PMKnMHujAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyinternationalwomansday❤  to all the ladies out there! May we continue to love each other, love ourselves, kno… https://t.co/1ChTpw5ntv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOSHY_W4SHY @NFL @_Antoinetteeeee @Seahawks @Shaquemgriffin No.  I can see the NFL breaking their necks to get her… https://t.co/HRsb8ubilH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sooo glad we are done with youth 🏈 🙏🙏 for my youngest son!!! #WeHighSchoolBound]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lying wide awake at 4am so I can make the bags under my eyes my most prominent feature]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t usually feel old but yesterday i fell on the ice and today my entire body is sore. anyway, where do i sign up for social security?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcelhenri5 @CBSNews The reason I say this ,Is someone is always going to be butt hurt about this kind of stuff a… https://t.co/JmvFJc7kqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okeybams @ballamingie @NatGeo @gatesfoundation every small effort amplifies others &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now my mom is telling me how she has her outfit planned out for my wedding 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_ima @epigmenioibarra Si no vas a decir nada inteligente mejor cállate,  hablar mal de los demás, solo habla mal de ti]]></document></documents></author>