<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DrStevenGreer if aliens are concerned about our hostility,why don’t they just go elsewhere? The universe is fairly… https://t.co/WWwZvps8U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder to start our week.  We are at school to help.  #MyWhy https://t.co/AzYfsSgDa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be my Valentine?  The overcast skies made a beautiful soft-box for Macro Photography, so I stopped after work to ge… https://t.co/ft5yMdQ5uG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/dOKLwZCQ32]]></document><document><![CDATA[My British #wejo colleagues getting ready for a #ucf #ucfknights #ucfbasketball game. #top25 @ University of Centra… https://t.co/VVdFXDuEjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickiknowsnada @CoWildlifePhoto Somehow I’m having a hard time feeling any empathy for Maniford.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @TomSteyer Do you honestly think you have the character to make me believe there was “no collision?” Yo… https://t.co/0ko6uCMF2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@UArkansas system delivers $2.2 billion economic boon to #Arkansas’ economy, report says - @TBArkansas  https://t.co/a3VckYTTIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This same energy keeps me constantly on the defense and ready to apologize at a moments notice]]></document><document><![CDATA[This montage is awesome and very welcome. MISSION IMPOSSIBLE AND MR. RODGERS LOVE!! #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[[different species of lesser cat]  Me: ok, I can see it  [different species of Diptera (flies)]  Me: what the fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geraldwolfe1 23 years ago today I gave my heart the Lord #savedtotheuttermost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupremeOne3 Dude everyone has on Canada goose or moncler those are like $1000 jackets fools go ham , moncler with… https://t.co/2eK2knTkbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve all felt this, wether it be not having trust, distance, time, effort, we all have felt like this song. I’ve l… https://t.co/9ohN4g81AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[JURISDICTION AUTHORITY INCORPORATED BASE WEAPON SYSTEM AND OWNERS ALL NOT LEGAL BY AMERICAN STANDARD LAWS AND CONST… https://t.co/pbwwm3K3wj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discovered a new “practice area” in my neighborhood yesterday.  Tall grass so best to keep an eye on your ball the… https://t.co/uulCTUzHcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPBiggie We will forever be missed. Just know your fans are still with you BIG. https://t.co/Zay5OBcmcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzzi4u @EdKrassen Calling him stupid is one thing, disrespectful at best but I guess respect went out the window… https://t.co/yI2Oyg9meI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#grabthemiccomedy is back this Monday with yours truly hosting. This is a dope lineup of up and coming comedians th… https://t.co/md7rV1BUgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump The drugs come in through ports of entry for the most part. Bigger walls will do no… https://t.co/GTWGOau2r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going live playing #7DaysToDie. New World New Game. Game seed UzumatiWarriorNation. Catch me live at https://t.co/ykNVYZULhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people have slept on him, but he's been on my radar since 2017]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MediaFail come on press corps , eye on the ball re priorities #SecurityClearances #MarALagoMadam]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re hugging. @lovinhistory @mitchjonesreal #noottershere https://t.co/e0AUtki1zY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier this month, I had the pleasure of sitting down with @GamecockFB WR Deebo Samuel. With the receivers partaki… https://t.co/NuvEkEiPds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff We must confront #climatechange. We must not allow Trump’s climate denial to weaken our national enviro… https://t.co/vbJ9st3QQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you gotta close the garages close the school. I can’t get to class if I can’t park.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbykleeK @maddiesullivan1 google it , lol   its nothing that bad , but it easier for you to just google it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m betting AB going from the Steelers to the Bills will end up being one of the most infamous ways an all time gre… https://t.co/MlQsxVtoOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do ya ever go back in your mind and think. " Boy I wish I hadn't tweeted that." Donny? Oh that's right. You have a… https://t.co/wRMgd93Zlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @MichaelCohen212 : “The more people that follow Mr. Trump as I did, blindly, are going to suffer t… https://t.co/fVkP19HIOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ballentine1037 @Super70sSports Don’t forget Hairston and Dandrudge who are also in the shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_williams The kindle version on dark background has close to unreadle dark blue headings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @WSJopinion Someone needs to teach me how I,too, can profit off of my foolishness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @gracietpt A banner like that might as well read: The resident of this house is stupid, racist, an… https://t.co/IF67wNqSmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trump starts a nuclear war out of spite, a majority of the Republican Party will blame Democrats for making him… https://t.co/crWacjbzi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillLang @SenThomTillis I called his office yesterday &amp; recorded my dissent. I hope other North Carolinians do the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattwaxman1 @carriecordero Sadly Matthew, those days ended with Trump’s election]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯💯☝🏻☝🏻☝🏻☝🏻🎼🎼🎸🎸🎸🎺🎺🎺🎤🎤🥃🥃🥃🥃🥃🥃 @ Shenandoah County, Virginia https://t.co/bwfhMAJPV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer went bad - Drinking a Cinnabull by @BoleroSnort @ Barrister Cigars  — https://t.co/YiI81lQMzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrestonLewis8 @Goose003 Do you have a direct hot line where people can call in because with all ur knowledge on sports you really need one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ South Lake Tahoe, California https://t.co/TFGJizcLiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFFMen @OnlyFans #onlyfans #justforfans #4myfans @GAYADULTSONLY @AmateurBBack subscribe 4 ONLY 8 BUCKS to fan page… https://t.co/hGWhF5fWDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[YEAH WELL I'VE BEEN SAYING EXACTLY THIS FOR YEARS - Pew: Phone polling in crisis again https://t.co/UCQ8LbgfD6 via @politico]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_picazo @MaximeBernier Or maybe we don't like Liberals soft-selling sex to our children... https://t.co/XNXfcobQoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying that God will be glorified &amp; that lives will be changed during the @RSCCBCM mission trip https://t.co/8D0ICiQfLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos actores eh! Ya parecen como @josefriverap y sus chistes sin sentido! @jpereznavarro @ZonaEspn @pilarperezr 😂… https://t.co/k7IG5tV584]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion should end his Duke season early &amp; focus on the NBA draft - Scottie... https://t.co/7qkNRoFhYN via @TBM929]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloe It feels great!   I’m sure  many people need your beauty and kind soul Khloe💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @HillTVLive I agree with you partially but Trump had no idea about Foreign policy yet he is President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you just say you weight 110lbs and enter @GoZwift Nationals and crush everyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Wrapping up this probe means very little. It’s more than probable that bar had to promise Trump he wo… https://t.co/zMgl54GvvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamAhsoka Kelly (assuming that’s your real name and if not, whoops), I’ve now watched the video game trailer at L… https://t.co/zorKq6ljVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last line of defence: after today's "discussion", no longer can trust a single person for anything anymore. ANYONE.… https://t.co/zdDamVFTH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longballgirl @metrikk @KellyTownsend11 @noprezzie2012 @DanSerrano2 @JamesTHarris @Broomhead its...on....video😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElisaJaffe Here is an advanced copy of Michael Cohens testimony.  https://t.co/kbVtaHb2RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbt with my Best Barber Instructor Mr. Ron Koziel.... #tbt #bestmentor #bestbarber #instructor #bestteacher #mentor… https://t.co/enezlotAwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeraMBergen @MalcolmNance I thought DJT reset the day before leaving, that he would demand Kim pinkie swear to not be mean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACreativeMuggle @jodikantor As part of the settlement from World War I, Germany was required to repay half the war… https://t.co/qMZpFUEnWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living with your girlfriend means there is no line of defense between her and your sweatshirts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eskalia @Tyjet @CheckpointXP @UnderTale I don't refuse I just been playing other stuff 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_AM_WILDCAT @IzamiTV Gah damn, I’ve seen some people destroyed, but this is on a new level]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitchbartol1 @CoachNiekamp @Coach_Spack @McNamaraRivals @travisWSN @AllenTrieu Congrats Bartol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting story at halftime, about the Arizona Hotshots and why they’re called that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esteyx I put in an app for the clan, if you could put in a good word for me. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[since he tweeted this, we established that nobody can really out drink me 😂 but I don’t like drinking so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russbengtson Dammit. I haven’t achieved enough to fill two, let alone 20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 classic 😄 snow on the Big Isle AF hb https://t.co/6oSaEKCAMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estraudi1 @noprezzie2012 @queerdawn @Supt_Hoffman @SenQuezada29 @GLSEN they love consensus science....what we used to call superstition]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cinema Wasteland Retro Double Feature Movie Night #3 - THIS SATURDAY, 7:00 p.m., at The Berea Elks Lodge #1815… https://t.co/FyjoKi1k2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjchoppy @coachkelton417 @1053SS And saying Mookie Betts “isn’t that good” certainly wasn’t one of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobDKall @keelyn_kotecki @fendinutsock we just have to add in a really big and overweight person now 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lchancepsu @KaliaReynolds On the day that I post a dystopian fantasy novel about video games, you post Bonhoeffer.  Awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliLake How and why did Pirro go off the rails so badly? She has become a howling far right jackal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWErickson Yet you continue to support this insensitive, disrespectful, man-child who echoes whatever the dictator du jour is saying. Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcharlesworth7 Morning..... my favorite time on Saturday....   lol... btw nice color hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElFinanciero_Mx Están como los taxistas y Uber el publico decide con quien]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Cam Clark on his first round victory at IHSA State Wrestling. #ibtigerpride @ib327athletics https://t.co/i6tIUszHBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amberella06 A sponge bath with special attention paid to certain parts of your anatomy... I was laughing at the bl… https://t.co/tBRuWAYrLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dominicci13 papá es que esa tipa mientras más buena se pone, más le pone a su forma, cero poses, siempre en rabia.. lo que todos soñamos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HistorianGab @nonsense_PW @luther_bj @NPR Here's some history that might open some eyes: https://t.co/gs1vMUS8nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the bright side got a huge blessing today and I’m very grateful for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOHO REBELLION x @volant_magazine . . . Models @adamdeso @cyyppp  Makeup/Skin zoliartistry  Photographer whitneyott… https://t.co/1FSeETm1iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work 3-11. Day 1 of 5. (@ ROCKTENN-Mishawaka,IN. in Mishawaka, IN) https://t.co/dTL5g4oV81]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @KC1stDistrict keeps giving our road resurfacing $ to organizations that dont do road resurfacing we'll all be p… https://t.co/PUKipNnQ0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggsacks @jaykisokay i accidentally bought little fires everywhere paperback but LARGE FONT. everyone reads with me on the metro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanDolan Keep on keepin on brother! If real talk makes folks cringy, they're just weak and uncomfortable with th… https://t.co/Bkt5zB5b2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched the @NHRA #ProStock show. I was impressed with the coverage that emphasized the relatability of the… https://t.co/TtYZNygq17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikeysurf @diidlake @_ThatDudeWill It’s amazing how many people that don’t see that]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are under way at Cimpl Arena with the Great Plains Conference Clash at the Mount. Avon and Colome playing the fi… https://t.co/5njx33SLVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misleadia @bigredwavenow @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @WhiteHouse @SecretService @NSAGov @jkiddrock… https://t.co/NYihq3Gj1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then on the flip there’s this written word inspiration- 💪🏽☎️📞👂🏼  1-900- BreakUOff -EPMD - Symphony 2000 ft. Redman,… https://t.co/Nv5RdW8vD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brueggers 5° in Arden Hills, MN. The North Oaks location is a stone's throw away. https://t.co/7M8ikOxU8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[#leprechaun showed up for class yesterday. 😁😎😜 #havefun #life #selfie @ Charleston, Illinois https://t.co/dpQeLx6N9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Champ himself Mr.ApexLegend is back #ChampIsHere @PlayApex #ApexLegends #ChampionsLeague  #Xbox @EA @CouRageJD… https://t.co/T9FGm7KOW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRochaSays @Samsung Not much consumer 8K content yet though. By the time there is the tv model you were looking… https://t.co/Ejv233M0KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/ When people are fanatically dedicated to political or religious faiths or any other kinds of dogmas or goals, it… https://t.co/3kxhVHY9lV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that enjoys buying books almost more than reading them ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @realDonaldTrump Do you also wander around all day humming “If I Only Had a Brain”? We all know Dumby Donald does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ONTSpecialNeeds Remember, nothing will be as difficult, complicated, or bad as Our anticipation suggests, 110% of… https://t.co/EhEXwvgAHz]]></document></documents></author>