<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[These women working here today are making miracles happen! @americanair (@ American Ticket Counter in Newark, NJ) https://t.co/3f8fJiTw0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a #twin...the constructive feedback is 24/7. No one better to point out your flaws...than the one who… https://t.co/2itpSULxCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open availability!!  . . . . . #eyes #hudabeauty #lashtech #minklashes #makeuplover #eyebrows #beautiful… https://t.co/CGv2dydSWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[my moms ex husband is sitting at the bar and I want to die SOS @savysavsav @T_Filippello]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love all of the casts of Arrow. But, these are my most favorite of all!!! https://t.co/oa0AWiWVbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[May your day be as pleasant and bright as this #flower  #park #nature #photography  #shotoniphone  #SanMarcos… https://t.co/MRRG69xL15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityNews 4 years and 1 month???  “Ya gotta be kidding me.” Marco Muzzo got 10 years for DUI killing 4 people. Some… https://t.co/9ea8HKitq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[ya girl got some chocolate covered strawberries and I couldn’t be any happier 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you on the Music Strip later, Miss @JoCurrie so you can get your quality Birthday pressie. 😁 https://t.co/n4o8E40Nwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASimplePatriot She is seeing confidential info that maybe she should not be allowed since her connections to Musli… https://t.co/Vmdi0guZWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLaYBoYKeNxX_2 We will definitely go this week. Can’t be today tho, gotta be with Presh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much of the Steele Dossier has been Corroborated, Nothing has been Refuted  https://t.co/nwXRfPEkSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toy Story 3. My kiddo is heading off to college this fall and when he was two he dressed up as Woody for Halloween;… https://t.co/oEIvD2cjmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[PT THAT SPIT ON ME, THREATEN TO KILL ME &amp; THREW WATER AT ME IS BACK]]></document><document><![CDATA[remind me never to go to the grocery store before a huge storm again I don’t have the patience people were  running… https://t.co/l8ZtWI4xDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the best time of year to expand and tighten up #reading instruction while planning ahead for next year. Her… https://t.co/PhkT83IBbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is NO verdict yet in the case against Buffalo Police Officer Corey Krug. The jury wants to hear more testimony. @WKBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mini slices breads are by far the best component of @ChexMix. End of discussion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[College is gonna be hard??? Wow that’s amazing I would have never known thanks for mansplaining that to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP_Politics It’s the new KAFA campaign. Keep America Fat Always. Big AG and Big Pharma love this. That’s who actua… https://t.co/xS3AzZTJgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My $3 Franklin Computer Word Wiz is off to to an interesting start https://t.co/55Ped5tBlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newsbeastnick @IssuesOn1 @YorbaLindaCity @SpecNews1SoCal @alexcoheninla Thanks for having me on the show @newsbeastnick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Love @GameOfClonesMTV #GameOfClones  especially with @DJPaulyD #DJPaulyD  and @KailLowry #KailLowry]]></document><document><![CDATA[bringing this back to the timeline for international women’s day, so damn powerful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sausage_Leg_Joe @JMVV1385 @RepDanCrenshaw CNBC cnn fortune magazine. Sure there’s more. End of dec probe cost $25.… https://t.co/EUdYZ2ZytW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petersonpat17 @IlhanMN Utes she should lose her citizenship and sent back to het country, she's a mean hearted woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just SOME of the times fb has arrested me. mind you most of the times i was arrested was for posting SCIENTIFIC JOU… https://t.co/AOgBx1PDzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO lmfaoooo why am I really like that?! Idk if I feel attacked or understood. 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernandoPinna1 @opropriolavo @jairbolsonaro Kkkkkkk https://t.co/uD6CyHIHTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyDatelineEpisodeIn5Words When @dateline_keith called in sick.  😭 https://t.co/JX8TSTzt55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovAbbott I only vote for lottery because funds were to be used for school but the stopped state funding not the deal 😱😱😱😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Stay strong my sistah and continue speaking truth to power. Do not stand down. I support you 200%. Racists… https://t.co/iJBvjlC8ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closed out the weekend with dishes, hugs, and tears of joy. What an incredible journey 💗🥰🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS  tell the truth.  You’re a very bad man.  Melania is who I feel the worse for  and Baron....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had both, Jonas brothers since 6th grade &amp; big time rush freshman year okkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best days of 2019.  Sightseeing in @washingtondc with @moekolee and REH after presenting at #ASPA2019 on… https://t.co/3aUMKs0u7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobLonsberry So important to know our history. It only got worse after 1865.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie: My dad showed up *traveled across the world and casually knocked on my door* at my hotel room.   Colton: *d… https://t.co/SVFfAHy4A8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letatianosky 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣está mujer 😘😘😘😘me mata de la risa 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🌹🌹🌹 https://t.co/sn8YCwgHbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The nice thing about the @DrakeBulldogsMB throwback unis is the throwback color. My alma mater has enough trouble g… https://t.co/8QVRKwoHJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reymundo_Ortiz1 @Winston_ES Thank you @Reymundo_Ortiz1 and @JamieMcBee for leading this session and sharing your l… https://t.co/0SGeYKGWGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how Niall always takes the time of day to respond and tweet some of us back, I really appreciate it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marygribbin809 @thehill You are a disgrace. Crawl back under your rock 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you hear that it’s actually going to be above freezing this weekend?? I’m as shocked to hear this as Lea!… https://t.co/Ao02mFuo5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[who has a tattoo that someone wrote for them? if you have one please dm me i have questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been in bed rest for like 4 weeks and my neighbors have only had one fight... as soon as I go back to work the… https://t.co/XlMMYaUJCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QH3hJvYpDU - After owner's tweets, many sour on his apple farm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi He's on some kind of #amphetamine probably for his weight but now got hooked on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamosumSihammm @monk_moha @TAASAA1756 @CristinPereyra @r95731 @lauragarciabou @OcasoUn @Silviadomi22G… https://t.co/kaI8Wt9Asj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowBack #SleekSkinette #RedskinsDivaGroup #HTTR4LIFE #Hail2TheYeah @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/fBGYU2dAdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[these night sweats are annoying as hell let me tell you  a n n o y i n g]]></document><document><![CDATA[#somedays #inkedpoet #poetry #bipolarmoods #aloneinacrowd #jrc #bipolar #borderlinepersonalitydisorder @ Lawton, Ok… https://t.co/f6cpw2vKxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You’re too much”  Says someone who clearly doesn’t know me. I’m quite easy to get, once you get it. You get it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kya Dukes with a triple after an offensive rebound to pull Purcell Marian within three at 31-28 with seven minutes remaining. #cincyhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamLukas3 @grailsnail @Lazulioness @nprpolitics Dems in Congress will have to draw up a Bill for funding the MASSI… https://t.co/ZaPYFShpBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmeraldRobinson @Maxineskrazy Wishful thinking. They’ll get away with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalkingDead_AMC Think I would do exactly what Daryl did and send her home first then save her later]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_v It was my Sr yr of HS and I’d just gotten to campus after a morning of cc classes. It was lunch and I remember… https://t.co/yO5OA28MUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Automotive Service Technician" at Reno Hyundai? Apply even if you're not a 100% ma… https://t.co/p9fm7aZdc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord knows i needed the rain to stop for this. ☀️🐴💛 #MyEscape #SundayFarmDay #OleGreg https://t.co/rpGX73jjqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Why in God’s name do @SenateGOP not support our President, are they as evil &amp; demonic as @SenateDems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hartwelljetski @LionwithaLamb @charliekirk11 Well, proof of life for one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @JonLionFineArt Omg I was so saddened to hear hear about Katherine!! my heart n prayers go out you,… https://t.co/1z2DCcQSqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop Recycling Plastic Bottles Without Caps On https://t.co/itqaxEVDhh via @lifehacker #TheMoreYouKnow #Recycle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study guides and teacher folders ready to go for EDWARD TULANE School Shows tomorrow! ⭐️🐰💫 @vytphoenix #vytphoenix… https://t.co/u7zFypTwSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Sandra’s will from Thursday night when she fell on her head at American Junkie and thought she was gonna di… https://t.co/TRM2zy9nJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyjanning @AmandaCUInsight  and I really appreciated your Ron Weasley #dadjoke today 👏🏼 https://t.co/JsWafKftcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would have thought Colton would be one of the most stand up bachelors! he knew the minute he fell in love with… https://t.co/nwvPs70kqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else ever suffer from vertigo and have any tips to get rid of it???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump It's a shame they've wasted 2 years trying to get him thrown out office because of bein… https://t.co/M7VnxogfGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ameliaaaaaa11 it adds to the sense of sleep deprivation, so you’re good!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so okay with what’s about to happen i just hate that you’re okay with it too🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[But in all seriousness...I missed my little fat man so much🖤🖤🖤 #ozzyosbarnes https://t.co/RM9zk6FuHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @honeystonemusic with get_repost ・・・ We're back this Friday, 3/15 at @mercuryloungeny with @KendallStreetCo… https://t.co/FDspTQpcMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@VP, how is someone free when they don’t have reproductive freedom, which is essential to economic opportunity?  H… https://t.co/vm85w1ronr]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi we had an extra hour of rehearsal and did 3 full run throughs  my body hurts #NevadaWinterGuard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas Says Most of Its Students Aren’t Reading at Grade Level. But Are Its Tests Fair? https://t.co/iy5nSxZ2im]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shower this morning was for nothing. I’ve sweated like I ran a marathon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaffiganshow @tvland Waiting for 15 minutes of Walter Cronkite, the news is now reality tv “entertainment.”  Thanks Rupert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Why did Cohen never come forth with any of this information until now #Liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TirathPatelMD @gabrieldane @CubaLibrePHL @LatinasInMed @TirathPatelMD - It is one of the closest approximations in… https://t.co/wLKkcXm0VT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MickieSherwood I really hope you and M. Obama took the same flight to the Oscars and save the taxpayers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSelter @Sib_Vicious You just felt like retweeting a fat ass tonight, Sib? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump One thing that never changes is the lies that come from your lips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to a great day. Teamwork makes the dream work. 🙂 #SXSW @Emily_Espo @WalleriusK @MarcIacono2 https://t.co/1yM4KwecHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually I take that back… Mohammed Bone Saw. And Erdogan. More I’m sure. Just no Latinos that I’ve ever heard of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ô, Sunlight! The most precious gold to be found on Earth.” 🌞 -Roman Payne #vacationmode #goodforthebrain 🌞 https://t.co/M2NjpD5mNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so happy to share this lifesyle birthday shoot of my best friend's baby including a behind the scenes video of… https://t.co/NRWZXyhjO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/aLFk1ZjGNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcspocky The problem is if his followers take to the streets they all have guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night team dinner with some great peeps I have the pleasure to call friends. #pittsburgh #pittsburghautoshow… https://t.co/T6IsHYv6pR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My love for expensive clothing ...well...fashion as a whole is a curse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul It's time to back the President and get that wall built!!  If congress is against him you show you're for him!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That TRX triceps exercise is NO joke. 💪 It’s been a couple weeks since I did that particular exercise. My triceps a… https://t.co/Zt4XXDxDFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is Mahgdalen Rose? John B finds out... https://t.co/8sgdFe7GNi via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my boyfriend ever proposes to me he better hide that ring real good. Just because I’m so nosy all time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sick of politicians and celebrities getting special treatment. No reduction. He pays it all or his sorry ass s… https://t.co/a0TTK5b1uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@popcallit @javitagracia @JessicaValenti This the argument against smoking in Public.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So This is How the rest of the World 🌎 See USA 🇺🇸;( I fear the Aliens 👽 would just run.. saying “ There is No Intel… https://t.co/Zwl6wIsJ3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLeeZeldin @HouseForeign So Steve King, Steve Scalise, Jim Jordan, and of course Trump is ok. Got it. You are a hypocrite!]]></document></documents></author>