<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[if u got a valentine card from me today, i hope it made u smile :( &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedawson @ParisJackson I don't believe these charges against Michael. Why do this now? Why do this when he can't defend himself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman He’s a liberal rules don’t apply to them the same way that apply to a conservative!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@takeabiteofthat @prairielive @essenviews @RoyBlunt @GOP Since Nixon, as far as I can remember. And it's gotten extremely blatant lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar @elfcosmetics I just watched this video and its looks awesome! I'm gonna go buy these and try to follo… https://t.co/xBkES9xR5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactamente como el de Cuba donde el bienestar de todos lo ha garantizado el sistema socialista. Por eso millones e… https://t.co/krb8neEdcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Segundo martes en el que me @mesalebien estar triste. Triste de estar a más de 1Gm(giga metro) de la CDMX y no pode… https://t.co/vAz14rKQWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The roof over my head, I bought.  The car I have, I bought.  The food on my table, I bought.  The clothes I wear, I… https://t.co/Csr29khjzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good boy. @ Old North Boulder, Boulder, Colorado https://t.co/cQ2HUSvWlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just playful. All the Amazing, Empowering Things Melissa McCarthy Has Said #funniness #chuckle… https://t.co/Tce3D8ZcS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 I take every single suicide threat seriously , no matter what ; and I’m always viewed as a cunt for it . But… https://t.co/CgVyoIPiYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve read a ton on best practices regarding coaching millennials. This list is as succinct as it gets! Take out the… https://t.co/sfZQHVSrw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone PLEASE tell me why I’m always at the bar even if I’m not working...🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[in other news im the worst texter like if you get texts back from me within the HOUR, you’re a lucky one]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s another person in need in this challenging world. I donated to 'Mel's Fight Against Astrocytoma' -… https://t.co/G9BcGaHY0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CivilEats @CivilEats Check out #GroundWar at @dceff_org how activists around world are fighting pesticide industry… https://t.co/59emmBrBMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤓Thinking outside the box: 🙃... Since my #specialneeds #lilbro mygraypants  is unable to sit still for a haircut...… https://t.co/c66FmQGeOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpryGuy “The truth, it is felt, becomes untruth when your enemy utters it.”   ― George Orwell https://t.co/KswUxLSMmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty buzzed it i wish i could express my love to everyone without it lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward, the most sophisticated feline. #edwardlyle #rescuecats #jonesstreetsavannah #10East #kimlylesstaging… https://t.co/k9g8NJHnLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @billieeilish sings “if we were meant to be we would have been by now” OOH that’s a killer line right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ye was a good album in my opinion . Despite all of the controversy at that given time with Kanye’s image, it was a great project.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Glarus ms/hs lunch options from last Friday. @ New Glarus, Wisconsin https://t.co/dyF7CnDeFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generations of this knowledge are shared through the wisdom traditions. 🙏🕉 Thank you @DalaiLama @homeofhopeindia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our outstanding BA Algebra 1 Team collaborating and thinking outside of the box to ensure success for students at a… https://t.co/V13jaClEfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torihatesyou @wtmort LOL I’m probably on my own for that one. This week 2 have to go! I’m so excited! Because I fe… https://t.co/fsMhDsVrmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is just Camille ❤️#illustration #artistsoninstagram #artistsontumblr #photoshop #dogsofinstagram #rescuedog… https://t.co/bAxEPxaf77]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion will win it but Cassius means the most to his team and deserves it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally got my hair trimmed a week ago &amp; i made an appointment to chop it off a week later ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld I am afraid that is the ultimate deflection #TrumpRICO  #TrumpRICO #TrumpRICO  #TrumpRICO  #TrumpRICO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my son with all my heart and soul. I am sad because he struggles with autism. He is considered high function… https://t.co/r4sIhm7oYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm proud of my attention to detail and I consider it one of my strengths. My passion for editing shouldn't be take… https://t.co/mftzz3WudP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another phenomenal Gem Show this year with a few of my favorites and sweetest loves! Until next year ~ ❤️ #Tucson… https://t.co/EPPyjlTf4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yesterday my shoulders and neck started hurting. Right now it hurts to touch my shoulders and I can not move my… https://t.co/ZqfTBw74P7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IAmTheNight 🥴🥴🥴🥴 that was from last week’s episode. About to watch tonight’s new episode! It’s so good. Does anyon… https://t.co/SDXFYoJUul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmick66 @PattyWheeler12 @nypost No one is sacred to this foreign name caller.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieJaneDuff McCabe isn't an asset anywhere ! His wife is more of an asset than he.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living in Los Angeles changes your opinion of the #Oscars real fast. So many people here are connected to the “indu… https://t.co/XQba17HTtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Shelby, NC? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Associate Logist… https://t.co/kcJ6qCcsaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a delay meaning my chem exam has been postponed! https://t.co/2t0TiJAqlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horses in danger? Former Wells Fargo VP demanding changes in iconic stagecoach program after claims of horse abuse.… https://t.co/cO6xCRk1D2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about the best testifying scenes in history and I’m partial to this one https://t.co/UkPgpx09kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you want the rainbow, you have to put up with the rain.” 🌦🌈💕 #DollyParton #Dumplin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmorein @webgirlmorgan @hillaryborden I usually use “Its a good thing you’re pretty, hun...” totally dripping with sarcasm. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[But with an overflowing flood he will make a complete end of the adversaries, and will pursue his enemies into dark… https://t.co/83Aeuotpem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneRN79 @RoundRockTim Taco Bell is easily the best of the cheap national fast food restaurants. Value, taste, veg… https://t.co/wu00Dps4yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crazymom50 @lucyRoseReedus @linalan96 @emikoko896 @annedo55 @ldavisusa @RehFurttado @justmel_li @wendy_talmage… https://t.co/QJDroZPaX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the authentic and genuine people in the music industry. And also one of BEST performers to touch a stage but… https://t.co/w49EjczKWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Trump is not a legitimate president. He is the imbecile of our age. Congress must acknowledge and rea… https://t.co/VcNIXHLqIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a fever and feel like garbage!!! Let's see how many episodes (seasons?) of new girl I can watch on Netflix until I feel better!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m bipolar, which means I’m actually both of the twins from the shining, not just a loud one. https://t.co/66BJFeeNE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch said she grew up watching baby boy and still got pregnant by Jodi that’s by far the funniest shit I’ve heard a baby momma say 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Course selections for next year have begun @MPSSBlueDevil Please see Guidance and check our website.… https://t.co/pUbMAmiq5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use my code below so I can make some cash for my wedding debt people...lol Sign up and get up to $20! https://t.co/93i0XooPD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @RepAdamSchiff @RepJerryNadler I remember long ago (it seems) when you described Adam Schiff as a former… https://t.co/TPe1GGdhTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[March Giveaway is up| Picture will be posted later today!!  Go watch the video NOW! Link is in my bio!!  ——————————… https://t.co/laQ7yga3HM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benzie55 @wilkim1971 @alysa_apollonia @skipandpete @ann2156 @ki_native @quisqueyana1102 @Tia_Lunes @Sammy_Markle… https://t.co/XozsYkr1GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am mad at myself! I took this out of the box to put together. Pushing directions aside as usual....I put 2 pieces… https://t.co/YP6LODUUKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking foward to lot's of videos pictures posts from @madonna after #Ocars bash . @guyoseary @julieroot4 https://t.co/UmF0qLZFLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[TY @thecarlarossi for an #amazing #weekend in #Portland @hollywoodtheatr #vincentprice #soldout moviemadnesspdx tra… https://t.co/PMJnzNHYxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to religious reasons, I am giving up caring for the next 40 days #Lent #Lent2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never be anyone to you, I’ll remain broken to you, and I’ll never try to be next to you... I promise you that much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EHomeschoolHelp Absolutely. And the toll it can take on your own mental and physical health is real too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LascoFrancis @RealJamesWoods Border Patrol thinks that number will be 100,000 in March, while dems fight anything… https://t.co/JYvROaseiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AcademicTwitter, Do any of y’all use a rubric for your teaching self-evaluations and/or teaching observations? If… https://t.co/xegEbSfdIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then i got a message tonight saying we have hidden your post ...i am shocked and my son came home at 11 cat was out… https://t.co/50VzOk6KGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it didnt quite work his folks thy just quit then Danny took a look 𝒾𝓃𝓈𝒾𝒹𝑒 𝑜𝒻 𝒾𝓉 There was a great big flash ev… https://t.co/cXjHab7j1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@777KAB1 Something tells me we’re getting closer and closer to one heck of a BOOM! 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras, everyone! What’s your costume? How will you spend Carnival Day? Be safe, have fun, everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Train Your Dragon 3 (@ Regal Cinemas Marysville 14 - @regalmovies in Marysville, WA) https://t.co/87FeLVmDiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be mindful of who you forgive that hasn’t given you an apology...no apology means that they thought you deserved what they did to you 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask @DonaldJTrumpJr he may know the answer.  He was upset about teachers indoctrinating students-maybe he will have… https://t.co/2K8mfv3z26]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you see me trying to walk off the elevator why would you force yourself in when you see my trying to get out...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingLRG_ Had to choose a gif from one of my favorite movies 😂 https://t.co/4FFVN4TWRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eva in set of an upcoming photoshoot for a magazine.  📷 @RussellBaer  👙 @Lindamedvene  💄 beauty_by_hidi… https://t.co/2s2Cz48oyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be spazzing out tbh I ignore it till one day I wake up in a bad mood then all of a sudden I’m telling some random… https://t.co/waH8gGfrkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I completely forgot that this month marks one year since we last spoke. Everyone told me “it get easier as time goe… https://t.co/Q2pIyYQYh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[the worst part about being friends with riley and regan is thag i’ve started to talk like them... if you’ve ever he… https://t.co/DoSg9rtXA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn sure hope so.  He has gone off the deep end.  He also looks frazzled. KOMPROMAT?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink Floyd's Waters slams Venezuela border aid concert | Article [AMP] | Reuters https://t.co/eHr6e3Tv3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this program. We all need more KT!  Sign up @SickKidsNews #SKLearning @ronald_cohn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime I don't care what Beauregard says. Tell the dear sir the Civil War is over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bekind #NorrisKind #Proud2bMPS We do love green eggs and ham Sam I am! https://t.co/okUIsmn0ZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholasAHowell This is great to see! Will for sure read more. Thanks for sharing 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebtown The same Pacific Storms affecting you are hitting us repeatedly. We’re downstream 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time of the year.  The real March Madness!!! https://t.co/achRkNmtdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kypmom @SpeakerPelosi I also think there is a specific strategy that we haven't seen yet. She is not knee-jerking… https://t.co/Qz059rXQx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[New skincare products with @yesto! 😍💖 ✨ Yes To Grapefruit Vitamin C Glow-Boosting Unicorn mask⠀ ✨ Yes To PrimRose O… https://t.co/PofMYcb26H]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will not silence me. I feel blessed that State Sen Flowers stood her ground for children in Arkansas. You. Will… https://t.co/EcDTaLTn67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me going through the quiz: I know I didnt study, but these seem like common sense questions. Probably got another 8… https://t.co/bUOBvHnTkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 is taking shape  Dems will talk about climate change, voter access, affordable college, Medicare for all, Gree… https://t.co/s6XzNO82Bn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a smoothie for breakfast and all I can think about is how bad I want a breakfast burrito 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get home to find my children standing out in the cold, throwing wet sand at one another. You know what? I’m not e… https://t.co/NlLlSOVNOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruthTwain @ChatByCC @DonaldJTrumpJr Seems kind of dumb. Makes no sense. So sure,an appealing scenario to the MAGA hatters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResistanceGold1 @LiberalismReal @Try_Facts_Libs @dinmark2 @Gram247 @MissMaryCovfefe @paulpuckett911 @WHurensohn… https://t.co/kA7a9HNou3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's year 4 of using florescent imaging in my research and I have yet to spell it correctly on a first pass, here's… https://t.co/N6nXkaRpiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just love the feeling when you think you have work but you don’t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are tired at work but you look cute af doing it! 🙃✌🏻 https://t.co/td4LjMqMtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite thing is getting blocked by irrelevant people; ain’t nobody want you on their tl anyway https://t.co/0chz5OLivN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras lesson winds up with a parade and food! #cutureofawesome #bgisd #PotterGrayPride https://t.co/BNnU4SDSiD]]></document></documents></author>