<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dear #LoserTeachers , after you are done prepping kids for standardized tests and buying glue sticks with your own… https://t.co/O4ZlRwC0Cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maryamhasnaa I am blessed to have that in @SammyTU &amp; @DJ112sa and my boo @CheetahBronze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just2Educate @tyhollowell I'm very biased when I say In-N-Out is better than Whataburger when it comes to burgers.… https://t.co/NbX4Bh23xI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geno_grigio @Freesus One of the things that makes it hard to compare to past long-term deals is that not many of t… https://t.co/tbSFNZYfwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si mis compás no están triunfando algo estoy haciendo mal https://t.co/TsntUA53kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Senator you had a chance to have moderate Judges and you refused. Elections have consequences but Dem… https://t.co/PdfsRoYMIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the go-to, prototypical doo wop song? 🤔 Classic, nonetheless 🎧 Blue Moon by The Marcels on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/soOVqkIx0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HistoryofWrest 9.0 - I’m in a good mood tonight and this is a good card. I’ve got to guess that Barry Horowitz lost his match.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muhlenberg defeated York 66-63 in York. All kinds of problems during and after game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shelli69jeeper @THEJeepMafia @Jeep @TopJeepers @KrawlAmerica @RayGunVoss @Jeep_Familys @ItsaJeepWorld… https://t.co/p1Vwe15mZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I got from this was always spread positivity and love for the game. This is the type of things that makes me w… https://t.co/4o9urctP3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the power comes back on at home, everyone just bursts into a... https://t.co/AbUGrQgDfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfienberg17 No urge to watch. I’ve been spending time with my family and doing things with my kids that I haven’t… https://t.co/8akXI68dbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@journo_dale Dale is a liberal fart catcher posing as a journalist.  And now he's playing the gay card for whatever… https://t.co/XsILfWLyeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: @CBAColtsBBall advances to the SCT semifinals with a 63-55 win over Toms River North. Stephen Braunstein sco… https://t.co/bWvXafQuTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never understand “your contact” and it’s always some random ass account 😂 https://t.co/KWTNJhqlsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for tip-off! GlenOak Eagles ladies vs Aurora Sectional Semi Finals! GO EAGLES! #BeatAurora… https://t.co/YaLbkfRHCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyFriendCamilo Haven’t seen it, but for whatever reason I wasn’t in a hurry to. Maybe it’ll surprise me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably the #1 thing holding people back from sharing what they know - fear of doing it wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanSamFreak The pure joy that man has in his face for his child is just so precious. I'm sure she felt like a real princess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDaniel2033 Best team in baseball when he pitched in 72! Won 59 Lost 97 Carlton Won 27 Lost 10]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAWG 😩😩😩😩 whyyyyyy did my nephew say he had a oooop for me and she’s cold .... like I dead ass really believe him b… https://t.co/wePvKdaJqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWILLIE881 Congratulations On Your “5 t h” H D A n n i v e r s a r y ! ! Congrats On “5” Years!  !  !  !  !  “V” -… https://t.co/LdocTpSkWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Urban_Wolf @ramonaa1yahooco @WolfVivienne007 @isabenfica51 @OfficialGRT @Rubiconski @bergwolf12 @zazabelou… https://t.co/nEvNmVzgws]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the same morning video session, @jasongilleranmd demonstrated robotic-assisted laparoscopic revision of an in-pl… https://t.co/QWlEOP3AME]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no school today, so you guessed it...Robert is awake at 4:25 am. 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting better about the #DailyPractice of #reading (about 30 pages in 20 minutes right now - I used to have to rea… https://t.co/owICXFr7Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @frederickhiller 1/ The machine pictured looks like one of the new machines here in Johnson County,… https://t.co/fUJKNGZtXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday September 7th Santa Ana CA 🔥🔽🔽🔽🔽GET TIX: https://t.co/RgGQA5FysI🔥 #enforcer  #nuclearblastrecords… https://t.co/zuSZnnl50x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 starting early! Challenge accepted from @Amy_Hayes5 — Post 7 covers of  books I love: no explanations. Each t… https://t.co/k7pfeDtpb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holysmokes, so you know all 5 million NRA members with a large majority who fought for your country!  You say we do… https://t.co/KOFT84AScM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have great sex, buy expensive whiskey, drink beer , smoke weed, eat that damn cake , buy those shoes...and if someo… https://t.co/qOlaoQnFwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WakandaForever!! : ~ 1 yr ago, #BlackPanther appeared to us on 📽. This fascinating film us the fantastic and massi… https://t.co/2gsrLoDGtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidgura they can share a bucket of KFC in a king size bed while trumps snorts adderall and kim chain smokes for all i care]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪🏼🏋🏼‍♀️🇨🇱💪🏼🏋🏼‍♀️🇨🇱 #FamilyWorkout Wifey, Me, and the Boys @gogettemissac vq_christian @ Gold's Gym https://t.co/MhVPhRovry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaismithLives A guy with Tatum skill level only getting to line 3 times a game is just awful - I actually think th… https://t.co/jhE2enTO5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked by the office of my congressman @RepHarley with a pride flag simply to show his commitment - not because of… https://t.co/37gtsmwu1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dyse x Stifle - Coins (Wax Remix\ Prod. by EOM) https://t.co/LePlEjdWw6 via @YouTube @imgOWENin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always get annoyed when I see something that another account did that’s really clever, BUT I CANT DO IT because I’m not on that scale. UG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using company time and resources to apply to other jobs &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; https://t.co/tyZCJAUKEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killing babies is a national crisis and an act for war. The Saints of God will not be held back on that day. https://t.co/s5KeTeHmQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soccerluvr13 If you haven’t listen to that album I showed you yet, I usually listen to it when I need to chill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day 💐 everyone!!!! Be that love to someone you care about and even try the ones that may be chall… https://t.co/XcmW8PQGby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast with Jeff.  Tried the Roscoe.  It was good, but the waffle needs to be a bit more cut up or bendy. (at… https://t.co/W0iHfISzV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo wait a min, we are talking about a written rule in MLB...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunes and the other Republicans blocked Democrats from calling witnesses, recalling them and interfering with evidence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darinweed How similar are MxB and MxA? Or maybe a better question is do they share the same loop 4 structure but w… https://t.co/dZuUeqWijv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why you invest in a great headshot. Don’t skimp and be mediocre. Make the investment and stand out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why these comments by Council Member Diaz are so hurtful and damaging. We have fought and struggled, and yes… https://t.co/sUnHH2KDOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our democratic process as been overthrown by a president currently under investigation as a foreign operative. We d… https://t.co/Mw1hMDBOJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSasse #NotSure if this was sharing a great staff photo or propagating a narrative of a hard working female “bos… https://t.co/I82Nf4JQpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is a designated 15 min parking spot, you don’t get to be mad when you have no indicators that you are goin… https://t.co/CatoLkR4RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcollinsking @janson_chris Chris is simply an exceptional entertainer !!! WOW  Tom &amp; Kelley - Alamama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madflavor I think it was on ur show like 10 yrs ago wen u Had A (Sammy the Bull. I Think it was) was running Apts.… https://t.co/BW9djQQcCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[finally bought the james charles x morphe palette 😭 brb cryin hell yeah bitchachos]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 21. I heard my first cicadas today—a sure sign that spring is here in the South.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greencoder @jacobian Big gap between rolling your own and using external auth. Two reasons: - As a user I don’t wa… https://t.co/WY4IldT8yF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ubhatti234 @Christiano21 @juliusiswinning @BennieBenjamin @aaronbruski Bringing up Dipo after the fact is major, m… https://t.co/QtDPfg4yak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay. Italian sausages with sautéed peppers and onions is happening tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinaBuenoLopez @lopezobrador_ @LillyTellez @kioscomayor Alomejor ilegal exactamente no, pero es ético? Porque ganó… https://t.co/nn4vibU1z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myserenity69 @GOVTWINE Not to burst any bubbles, but there’s definitely a third type...neither dogs nor cats will ever be at my house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariannaAlfa @JESUSED71770925 amiga @MariannaAlfa te mando saludos  ya mañana te escuchare  y el domingo en @alfa913fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshmccormack @TheComicHunter @JimCanto @DreaVilleneuve @jesserker @katyb_spencer @nplusg @alysonshane… https://t.co/wJEJ9cNtvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calebgreiner001 @niko_cho2 @NicolaiDalton @blokabentley @connoroneill22 @jones_blake1015 this chode just admitted… https://t.co/xZKqAqGcRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a coward! Wimpy little coward! Hell to pay for Democrats committing TREASON!]]></document><document><![CDATA[1AM outside the 24 Hour Sci-fi Marathon  #columbusohio #bexley #drexeltheatre #scifi #movies @ Drexel Theatre https://t.co/WgJx96pbM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 6,000 allegations of sexual abuse have been reported involving immigrant children in US custody in the last four years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my yoga in today. Have you?  Even a few minutes of upward dog helps.  #yoga @ Kahn Center for Cardiac Longevi… https://t.co/PVmcCNyUEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop Running From Problems Without Solving Them, Otherwise They Will Never Go Away. Take The Time To Solve The Prob… https://t.co/K7WSM83lez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thor_benson @THELNUFAM Oh yeah that's a good one. Imagine your "lawyer" blaming you for breaking the law. Do you e… https://t.co/HN5Eo0tf0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ultim8HEEL @DecMonaghan01 @dougpaddick @SkyFootball @SkySportsPL Bullshit - he was hurt and the punk sss keeper su… https://t.co/hCNUhxpZ6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStakeClerk @ByCommonConsent “The things I am going to tell you about are not so rigid that the Church will fall… https://t.co/8RULzLtdDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 SWEETHEART!💝 Miss aliceroberts_ The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MOST Bea… https://t.co/qdK1rwscxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boozy for a double, but still tastes good. - Drinking an O.P.G. by Batch Brewing Company @ Avondale Park  — https://t.co/fOpE97wdYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monroejamessiii Most of them do CC, and we have counselors that help them out. The minority scholarship thing is e… https://t.co/QIl46N35Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyVegaSOLE I guess it's true when they say "the fruit doesn't fall far from the tree" ... when do we get to see… https://t.co/H4kBptDuQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beachside bikes in Miami  #bike #beach #miami #vacation #southbeach #photography #igtones #travel #vacation @ Miami… https://t.co/Ohbm77l3ZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael If we had one that you could TRUST!!!!! We wouldn’t be in the mess that we’re in. On the flip side… https://t.co/hvRoedqZld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humiliation and beatings dont stop someone from doing something it only leads to trauma but clearly the people abus… https://t.co/eso5yqxvrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD will say to each of us one day after we have passed away. WHY SHOULD I ALLOW YOU ASSESS TO MY HEAVEN? ANSWER PLEASE ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jan_hemeoncRN @BertJ4411 @Hybrid1979 @howdidyoureact @all_eyezonmi @Allie4Christ @Lo_Gannicus @Diaper777… https://t.co/ti6c5KcMFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump the greatest threat for any country, corporation, etc. comes from within not outside. #RememberThat #FAKENationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiserableSDFan What number while Machado hit in the lineup? (I have a 25 dollar bet with my brother it’s not the 2 hole)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black folks, we need to do a better job with checking our health. Including my damn self.   Don’t wait to go get ch… https://t.co/UX16svcO0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierrejvallee @PierrePoilievre @CPC_HQ @AndrewScheer Again...the issue is interference with the AG.  That's it..no… https://t.co/HHAw42fTRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctorOsty He changed the culture, you may not like the low jersey numbers / no facial hair but it shows sacrifice… https://t.co/xY8HUoaBK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going out to Raddichio’s last night and hearing “A Yankees hat in here? That’s bold!”, seemed like a proper send off ✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniqueSportplus it is outrageous. you’re claiming to trade lebron games bc of zo.  don’t get me wrong i’m actually… https://t.co/lu5cRLIl8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Scripture is breathed out by God and profitable for teaching, for reproof, for correction, and for training in… https://t.co/D87TM1rv1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RepAOC @AOC EARTH is 4.5 billion years old! “Ice Ages began 2.4 million years ago, lasted until 11,500 years ago,… https://t.co/OFjQDIZufI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank Veterans for their service by getting us  FULL DENTAL SERVICE AT OUR VA. LOTS OF VET VOTES.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deathbrollins @AlexaBliss_WWE Let me Induce My Self My Name is Giovanni Suarez, From West New York,N.J.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EschSupply Dear Madam or Sirs,  We are a professional manufacturer of tungsten carbide tools,and can produce exten… https://t.co/nwQpwzxqtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EatsTreats @Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/oHBbXDvkj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick primer on Gen Z, now entering the workforce!  https://t.co/EIcwBXHBXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EbiKingsley04 @cyruscake Um just sayin both her albums debuted at #1. Figured I would teach you a thing called fac… https://t.co/CnDXDBX6a1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#4 on the Lakers looks like he won a contest and gets to be a Laker for a day @MAL___]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hintzt @purplexion12 Owen’s wake-up time is 7, but I’ll enjoy this! Thank you! 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nosferatusaint @ZeroCarbSarah More like something to drop into the disposal😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday at VATP! Big Staff, Big Schedule, Big Expectations! Go VA! Go Central! #doingitright! https://t.co/0QUj6gBqpN]]></document></documents></author>