<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@andjustice4some @ETCanada i need to speak with you in person. clearly all the info you have are just hearsays. i a… https://t.co/PrxoDoUBbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please not chase this game? #NHLBruins also... can #NHLonNBC stop kissing the penguins feet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wyldcdn @notrunningfast The Enviroment groups are talking and pushing . I’m not sure why some Farmer’s just don’t get the message]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t be a 31 year old mf and still live with your parents and don’t work. That shit is weak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harjo111 @tenaciousT0286 @jhane415 @BlueEyedTweetie @LaunaSallai @NOMERCY604 @MislaMelissa @cindy_nurse @gailsline… https://t.co/irihv47hoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyMesnick @colton @jason_mesnick @GMA Hey, he can drink as he likes. Isn’t it what you like or is it what other… https://t.co/9yIkmKB7y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charcandrick26 If I made half as much as you, I’d be happy to allow national scrutiny. That money would allow me t… https://t.co/yx8mrnqbQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all I can’t feel my feet, face or hands it’s fixin to be a damn goooood night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffgerstmann probably been told this by now.  There is a bright colored plastic piece that you can remove to incr… https://t.co/Dhp7gRs23j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I just remembered the time michelle drove me home bc I got too fucked up and I was being stupid and distracted… https://t.co/Kj6zEsyTeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcezzz @AOC lol...a non answer. Stop making up facts, You prob don't even live in the area]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to do my makeup for fun and just take selfies. But I got not time for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a bit of a slow Monday before the @TheBachelorTV is on tonight! If you know of any amazing fashion or beauty… https://t.co/IcO8QnuBUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking forward to a good night’s sleep tonight and a super productive day today. Watch out world, the best is… https://t.co/jat2sMC9eU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mylanieeee @ayye_briii I’m all for it! “Hypothetically.... if I come with heelys will I get a better grade?” 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went on a bagel pilgrimage this morning and I am changed. 🥯🙏🏼 https://t.co/jKcVmJxa9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatBailey Where will you get it?  I don't know about that one.  I like Tony's typewriters on Etsy and Cambridge ty… https://t.co/KwLnYkn9Yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black History Brunch with my people!  #bkackhistoryallyear https://t.co/1OuIhGgTJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching anyone defend Michael Cohen is pretty hilarious. It’s like animals who eat their young. Witness Tampering? Haha , OK!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I’m here and the man is hooking me up with a whole hunch of wings Bc I said 11$ was too much for me to pay 💀 https://t.co/O6WfczKZwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOOKLYN were there any empty containers for potato chips or other snacks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrisD236 @edie_rische @SabineP2908 @NancySimonds1 @RollerRuthie @ElenaFadeeva3 @GinaPustor123 @odyssey158… https://t.co/YLPKbXKTm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you missed this, Alexandra Thomas, who just qualified for the indoor track state championships, is Rockland… https://t.co/5n8OUiywxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBrunoWSOC9 @AllisonWSOC9 @wsoctv Why can't Gov Cooper appoint someone to represent #NC09 until the new election… https://t.co/Wwzgnz0pVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE RACE TO EXTINCTION... Please watch this critical, honest content with everyone you know; share it with your loc… https://t.co/y0jKSErpiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA @Weezer love seeing you - my sons fav in 90’s. Have your songs on MY playlist.  Never forget the scavenger hun… https://t.co/UoGlmyNA0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alaya is lucky that she’s cute af because this little girl has had be up since 2:30😭😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple and cute today!! #datedenver #Englewood #Denver #DANK #Coloradoweed Available in Englewood until 10pm 720-58… https://t.co/h5NGnJfFOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a broke ass grow up homie make your own money and stop wasting this bad bitches time and money trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ty has given me hell about having an 8 am class and having to take quizzes and test since we got together and now t… https://t.co/QkPmb36rlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaroleRadziwill I have yet too see anyone that challenges @CaroleRadziwill be right. So good luck with that. This… https://t.co/czpo54SKOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a little too much fun with food color hehe.. These are actually banana muffins made using Bisquick. Super quick… https://t.co/r96poqSQb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton I thank God everyday that you are not POTUS and will NEVER be POTUS. You are truly a disgusting dis… https://t.co/gnlZ2rGA2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#marinacat won’t let me work #igiveup @ The Boathouse Marina https://t.co/QbRi42po6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating some delicious fish w the fam!! #thefishhouse fish are def food not friends today!! 😜😜🐠🐟🐠🐟 @ The Fish House… https://t.co/iXnoghms2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hip Hop Brunch (@ The @Common_Table in Dallas, TX) https://t.co/aXD85mU2yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadass @MsPorcha96 please please please come back Pullman isn’t the same without you, we miss you so so soooo much… https://t.co/UO0H6Yu6nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casacentral celebrating 65 years serving Latino families and others in need, congrats on behalf of @BankofAmerica https://t.co/DMYwdI8Sga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaMannBabiy Due to a horse riding accident in 2003, they said I would never walk again. 2 years after, I proved them all wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you  Following Following @loveforrealstar Star @loveforrealstar Follows you A grateful❤lost in the music❤… https://t.co/Zadvf1Ykt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Guess that Trump is racist is FLYING RIGHT OUT OF THE WINDOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to be at work in 10 minutes and I just left my house... happy friday y’all 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leaky @James_Phelps @OliverPhelps @PlanetComicon @thisisbwright Happy b-day 🎂🎉🎉🎂🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBenditcha I just found that to be funny after a 45$ offer 😂🤬🤬😘😘👭🌷♥️♥️♥️😍🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP rep says Trump 'violating our constitutional system' with wall order  https://t.co/aJcBtxEK07]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy and proud of you, @DustinSchwindt!!!   ps. I wanna be in your film class and write a thesis on Amélie.  🇰🇷… https://t.co/cHBPFTK5QV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 @in_pubs @Markbreeden @RPottery @Toonces_Resists @ErnieVillany1 @1saneman @Badmotherrucker… https://t.co/PHVNVXkwTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times touring @GrandviewCSD4 Middle School with @SouthKCChamber to see all the amazing work our fine students d… https://t.co/hMxr0WVixq]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 days until the Holy Land and I don’t even know what sunglasses I’m gonna take]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colin rolled over in bed not even a minute ago and told me he was going to sleep and he’s already snoring. How the heck???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still cry so hard for people who don’t care about me and I know they don’t care about me but I still cry because… https://t.co/QV63DSjfZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really felt you won the first round. To give Buddy an extra point because he had one more step was ridiculous. At… https://t.co/ZP7NZ7XPt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSylviaGarcia Being an American is never temporary when you do it LEGALLY. Stop supporting ILLEGAL immigrants! P… https://t.co/FOhUHauRb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[2ND ASSIST CHANGED: #TBLightning: McDonagh (8), Cernak, Cirelli at 3:06 of the 1st. #RedWings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to make an Urgent Care stop in Savannah bc I suspected I was coming down with the flu (I tested negative - than… https://t.co/sYOFsEU0Sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy we finally got a toaster lol ive missed waffles soooooo much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a lie, of course. I didn't apply filters, but Google Photos turned it into a stylized pano and added them in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkpolaroidgrl In here !! I know you all can't miss my crazy ass ! LoL. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom brought me as her +1 to the final @WichitaSymphony concert of this 2-part series. @lisedelasalle is doing 5… https://t.co/u4Ff6Ic3Uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alejandro and I saw Elizabeth Olveda from channel 2 at the gym yesterday and he was shook 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are thieves, and we must recognize them as such, "I've had gold ships before, I only stole them from other st… https://t.co/drSWMH5L7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a difference a few hours makes? Snow, thunder, sleet, rain.... At least no one will have to shovel today 🤷🏽‍♀️… https://t.co/APtimz78EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertclinejr @raywylie @OldQuarterAC @GabeWootton Have a great concert.. Get well soon, @raywylie ! I keep checki… https://t.co/R8fpQ7sJqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmeyer115comcas @Gloretired @RedTRaccoon @GGinCHS Cats too. Ask the Vietnamese lady down the street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/e6B8eqDQGk  Get expert advice via our Amazon Customer Service Phone Number 1-855-431-7111… https://t.co/FHW0LWCG40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Numerous job opportunities @SDNHM - and bonus, you’d be working with an awesome group of museum/fun loving individu… https://t.co/L1PLDPR7oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephen57036680 @KevinMFerrara @msmithadc @Kfuller8870 @gator4kb18 @rkline56 @hoppinmama5 @LissaLove123… https://t.co/xvnjewYXYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 @highbrow_nobrow The Trump's have such a public record of defaulting on loans, bankruptcys and fraud,… https://t.co/6a4RrSGWYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Author @KilbyBlades makes a valid point in her new blog piece. If you live in Romancelandia and also hang out on T… https://t.co/fio6eeUuf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, we’re discussing The Water Cure at book club rn. @fairfairisles, what are you doing to us?? https://t.co/8UFpze9Yo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PayyPayyy21 I feel this so hard today!!! It’s been a freaking MOOD 😂😫🤜🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: that snowman got demolished immediately after my live-shot.   #LasVegasSnow @FOX5Vegas https://t.co/3lRr6Kfld5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Maybe Junior too!!  ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need some dick I just need some love!  Tired of fucking with these lame ass niggas baby! I just need a thug]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had 3 drinks knowing damn well that’s one too many my limit https://t.co/RaVApxt4tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be dramatic but I told my boss today that I would die if I don’t see @KALIUCHIS on tour 😩🙏🏻❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amaba quién era hace 3 años, pero no quiero volver a ser la misma, quiero ser mejor. Una versión qué pasó por mucho… https://t.co/aCQXkDZD3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Maria DiCarlo, yesterday was a good day and here’s why: because yesterday, I met Evan Hansen !!💙👕💙👕 https://t.co/z4qeSkqntn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philadelphia is a welcoming city. Let’s keep it that way | Opinion https://t.co/NbB5xoKsB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI in today’s Sunburn: @RDBDbenefit announces bartenders @DanaYoungFL @JaredEMoskowitz @Kathleen4SWFL… https://t.co/YwM8Xq7sWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle Not even with my last fuck or shit do I care about this worthless waste if carbon based molecules]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ant. 3 The Lord is king, let the earth rejoice.  Psalm 97 The glory of the Lord in his decrees for the world This p… https://t.co/MMIYbNM6Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShriramKMurthi @johnregehr @justinesherry At least we have time for Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what the day holds I always know who holds me #nofilter #gorgeoussunset #puremichigan #thankyou… https://t.co/P42OPgAiVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself How upset w/you be if you found out that muscle knots can be removed immediately anywhere in the bod… https://t.co/ICOF6mvR3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was supposed to study for my midterm last night but instead I got drunk and went to sleep at 2 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought some ghost pepper cheese, and it has vanished. Seems fitting.  Cc @chuckinthechat @DisCounselor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee really gives it a good go at trying to warm my cold, dead heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students who are motivated by the intrinsic joy of choosing a great book will have greater meaning and value more t… https://t.co/Qqvh3Gsqv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put too much trust in some people, so I’m really just screwing myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkySportsNews excuse me sir/ma , have u heard any rumor of Chelsea sacking Sarri Cigarettes? Or any tip off like “… https://t.co/Bs25mJznEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pedroultreras @UniNoticias @jorgeramosnews Interesting that the US Embassy is protecting Jorge Ramos, I am now cur… https://t.co/y06yZMm12N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Thursday morning Ladies and Happy Valentine’s Day! I hope you and your love have a wonderful day! Love y’all 😘… https://t.co/AUqhCsTEZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowing 🌨 #loveboston #bostonsnow #snowing #usa #boston #snow #lovesnow #love #me #behappy #behappyandsmile @ Renai… https://t.co/Ew4CdANK9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnpmcd Exactly. That clearly is their strategy. The AOC gang is under the delusion that their ultra left messag… https://t.co/DRnsMEme6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhh shit guess who's on trending "again" ? CLICK THE LINK IN MY BIO 2 videos out now for #Genie. Miami the Queen i… https://t.co/jsYzb2c9vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abclarkmath Just got the “full” story on this from my math and hockey-loving boy. Be prepared to discuss in class… https://t.co/9OrU8K2PqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoaoSilverstein @realDonaldTrump Read the Declas papers that are about to be opened!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 This may be the answer to why the repubs are so complicit. It's the Kompromat we all have wondered ab… https://t.co/u0OAzlwZTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teach us to restrain our greed for earthly goods, — and to have concern for the needs of others. Lord, give life to… https://t.co/YEaaeRb9J0]]></document></documents></author>