<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Morning @GhopperFilm wondering if you all sell the digital version of Bertrand’s music or is it only available in Vinyl?  Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 WWE Sunday Night Elimination Chamber Live!  Toyota Center!  Finn Balor New WWE Intercontinental Heavyweight Wr… https://t.co/SIkKL6ghua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigjimmurray After watching that, I would never say he is the greatest of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crazyjane125 @Ravi88545166 @Shaun12361257 @Lisa19576 @_dopedaneille @blackyngdave1 @SweetlySmiles @SusieQ99345590… https://t.co/XCKPx0pysi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OatmealSoggy @AiG Again u conflate servanthood for man stealing/kidnapping a crime punishable by death in the Old Testament Ex 21:16...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceCoast_Hoff @FenwaySouth @RedSox @Yankees You know I bleed blue and orange.  #LGM2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida style 🌞 State - Drinking a Hop Gun by @FunkyBuddhaBrew @ Rocks  — https://t.co/BZt9FtLB2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terryschappert And after he asked if they were caught hahahahaha he is like Comey and McCabe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SingleSiStars @nativejeweler1 My 2nd oldest daughter got busy for Jesus ministering on a Chicago inner city Sunday… https://t.co/hh6F5YBRA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica I tell you, the uniforms are coming.  They probably are being made in Vietnam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridgers_kirk @EWErickson Those words sound nice, but you’re not making an argument in good faith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveWolstenholm @halfurd13 You can’t adjust for the one hour though? I’m not judging, I’m just curious. I find it… https://t.co/CbWyWlssvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[737MAX groundings as of this morning.. Carriers: Ethiopian, Cayman. Countries: Indonesia, China. 114 tails affected… https://t.co/MMIEGNhwEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“God didn’t put you on this earth to merely exist and vanish. Live with purpose, on purpose. Every single day.”… https://t.co/pMN938L0VQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond grateful for the amount of love&amp;support I've recieved from my peers today/tonight. Y'all family for real]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmw_337 Meaning he did not get them to playoffs. Great player, but in a  kaka 2015 situation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garfep @SuckerPunchProd Dude congrats and welcome to the SIE family! Downtown Bellevue is a little gentrified and… https://t.co/HVmKY9LiOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clswitzer Having to use a PC keyboard after years on Macs infuriates me. Typing a sequence of numbers plus alt to… https://t.co/wT0ESBjgG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KentuckyLucky_ @hoopvision68 Got a few on the docket that hopefully I’ll get to soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m dunking oreos in almond milk so i never wanna hear “grow up” from y’all again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicGregovits @mooseoutfront Not sure who looks better, @VicGregovits or that @Daktronics big 📺.    🤔 maybe Vic on the big 📺.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadenbrennan4 @SportsTalkBarry Kobe didn’t get a top 4 seed when he played with 2 nba all stars (Dwight and Nash)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul Or Lindsey Graham, or Ted Cruz, or Marco Rubio, or any of the other men who were in the primaries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rip to the hardest pimp to ever run the streets https://t.co/cmlw18131J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 10 months my love😘😘😘 @ Anaheim, California https://t.co/vxxDztGBWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump “Furthermore, as a gesture that only your favorite pumpkin-colored President, ME, could deliver, o… https://t.co/8eUQzhWHo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRATV @SpeakerPelosi @AOC @RepSwalwell @OliverLNorth Here they come buy all you can now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naomi_jay I’m reading Dean Koontz’s fourth Odd Thomas novel, which has two dogs in it. https://t.co/MptkZRoAR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JrLawrenceG @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @IvankaTrump And the majority of her workers are in sweatshops across Asia...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theodoreshoebat No shit. Tell that to Bergoglio and his buddies. Oh that’s right, most of them are homos too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out tracking freezing rain across northern OK for @kfor this morning. Currently light freezing rain in and around P… https://t.co/F9mkXwhu2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSigal @gelshenen @ROIChristie @RampCapitalLLC https://t.co/u8UB1nGRV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciate it @DonBougeII! Grateful for the friendships this coaching journey has brought into my life. Blessed to… https://t.co/3X34rXNCUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @realDonaldTrump Honesty. Self-assessment. Personal development. All good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TNMC at Camelback Brewery. Fun night of music with friends. #camelbackbrewingcompany #localmusic @ Sanford, North C… https://t.co/Q9L8cy6R94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelley_AK ordering my copy from the local indie store this week. can't wait to have this beauty class up my shelves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s honestly heartbreaking I got to see Zion play his last game at Cameron Indoor and it lasted 36 seconds 🤦🏼‍♂️🤦🏼‍♂️🤦🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls in Montana that wear yeezys and dior have a finsta named A$AP Nazi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone, big news for #HATM! Tomorrow night WEST SIDE STORY will be guest hosted by @sarageorgini ! Sara sugge… https://t.co/TL2uVpZkoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up close and personal in the murky Florida #Everglades / shot #onassignment for @Enric_Sala @ Everglades City, Flor… https://t.co/OApodnvdMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitansTonk @Midday180 @3HL1045 @1025_MD @1045TheZone @1025TheGame @JaredStillman @Hutton1045 @MickeyRyan1045… https://t.co/Li60tgGhwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moltes, moltes gràcies.  We all need to stand in solidarity against the corruption that is El Reino, which means “W… https://t.co/w1fGqbKQV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was right on time @marvinsapp. Hope @MsDeeMaria and I can make it to Lighthouse really soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy stat AND this was before the series against Clemsux. 👀💣 https://t.co/0rBApneGFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJeffHudson That’s great! I’d wait a few years before getting excited but u can do this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen retweet for vets! 11% of homeless are veterans. with ptsd and mental health issues. Venmo rob-donley… https://t.co/DWt7hBEds9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharcat12 @riotwomennn @BC_Real6 @chanwalling @BillKristol https://t.co/rfam7HRUS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lhaeger17 Because they trying to make money. Not hard to figure out. Obviously not selling well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @mattmccauley81! great word today encouraging us toward #FamilyDiscipleship at #Village101 https://t.co/7HgiASLe33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Initial applications for #5G will go beyond smartphones. Enterprises will use this tech for #IoT, video, edge analy… https://t.co/HpWjPmGbmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @NASASpaceflight @flcnhvy @rogiermaas @SpaceX Not totally tongue in cheek here, but what would the carbon… https://t.co/vvAjpgyaqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humbling and disturbing session on prisons how much we don’t know, what we do know, and how little we do to change.… https://t.co/ZGjnGuxdD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will any other stations follow suit? I've changed stations whenever one of his songs plays for years. https://t.co/Pfp1D9J2vi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie has an email list he’s been building since 2015. Email is a powerful tool for fundraising and digital commer… https://t.co/36bMxvg7VW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @realDonaldTrump Wrong David! It’s not in service of his country. Unless you are considering Russia a… https://t.co/DtRDND1SGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser He's right about that. Reparations for some means cash payments. For others it means a series of targeted p… https://t.co/uclFTg8eV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So encouraging to hear “knowing that the Pope is doing what he has to do, and we will all try to ensure that these… https://t.co/F8jz07FdlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!!!  To all of this, I say yes.  #god #slowtospeakquicktolisten @ Enid, Oklahoma https://t.co/5hAlQHpiHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbn4_uk Oh absolutely. But it’s all good. Once this season is over. They will go back to being an “ok” team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#raywellsmusic #king #majorindependent #winners #tour #boooking #features #hiphop #pop #rnb #rdr #music #deep @ All… https://t.co/FE2vff3jCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[AWS Transfer is everything I ever wanted out of my "don't have to think about SFTP" service.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is true!  #coffee #caffeine #coffeelover #foodlover #coffeetime #coffeeholic #instacoffee #coffeeart… https://t.co/JcN4GUHqnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseballmarty @KPIXtv @extrabaggs @vernKPIX @DennisKPIX @SFGiants Just watched the piece from the Grotto. That was so great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordynNealLoves @E_Reid35 It is painful, especially growing up in the Gibbs glory years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethDrumsTV Drewski’s gonna need some context... what was in the soft box?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenPenaloza Siempre han sido cómplices. No esperemos nada diferente de esa basura]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the RINOS GONE WILD in the Senate over Trump's perfectly legal and constitutional emergency declaration, i… https://t.co/BZ25obQ87Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath @AnnCoulter LOL try that in some areas and you will see what a mistake you made you might not be ab… https://t.co/SjwyB6VICP]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the @tfp_podcast Extra: I love “Meet the Robinsons”. That crazy family and Bowler Hat Guy make it worthwhile. #tfplive]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in Oshawa hanging out alone at my parents house while @nivosupremo hangs out with my family. https://t.co/GCoUaqDuhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_Stanislawski @greenbouncer1 Hitler nie robi zakupów, bo nie potrafi. Poza tym boi się ludzi bydlak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[not tea cus everyone knew and i just suspected it was for her automatically but it ACTUALLY is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like when I have to leave my study labs early, I feel like everyone thinks I just got all the info I needed and that’s not it !]]></document><document><![CDATA[With 4:14 left in 3rd, @ExeterBlueHawks up 38-30 over @Londonderry_ath . @seacoastonline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vernam @suehallie @Will_Bunch Bill Maher has brought this up a lot!!! It may actually happen. He may need to be forcibly removed..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RagetheMudkip I’d like to have a word with you https://t.co/udmcA1QvFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Close combat/oversight/Initiate on ektachrome 🎞 https://t.co/61J5xkUphy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babies teach you how to love, be kind, and a lot of patience! #UpdateParenting #HappyVDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettDieselberg Man something about my face makes me look ugly as hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[I move we do pass into something more......comfortable.  #arlegvalentine]]></document><document><![CDATA[My colleague @ChristineMNews picks up #JassyCorreia coverage from here. Follow her first update at 6:30 on .… https://t.co/3w0hRTE9Eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dilemma of indian muslim.. becharay apna patriotism he prove kartay reh jaingay!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZwartblesIE @tomdoorley ...actually, this is about calorie accounts in restaurants, not on food packaging (sorry)… https://t.co/u5coY2eVzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lxwarr30 @ArnieVargas @ByRosenberg @Katie_Roof Screenshot for posterity https://t.co/HTNoUIkyDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Corrs - Everybody Hurts UNPLUGGED - Amazing version of the R.E.M. Song https://t.co/PBQ3SCHvG5 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMS_Billy @BMS_Derek Lakers are a joke now. Rondo far right not even sitting with the team last night. Lol https://t.co/xs83HoFAvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samwise_16 If I were a member of the crooked, lying Democrat Party that doesn't want to face any hard questions th… https://t.co/OUvUMo7JRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougCondidorio @RealJamesWoods Yep. A complete dummy, and the folks behind this puppet are who we need to be concerned with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope, and you don’t either! I never gave the fans the middle finger. You’re just jumping on the bandwagon, acting l… https://t.co/nU1R73yQIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woodworkz Entrepreneurs 💪🏽 @yummybrothers 🍪 @canyuphixthis 📱 @eagleeyesports1 🏆 - Thanks for all the support and it… https://t.co/XVOn9XKlok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkTheOverseer This thread is what I needed today... glad she’s doing well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Westminster Shorter Catechism  Question 15  Q: What was the sin whereby our first parents fell from the estate wher… https://t.co/gNGn1J3GiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is a #ShadowhuntersLegacy don’t miss the Final Episode of #ShadowHunters the Winter Premiere Begins Now on… https://t.co/iwrEPEhai4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoGfsHairGoals @dope_d13 @churchooligan @JakiraMou @ibrahimorich @T_DUBB_O @radiorilla @Bound2B_ Explain yourself… https://t.co/LNvXIudZzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“That if thou shalt confess with thy mouth the Lord Jesus, and shalt believe in thine heart that God hath raised hi… https://t.co/lTNKd0iu8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHikingDiva Yes.  We’re good. I live on a ridge but a lot of people flooded out that lives near Piney River.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/QxjEdbSqGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seungminkim @jadler1969 @amarimow Always carrying the Republicans water should get tiring Seung Min Kim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Albert, Ashley,Cynthia and Justin our Associates of the month for January! Thank you all that you do!!!… https://t.co/Zansl4zlRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Electronic Merchant Systems New York - @ems_newyork in Rochester, NY https://t.co/MGhk8PACDC https://t.co/UdxU3IZzM8]]></document></documents></author>