<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It's actually quite scary how much I think about if I had a different name LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta bella y talentosa MEXICANA llamada @YalitzaAparicio me inspira, me motiva y me hace sentir muy orgulloso de se… https://t.co/b5J84mLkEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I don’t know how to get in touch with u i trying this please need to work I]]></document><document><![CDATA[about to head over to my buddy @SimplyColeman’s for a late night smoke sesh and some bro time. #CannabisColeman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even @espn doesn’t want me to watch Alabama basketball https://t.co/v7caHhhtPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReBourneAgain solomonster said next month rey mysterio would be in the business 30 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump And yet strangely that looks exactly like the same crowd that was outside last years Alabama - Clemson game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealarcott @RudeDawgRules That schedule is embarrassing. An FCS team, two G5 teams and a P5 team with 1 winning… https://t.co/lg1PKkhPii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanDivish @KevinShockey Excited for group photos of Harper, Carson Wentz, Joel Embiid and Carter Hart. Fun time to be a Philly fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JussieSmolletHoax more #Maga giddiness in da’ Cupp...@RealSaavedra @almostjingo @Shem_Infinite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting advise for your social adoption program: look at #email usage, find and analyze email groups and move g… https://t.co/IjZLeqQns9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ODU Career Management Center - @oducmc in Norfolk, VA https://t.co/RYE5DLa2wK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Magiccityatl WE OUT SEE YALL WEDNESDAY! LABEL AND ROAD MANAGEMENT!!! #ATLANTA WE HERE!! NEW CHEDDA CHIXS THOTIANA… https://t.co/OuAMapgAUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night @ATLouisville #HumanaFestival #HF43Kickoff @ Actors Theatre of Louisville https://t.co/obGlLwb8P9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdrndad Avoid Google at all costs. That’s pretty much what I’ve been doing since I switched to iPhone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmittyTweets1 I refuse to believe this isn’t a private plane to STL. #ballin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday @TheOtherRosie Because this radical left wing Socialist version of a party left him and mainstream America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Torrance, CA #Retail job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: shift supervisor - Sto… https://t.co/LhhIj0qrXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenDoran I still haven't seen it. My wife is dead set against it. I have no explanation either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Star Trek: Discovery The Good Place Full Frontal with Samantha Bee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBoard1200 @Joeycules Nothing is quite vomit-inducing as “Say-Town.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 hour delay!!  @southwarkschool parents and students, we will see you at 10:30 this morning—Monday, March 4th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epilcher641 Re-send over the weekend and will try to give it a listen and thank you for your kind words!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjhaisch 100% but also NowThis is hardly above being a tabloid and cannot be counted as anything close to actual journalism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActNow_Climate No we don’t need any of that climate change is a hoax built on junk science.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MickeyRyan1045 @3HL4LIFE Make that two (said the radio voice of Marmaduke Greyhounds basketball from 1986-89!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieDevious I would be okay with them getting together though, I hope they make it happen in a way that makes se… https://t.co/NjqA0AwYNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larry_otreba @TheRealBuddyGuy Yes! Been a fan since my post-college days living in Chicago. Was fortunate to help… https://t.co/Salbvlv6FZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ORANGE VANILLA COKE!!! They changing the world @ Raley's https://t.co/0J9edA5fD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disappointing end to that inning for Arizona, Alyssa Palomino strikes out on a pitch over her head and Reyna Carran… https://t.co/2XX9dpABL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍀Coming to a mailbox near you🍀 If you would like #longislandrealestate market updates, shoot me a DM.… https://t.co/r64vWlIUb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Azmustangguy @edredmny @TerriblyMe @CNN @bopinion Our education system has failed you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericvideo @friocarrieo @jestkathy @MarieNoel45 Sorry, you should not say that sHaMe    She treats bad people a whole lot better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar your idolatry against ELOHEEM, does not work that way. demonic, common sense is extremely dangerous.… https://t.co/EwKNgAmQsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nolispui @Josephvss @CatholicSat @StLentner I’ll show you my facts so you show me yours:  An estimated 18 million… https://t.co/AQVoL2NXP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 BS Trump is kissing Kim asd. 2016 Otto was arrested in Korea 2017 Otto died. And TRUMP blames Obama… https://t.co/F71M4eMElP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bri_vacirca @mattcalabretta1 It’s either that or a cruise I’m thinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote of the day.  #ethics #values #philosophy #monday #Atlanta #atl @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/DvvUvQvyX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beta move for Seth to wear his brothers shoes during the 3-point contest #AllStarSaturdayNight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Jim_Jordan If you are on the Oversight Committee in Search Of The Truth, You are doing a Terrible Job. You are… https://t.co/jkyC6MBeIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ex_Wretch @SticksMix @sues3jewels @yeshua_porvida @IIIDeaton There’s lots of things lining up with His word , my H… https://t.co/dvL9m85btT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers for the little Chinese boy who didn't put enough glue on Zion's shoe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allisonjanney_B @KenyonCollegeVB Reminded me of your breakout Kenyon Alumni Bulletin cover from my year ‘98! I gra… https://t.co/ZzbN8fe4nC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm ready to watch #JoshAllen bring it at the #NFLCombine today on @nflnetwork. Which prospect do you think will bring it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen, this is the face of a pathetic loser, and a coward. Most likely he is also a complete phony w… https://t.co/kcC0I8CoPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DFSArmy the spreadsheets and research station last night were on point, thanks https://t.co/kfh3TVT1iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve determined that my favourite part of modern daily life is when a @YouTube “targeted” advertisement for a couch… https://t.co/0SLdvromYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostMalone good decision with the face tattoos. You definitely won’t regret them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Doctor says Coach Hill has never been healthier.  #ThatHappyFeeling #Salute https://t.co/QgbcziotPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ja Morant (top 5 pick) is playing Saturday. Tickets are 30$  bUt PlAyErS sElL tIcKeTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlaymon @usatodayhss @BigRebelNation @BchsEsports Man that's really awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote of the Morning  " LOVE LIFE " Blessed to be Blessed https://t.co/lNg0lU1fuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkRedbeliever Also, he said water is wet and the sky is blue. He’s spitting facts, folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr__Soto @elchivo1112 She blocked me for a MINUTE and I didn't do shit but she unblocked me :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍦 GIVEAWAY 🍨 To celebrate 2k followers, I've teamed up with @milkice20 to giveaway two small parfaits made with ITA… https://t.co/kj3SjUVXox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@INTERESTlNGVIDS @HoldMyBeerVids It is there enough room on the raft to save Jack? https://t.co/W4eZ8p0Tj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: @bham_fire says chemical fumes limited to inside building. Employees/contractors who were transported compl… https://t.co/XvEUd7Iykg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow my rule.  Watch this video without audio first.  Try not to throw your phone.  #Smollett #JussieSmollettHoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rocking at the Hard Rock with the National Champs! - Drinking a Pale Ale by @SierraNevada at @hardrock  — https://t.co/wNfF6YvwgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/11/2019 - 06:29 Temp: 45.6F   Hum:  88% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 30.326in. &amp; Rising Rain: 0.23 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoodgodabove Stop letting the good die young.   Rewrite the bible to support gender and racial equality and BAN… https://t.co/MpOFjRzld3]]></document><document><![CDATA[27.) L.A. CONFIDENTIAL (1997) *rewatch D: Curtis Hanson https://t.co/uKepyKjl7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekMill @MICHEALRAPAPORT YESSSS MEEEK TELL THIS MF WANNABE someone gotta shut his ass up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drevrpg Probably not. More likely to be a straight forward presentation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniel_foulkes @Calhalsall @CodySnow25 @JohnThomasHins2 @AtlantaFalcons Free agency starts in March and will affec… https://t.co/8iKtVB3GQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic When you analyze that statement, it is nonsense. It took a bloody civil war to end slavery de jure. De… https://t.co/rAxptTutCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loricurt @braceletsforof1 Happy birthday Sam all the way from #ThorndalePa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join us for our watch party this Saturday at BC Bottle Lodge in Liberty Township]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorSinema has been a very busy Senator. She kind of reminds me of the Zel Miller type.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skinnyandsingle @manny_ottawa @molly649 I think we're infecting Canada. "Sorry."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBobCummings @RblYellsCommish @John_Borneman @Bmosc1 @Taco12Pack @ChristianHaas13 @HellOnWheels414 @Pooka311 @JGodz_DPT Same ^^^^^]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSPLATT HI! Me again. Can you follow me thanks I have a very important question]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hear birds chirping outside my bedroom window and it makes me yearn for springtime so bad.  This potential snow t… https://t.co/XnbVfd6nww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 That's very normal... 1.5 months for each million stolen from taxpayers. Totally in line with the 22-… https://t.co/e0qvzP8JAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long week of meetings, schedules and running to and from, nice to have a day of no major appointments. Enjo… https://t.co/zvThHqeoF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stbutah @LindaSuhler @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity WHAT?? Trump is what will win,,, you might want to read a bit o… https://t.co/fmQphaPOkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espero aún lleves el recuerdo contigo así como yo siempre cargo con el tuyo. Espero algún día ser lo que siempre quisiste. Espero...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMehtaNYDN Love the traditional ones Parcells put us back in. Not happy about new ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[😇 GOD'S DISCIPLE MINISTRY'S Colossians 1:21-23 NIV Once you were alienated from God and were enemies in your minds… https://t.co/FshTW9bgDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solentos exactly. that makes it really confusing. but i know most for sure would have more awareness than to rip t… https://t.co/opzQF2bVm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Chinese father would say this is luck.   I’d ask: What about mother. Was that luck too]]></document><document><![CDATA[AWW SHOOT HOW DID I NOT GET THIS! YOU’RE NOWHERE IN SIGHT, GIRL I MISS YOU!🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Badgers may want to work on breaking the full court press before tourney time....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateMonroeTU Meanwhile JEA pension is doing well and they still increase the employees contribution. Wonder if any… https://t.co/sRxfaaOfGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your 2019 Suffering Knicks Fan face makes @kevinlove’s Instagram post #DoItForZion https://t.co/bduWURdNed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention all cattle rustlers be sure to wear your Cow Fart Protectors https://t.co/XjA9X6HOUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomhomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomgomg... @padres #Machado omgomgomgomgomgomgo… https://t.co/hracq6XYh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alberto_hrv @DavisSchools Thanks Alberto. Looks like you're having a great time repping @PlayCraftLearn at @ucet. Great job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man will lead the way !!! Save us from Ourselves.Some call him...Mr Trump... American Choice for POTUS...burp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samantha Leeks started the Princess Half Marathon! https://t.co/VYC5CUB3AR #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Flores @The4f45 @RainManDigital hey boys wanted to make sure you’re aware HAL S3 is now streaming on Netflix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost @chosen1saintv79 Jesus said, “Whoever wants to be my disciple must deny themselves and take up their cross… https://t.co/id6rCFVqGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VOColleen 2days #TuesdayTip is a #SafetyTip: If U have the hiccups while eating, stop eating once a couple seconds… https://t.co/CTUmMmm451]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alan Dershowitz: Ousting Trump via 25th Amendment is ‘clearly an attempt at a coup d’etat’  https://t.co/8jAQZrYCSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Obama boondoggle that Florida’s republican governor was smart enough to avoid. Obama n sheriff Joe (Biden)… https://t.co/lcMvvJEGTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m flying to the moon 🌙 again  📸: infinityandb3yond  - - - - - #moon #friendship #loveher #observatory #view #la… https://t.co/9tmohGYVUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FNugges @Flocris4 Definitely beautiful! Defiantly perfection she defiantly is!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!… https://t.co/pdlW7OCCMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Selling my prom dress, help me get rid of it pleaseeeee😩🤦🏽‍♀️ Custom made dress from a NY designer,… https://t.co/ff9vllMH4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌸🌸💞🌸🌸 #VisionZeroDC: Can #CaBi be this #PrettyInPink forevs⁉️ #PrettyPrettyPlz⁉️🙏🚲💞😻😻😻 That #pinkout is such Ground… https://t.co/4lCuewJzc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horseshoe426 @Minuteman223 @Tactical_review @JenniPrickett @Bearman1130 @pensfannc5 @44_rem_mag @teamregulators… https://t.co/dwgVgrtqYM]]></document></documents></author>