<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SeahawksMachine (like he doesnt get a say as much as he might have in Seattle)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elsa as The Bride of Frankenstein! #ArtWIP #watercolors https://t.co/nzGs9F6aBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $1,279.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/CHeKmoyYYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent an hour on a table today for MRIs, hoping for some new/better answers 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my guy 😤@SnowballOak can’t wait to ball out with you again next year ✊🏻💍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking Your whole existence is defined by race . Have you ever stopped to think that maybe you are the real racist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleDHester Make this happen.  Many GREAT and GOOD People have put their HEART and SOULS into this movie to Entert… https://t.co/BgsoJFaJrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was pretty close to buying a GPD XD+ the other night for the portable Steam Link possibilities, but after some re… https://t.co/1Mu6EPqWDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOMEN: stop babying your fucking sons. Housework, chores, and cooking ARE NOT A WOMAN’S JOB. They are necessary sur… https://t.co/h68oJDVEId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kshogueturf Get all the smokers a juul so they can vape while they work dog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DShivers11 Gotta make a living man 🤷‍♂️keep doing you you're doing great I don't know how people could be upset ab… https://t.co/d99AmjtYGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We be watching from Kansas. After we visit the fieldhouse and watch the jayhawks tcb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jerry Jerry Jerry ...this just isn’t gonna work https://t.co/q2rWhUEQpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without Yoshi, my significant other ,taking care of my every need,l’d be dead by now. Me losing track of what day it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanKarmel I got so happy listening to you @NonProfitComic @thegissilent go off for like 5-10minutes about shoes in… https://t.co/8MPYWvqHO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk "The emissions from 15 of these mega-ships match those from all the cars in the world" Read more at: https://t.co/kR3mvWzXeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[90040 unconstitutional; 90042 constitutional; 90043 constitutional; 90044 constitutional; 90045 2nd sentence is con… https://t.co/3ZjIvkV5y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Personally I like her. She would be funny if you were drinking and listen to her go on about her idea… https://t.co/6dsRwZ45WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedemptiveCycle #rctrample #birmingham #bham #bikebham  Great ride! Thanks @c_fuquacious_11 @charitymiles strava… https://t.co/hDII7WCt6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “noise” color fx on the pioneer mixers is a waste of space, its awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i can make $1,000 off my clothes i don’t see why i couldn’t make $1,000,00 honestly *]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I took 4 melatonin’s (I haven’t taken them in a while)  and in the middle of the night i put my hands up… https://t.co/BWL6owY8O0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to see the launch of the new @AAIEGlobal website.  #finalsite #internationalschools]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bookmarking this tweet, Wade may very well end up being guilty, but @DickieV serial bias and hypocrisy is too much.… https://t.co/FMzpYkKX9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[dark vs light.   Collaboration is a powerful thing. Don’t be jerks. Meet with people. Work with people. Trade with… https://t.co/1D4qWJSr1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who is the biggest threat to America right now is Donald Trump nobody is more enemy of the people… https://t.co/yKUitgJNjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWORLD @guardian @nytimes @postpolitics @SenWarren @BernieSanders @PBS @ABC @NPR @maddow @latimes @USATODAY @WSJ… https://t.co/CXA1p1bf3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4hemimike Check Mason website to find they use Common Core curriculum &amp; passed Fla Common Core state tests!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look@ this fool, so damn high!, he cant even hold his head up! ⚠️Indica/Purps https://t.co/9yuLQF6JkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neiljpat @CallieMPatel @Healthbox I also am an industrial engineer (Illinois ‘86) You May be interested in this le… https://t.co/bPZTnZlG0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t want to start any controversy with the new look #Phillies but how dare Rhys Hoskins do that to that ball yest… https://t.co/JlWoOjN21B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ward w/another steal, his second of the game and 10th of the season. Insane speed out of Dawgs CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealinformer I love how Hogan casually leaned into that one. Brother!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans: “how about you crybaby liberals go back to your safe space and stop trying to censor the world! What h… https://t.co/zGDvqcBopm]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my beautiful wife at Miss Saigon @playhousesquare https://t.co/sGKyC1BUEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida weather is 🔥.   #Florida #FloridaKeys #sunset https://t.co/65l6jnvKSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyNicholasS Well elway got several quarterbacks.. that didn't work out either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr What a dumbass. Illegals are not citizens. Unless you are a citizen you can’t vote. I am afraid the… https://t.co/qidt0pEffQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Poverty and shame shall be to him that refuseth instruction: but he that regardeth reproof shall be honoured.” Proverbs 13:18 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallofDuty so besides being drop into a LOSING game, they still annoy ppl with a message, of taking a lost when I’… https://t.co/Ucf1nTQLxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyslibtard @RepDonBeyer @RepCunningham Are you nuts? One blast of an airhorn can permanently damage someone’s hear… https://t.co/mdzRFlBv6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jahimes Rich folks who can still vote republican because voting is anonymous lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost together. #park #centralpark #city #newyorkcity #nyc #nycprimeshot #nybynewyorkers #nyc_highlights… https://t.co/YLDzzrDuu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Did the woman read the bill to see what's in it .... what is in HRI  ?? It's not that hate speech bill is… https://t.co/r4i8g17ud4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CattleParker Amazing ! Dirt, but no mud. My mind is blown. I haven’t seen that in about 7 months. Calf is cute, too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ik I’ve already had dinner and cigars with him but @michaeljknowles liking my comment still makes my day 😂 https://t.co/v7sb3x6N9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanddonnelly I think the best Sushi I have ever had is at the 7-11 just around the corner from the 20 mile mark in Tokyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe what are you up to?Gillis stick was as heavy and thick as Finner's.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ajax smash!!  Thersites brings Ajax to life?  #TrashcanShakes #GameDay @ Idle Hour https://t.co/UpbSdaXXUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Please. It’s chilling how talented they are. Libtards who tell us how to live and wear millions of dollars around their necks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadler1969 If I was DOJ, I’d also argue that unless the courts are going to second guess the emergency declaration… https://t.co/HowUyuBd5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to all of our amazing partners who make it possible!  @OWCsolutions @securematics @YamahaMusicUSA… https://t.co/S7LsZrkgCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to meet @ChrisEvans at work today and told him how big a fan I am of his best work: Not Another Teen Movie.  Bu… https://t.co/cmYNjg88Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop looking at it I literally have no idea what he’s trying to get across]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh fuck social media , people on this shit for no reason at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Otten DEFINITELY came through for the Jacob Coy Choirs!!! Enjoy your day off for a great concert!!!! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need to be aware. When Donald loses, there WILL be an increase in violence. Some directed by Donald, most ju… https://t.co/wcQNe1iyjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 1st time I ever heard of Daredevil was on the old Ferigno/Bixby Hulk show. He was dressed in black. The next da… https://t.co/Lnj8kg7EuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[K &amp; N West Series  Nascar on Dirt @ The Dirt Track https://t.co/NbP150M9cI]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really resonate w/ how they made miles more artsy in itsv and we share a love of music (drawing, not so much but… https://t.co/x0OcRxLdd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNDari Yep. I’m a big Phillies fan too I feel like I’m the only guy in the country that doesn’t want them to sig… https://t.co/qXXA6Gdbsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super contento con el apoyo y cariño de mi gente manifestado de maneras tan bonistas 🙏🏾 Hoy midiariopanama aporto s… https://t.co/DgjtbaXFz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElemSciTchr @taftphaedra1 @KRScienceLady Since CCSS, time in K5 for instruction built for ELA and Math focus has b… https://t.co/g2ScxVrqGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelenaFlorDeTX That’s actually in Midland, Texas @ christensen stadium]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year he’s in office, would takes take decades to recover from his actions. SAD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Newman Elementary for hosting Northeast Assistant Principals today in our PD on Guided Reading.… https://t.co/QksDyDffR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff We're still waiting for the evidence you said you saw that proves POTUS "colluded" with the Russians to… https://t.co/kyQ1J9opvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brayden Schnur’s incredible breakout tournament ends with a thrilling 6-1, 6-7(7), 7-6(7) defeat to Reilly Opelka.… https://t.co/CEDjhSSQ1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earth's fish are disappearing because of climate change, study says - CNN https://t.co/uB2rlxUcxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like a king, as Toby (@RedScareToby) has said flattering things about my article about Brendan Kelly (one of… https://t.co/a19FobswAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope to get Rich Rich in knowledge Rich in adventure  Rich in family Rich in health Rich in love https://t.co/q8HHIJrdUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Trump asked Congress for the money, but they refused to pay to help end a National Emergency. Congress has eve… https://t.co/1BpS5IGp60]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How many times have you watched the office?”                          Me:  https://t.co/IbOE8irpbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAW0116 @newyorkshuffler @MaxYarbrough @roughnrowdy your shuffling basics video got me through the hardest years of my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch This is garbage and also this guy’s shirt isn’t Fitton him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You failed to drain the swamp, but one by one your friends are going to jail and the Dems just wan… https://t.co/ATRWsApcW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoItsAlexx I would add Red dead redemption 2 single player and online. Its such a huge game i wish i could take… https://t.co/DYZnlSJ4Gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryWalterRadio Please tell Vince, “Nice one but he should have said “Snow much MORE to come!”   🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corruptedgem I gave them lots of pets on your behalf ♡ https://t.co/9PcMhdMaY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE the @Raiders, they’re an AFL original and Al Davis is the man who Bob Kraft wished he was, but the thought t… https://t.co/KO5B3s4Dv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance I wish but, nah. This will be a blip. Then we will move on to the next shocking thing and dismiss that too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDLCC In spite of what the liars of Democrat Party say, if there was even the SLIGHTEST bit of truth to what the… https://t.co/4EDa0UEdQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super on it this year....back with more hot shit... I told you we dropping heat .. coming from the #bigvision… https://t.co/MuiK78tJRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best #Philly cheesesteaks i've ever had in #Htown! And the #FLYERS won in overtime!!! 🏒 https://t.co/v5MxDTWEvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariahMillian No you are far from a hoe your a queen my love let me find out someone called you a hoe we gonna hav… https://t.co/YgWEAKs1y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers for the tornado victims and those communities down there in Alabama... just saw video....horrible devastation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“BITCH I WANT EVERYTHING, BITCH WE NEED EVERYTHING, U SEE ME N EVERY CHAIN, WE SWERVIN N EVERY LANE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scott Gimple ruined this franchise. I keep watching only because I’ve invested 8 years into it. I’m only seeing it… https://t.co/yiFYUGTUrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an all-day agile development training seminar during trade deadline season 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shareblue You didn’t need a poll to know he is the worst and a traitor to America to boot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyReagan1945 @Nrd0416 @WLWT So why did the governors of Texas &amp; California remove the national guard?a hole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sojo2006 @KirkCousins8 Good luck with Darnold 😂😂. He’s terrible and your team has been terrible for years, Tom Bra… https://t.co/qUM5k5GlJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog So Matt, you’re wanting to take away a woman who was raped and impregnateds right to her body. I’m n… https://t.co/SOZGa9oMn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memphisnews Great half-done story. Look at how well all 3 brackets did comparatively.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the monthly conference of the Maryland Court of Appeals. There are likely to be a number of opinions, f… https://t.co/3iZCIKxh7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobOfAZBirdGang @JeffPassan @ramonashelburne @JesseSanchezMLB He’s in decline stay away]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: person who claims to love Sublime but only listens to Santeria: 😌🤙🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yumcoconutmilk So some people suggested that you shouldn’t concede that the tweets offended anyone? We’re in some… https://t.co/ItEopPXY2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I learned on this 63 year old journey? Show up. That’s where the magic happens. #myessence #bornday #nomagic… https://t.co/V8TPK5mKi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yates_Doug @roushyates @FordPerformance @NASCAR @amsupdates @keselowski @MMUSCuttingTool @sallyzepp]]></document></documents></author>