<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So work it out. Give the baby its life. Life is a lifelong emotional issue -don’t conflate mental health developmen… https://t.co/1glWtsrPLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day Everyone! Always Show Appreciation To Fans, Friends &amp; Family 24/7. #happyvalentinesday… https://t.co/vGzSVdQ20C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Him waiting for me to get home &amp; have a talk w me ab it not being ok for us to be apart. https://t.co/ligNOEVzY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will you be my Valentine @piperrrrrrs (the post said to say this then tag the 3rd person on your @ list and you wer… https://t.co/MR9PflB4LP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tchapmanonline Check out one of our local, very talented, young men!  @ColeDagen   https://t.co/v2kU20KjAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend 3 of our neighbors (our RA included) blasting music and keeping us up. Let’s see if they do it till 6 am ag… https://t.co/gVzTDHJB9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you opt to skip all of #Arrow s6 except #Olicity scenes and quickly jump back to s1 to start all over again...… https://t.co/t9JFHFiwbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my sweet girl!!! 1st place in storytelling... WOO HOO!!!#proudteacher #yougogirl #SpradleyScholars 💙🤗🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selectedwisdom @Jim_Jordan @Jim_Jordan you are a lost cause and a disgrace to the people you serve]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I stay fat because I eat fruit like it’s candy. GIMME ALL THE SUGAR 😍🍉🍌🍇🍓🥝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well we'll the leader in fake news speaks again more propaganda never the truth ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueFirstLady I did say no tweeting #MarALardass, I just had to come back and see if I type right word...… https://t.co/cUsSU3jWOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asya_usvitsky @RepMattGaetz Omg !!  Guess you forgot about 9/11 and 3000 Americans killed !! You also forgot who killed them!! Sheep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jmonst @BibRave Haha! The fact I live in an apartment that doesn’t allow dogs is the only reason I trust myself...… https://t.co/wkSz2mKjni]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are several Dems who are running (or thinking of running) for President, who believe passionately about the t… https://t.co/cQBVOSSkWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[here hold my kombucha and this tub of olives what grocery shopping is like with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @MalcolmNance Well there's a "special place in hell" for this priest.  My heart cries for his victims.]]></document><document><![CDATA['Our little brown rat': first climate change-caused mammal extinction https://t.co/i0QcdKXqZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[A broken cup that has been put back together. This @HanaShafi art particularly speaks to me; “You’re allowed to hav… https://t.co/S4bbjpQk0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Best in Show!🏆Happy Birthday Birdie!💝🐶🐾#valentine #weeniedog #bowwowwowyippyyoyippyyay 💘💖🐶🐾🐾🐾 @ Bee Cave, Texas https://t.co/A1Uf1eZjen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianbowe It’s the Netherlands.  The windmill in the back ground finally clicked for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieSLalonde I grew up in Montreal and whenever I try to explain something about my childhood, people here are li… https://t.co/bluvc7amAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/MZJyeb0ozr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potatOSMDMA @MisAnthroPony (still getting robbed if captain marvel has anything to say...)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures in parenting pt 5764: knives in the plastic wrap. Maybe I should look for the missing Tupperware lids in… https://t.co/hw0CYbdL73]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Check out the movie made by Robert Redford that presented what happened to the people who owned th… https://t.co/fPlDlIiHbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foglia_mario @Rob_Dimeo @SteveSilbert @kforkish @jihan65 @ProfClayton @100978Marc @DianaSoriat @cibi1974 @xLontrax Amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are despicable. These women are brave heroines for our country and their communities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt This needs to be one of the first crises for Congress to address.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @funder @Outback @CapitalOne @AstraZenecaUS @Ford Just contacted Ford]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Willow Pointe Assisted Living in Verona, WI https://t.co/xeE5K27US2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morningmika, did you ever think that @SecNielsen *is* doing her best?   That her mission is the cruelty?  That she… https://t.co/kJtNqlhSX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to find a comfortable position to sit/lay in on your period is impossible to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Being “critical” means not only learning how one is oppressed but also acknowledging how one is privileged.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sweet student nominated me for the lottery’s NC School Hero! We have the chance to win $10,000 for @underwoodgtm,… https://t.co/3wIo59t8EI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two and a half hours of madness dear God listening to that lunatic. The man is certifiably insane. Not just impeach… https://t.co/SpnbRMLkcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandastweeets Hey @boo can we allow polls to have more options so we can get some stat sig results on favorite ho… https://t.co/alRKdqyLAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[. #silvabakgzbitch #wwwsilvabakgzcom #nola #SilvaBakGz #silvabakgzent #nlb #neverlookingback #SilvaBakGz🦍… https://t.co/KpCZDhDXkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronHimmlerATC @Bmangine1 @Koz_UC Happy Birthday Koz!  Hope you recovered from my Korean fire chicken. 🤣Have fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this might already be @Corrin31 preferred airline but now...! 🍷🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[just bought myself a fanny pack. where and when it will be used? I don’t know, but it was cute soooo 🤷🏻‍♀️😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddTPrice24 @JLee418 @laura24fan @Chrisracefan1 @JoePalmerJr @chevychevelle48 @georgia242011 @DaleJr88FanNate… https://t.co/7hQY7pgum3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kinda extort my bestie?  HOW ELSE DO YOU GET ANYTHING?!?! @benschoeller]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/N4QQcOkzXx  This is a pretty famous rehab facility in the Chicago area. Utterly shocking, grotesque, and breaks my heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trickfuel51 @realDonaldTrump And may you be damned for wishing that on our President! Satan is waiting for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the earthquake wakes you up before your alarm goes off... #tired #herriman #bluffdale #utah #earthquake https://t.co/aRHhjO9mF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lookin better everyday I got that Benjamin button 😉 https://t.co/WfYL5F1135]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houston0621 No one is trying to invalidate votes. In the words of one city council member today, (paraphrasing) no… https://t.co/TDYUts0AXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when your family leaves out of town and my cousins feel bad so they invite me to eat lol #realones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewieJones3 Hi, Sarahbeth. Can you please follow me back?  I would really appreciate it. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok thank u for this. BUT THE MF CHOMPING IN THE BACKGROUND OMFGGGGGG. ugh!!!! 😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff #9pmRoutine West Mifflin Pa is Locked Down! https://t.co/kDbX3m7HRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluegirl1564 @JohnKimbleSL @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Don't be ignorant.  I disliked Obama's policies greatly… https://t.co/aRAUzJel3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing pisses me off more when a person is on social media but can’t even text back]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI- Join us this evening for a #BoostingAchievement chat abt sheltered classes.  #ellchat #ells #esol #mathchat… https://t.co/3nRppat1L8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimHall60 @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump That wasn't a temper tantrum, that was a sit in to make a point. A temper t… https://t.co/DGeJYCmxbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalWomensDay to all of you badass beautiful women out there. Be sure to love yourself today ♡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRHLucifer @01AlphaOmega Not even, Nick... If I'm going to bite something,  sweetheart, it's NOT going to look as… https://t.co/6wdCW4SVD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless our homeland Ghana, and make our nation great and strong! #GhanaIndependenceDay https://t.co/j05hXinBmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigfrisky I see them do this a lot and I always want to go and I’ve finally got John talked into it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madlatinathot Damn Cleopatra my boobs are still bigger https://t.co/IvFeo9IMoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kassbekillinem Man I can’t wait until they figure out who created this, I’m scared just looking at it I can’t ima… https://t.co/Cgbx0zTa5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somesayclever @Chronic_FLKeys @abledoc @AmerMedicalAssn Your logic is what’s silly]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know summer has begun when the first Salsa band hits the stage! @BlueMtnVillage @BlueMtnResort]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Price is Right with my favorite sister! @ The Chicago Theatre https://t.co/XLA4tvxinv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I purposely take my lunch break at weird times so I can be left alone.   Why does everyone think that’s a signal to… https://t.co/aGU4ZZis81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dboggs24 It was rocking the Plaza building.   And didn’t show up on any of the flight radar apps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four years ago today I lost my sister. It was a time I genuinely didnt think i’d get through.  But I did. And I kno… https://t.co/uzXBOkCQAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro.. I’m like.. any other morning you’d be up.. but now... Im sitting in my room waiting for her to stir!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many favorite moments! But mostly just the funny and wise things kids said!]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚🌳💚 I have to ask: who out there have I infected with my topiary contagion...obsession...addiction?  Well, for that… https://t.co/FxG7XRXpD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introducing the Self Love Project Series ❤️💕 Self love is Key 🔑Join SSE March 5th-7th as we show you the importance… https://t.co/iGX4LsgT8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rare @BNSFRailway railroad maps reveal unique Northwest history https://t.co/bX01OOa82i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manufactured crisis at border?chuckie and Nancy? Not according to your buddy Adam Schiff! War on drug cartels needs… https://t.co/SsdsbyAxP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Bacon: Bacon is EASILY the best thing to happen to McDonald’s classics. #TeamBacon in the house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re also educated, considered middle class...I don’t forget that I have these privileges.  It’s how we use our pr… https://t.co/FN5cys0w4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am drowning in midterm papers and studying. I want to scream but I have roommates so I will proceed to scream in here]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel your pain. The harder acclimation is facial hair on a sweet little face. #moms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow @JennaBushHager @SavannahGuthrie @hodakotb @craigmelvin @CarsonDaly @alroker There all funny an loved by me .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Syrian Golan to sovereign over its natural resources, including land, water and energy.  Earlier this week, UN chie… https://t.co/tewERaKxLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like a perfect place too pitch for @AwardsIcon 4 night luxury stay? 🧐🙏🏽🥰 @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/IJJuPfJCtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The crowd chanting welcome back broke me goodnight to Roman reigns only]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aangelinaxh girls used to try and say joe was the hottest 🤮 id rather die]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetroSchools @MNPSDirector  @Churchwell_Elem More readers from today! #ReadMeWeek #DrSeuss https://t.co/NXP9Kw9EKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just met someone so annoying that you just wanna shove a giant dildo in their mouth to get them to stop talking? Lol me neither 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The staff and students of @RegisCollege_MA  continue to be so grateful for this amazing opportunity to provide serv… https://t.co/w2TL15MTqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 5 phones calling for these @AllyBrooke passes. I need to reunite with my girl . See @WeLuvAllyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier It's not a requirement.  A family member was in the concert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ This is great for the climate change debate. Educate yourselves Dem candidates! It’s on! 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiclasApolloni if we expand big enough to have our own cooks and cafeteria i'll let you know ;p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colton trying to get us to believe he’s jumping fences tonight. I’m beginning to believe this fence scene never ac… https://t.co/HOD4TzwMR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol super cute!! 🥰 #goodmorning #happymonday #Repost @PupflixTweet ・・・ Sunday vibes with stitchmalamute 😂😂 #PUPFLIX… https://t.co/NZwu6AQ8Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[had to cut all the broke ass niggas out my circle to get my shit together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavenVulcans Thanks for the raid. You are awesome. Thanks for all the #lowsodiumcoalition love last night. You guys rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samhudson3 @joncoopertweets @TheDemCoalition @realDonaldTrump Fake hair ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[when your old roomie calls with news &amp; freshman year me is screaming right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some guy literally commented on my insta post and said I was obese. Let’s all laugh 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaceyMusgraves lmao all these memes are just proving we got too much time on our hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FightingWithMyFamily I just watched tonight and I can say is wow! If you bleed WWE and WWF this movie is for you!… https://t.co/UQMrTNy8EY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m easily impressed by @CrossFit athletes. But what really moves me are the adaptive athletes. Any excuse you thin… https://t.co/cis56Y8kwr]]></document></documents></author>