<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BigDaddyDore @VandyFan_ @dbellwth @TomCrean Sometimes you just shake your head and move on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@79bombi @WispresortMD @garrettchamber It definitely looks worth it for sure. There should be a little more snow come Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yn’s be raised wit both parents in they house 3 cooked meals a day and got a allowance how you gangsta ion get it😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[# yes I'm on ,Check out my new single "Like" distributed by @DistroKid and live on Spotify! https://t.co/nUUEq6f8aL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSBanuelos An interesting take on the Mexican Revolution!  Made the goal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer @realDonaldTrump YEP GET THE LAW SUITS GOING  ENACT LAWS PREVENTING THIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can read this, you’ve helped me reach 10 followers. Thank you!keep on keeping it real!]]></document><document><![CDATA[William Barr promises to protect Mueller investigation during Senate confirmation hearing https://t.co/hJDEaGhkK2 v… https://t.co/lySzOxp4uR]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the other one decided to nap on me too.... I’m still the only one around here that hasn’t had a nap today... https://t.co/laLvsS3qwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@getupgetfree @bungarsargon The Somali leaders quoted in the article being highly critical of Ilhan Omar are not "white women"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr THIS NOTE IS SUPER MARKET for ALL wants public And priVate LEGA-L TENder SUPE-R MaRkEt A WALLED MAR… https://t.co/iT9SGDunH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not many better views in high school baseball. Charter loaded, squad ready, and Headed to dry land. 2019... let’s g… https://t.co/O1hdGmIx5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[25th street eastbound at a standstill from hwy 370 to Kennedy dr. Great morning to sip your coffe and listen to you… https://t.co/FDopNT56XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Skip, we love you’: Remembering a pillar of D.C.’s punk scene https://t.co/t7h6E7QklR via @washingtonpost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 7: Texas Tech 7, #Kentucky 4. Cats need some late fireworks. https://t.co/lpC1iH5HKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ari tore up. She fuck with gervonta but yet asking herb for furniture money....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YorkshireSmash @Karma_Rx @pornoissuer @PornTheGame @newspornworld Aye aye Captain Zee https://t.co/0TYbdQrVvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night somebody asked me why do I shoot sports Photography?  __ For moments like this.. __ PARA LA CULTURA  __… https://t.co/WW9sjJZhN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aftertaste @ House of Pies Restaurant and Bakery https://t.co/z1ECeLzVa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s topic of choice is on Precision. Analyzing, planning, and clarifying your next steps in life, while remaini… https://t.co/Dl0Ig9rkHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JStein_WaPo I mean in other circumstances it would be easy to imagine it coming  from Trump or one of his supporters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smellyman59 @theopholus @icyvert2 @realDonaldTrump How could they do it legally? Is it by declaration of emergency… https://t.co/j4OpdR2gTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnyboy73 @WalshFreedom That's not how the law see it. Maybe take that up with the GOP Lawmakers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docrocktex26 The assholes who support Chump are willing to trash our democracy instead of embracing diversity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatChickMickky Damn I cant wait..! Thanks for all the info!!!!!   Im low key kinda scared now haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guadalupemagu99 te deseo un Feliz Dia De San Valentin. https://t.co/q7XiuaCknW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Answering @blondenukegirl great question - Biegun says interim confidence building steps include inspectors and lia… https://t.co/zEogmC7gAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn Basketball players look and act like fuckin drug dealers when they show up for games. Put a suit on and have some class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a7madHadi لا انا اقولك هو الموضوع يعني اذا ما سوا وبعدين يعنييي.. عيد السؤال تاني 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have beds available for men with Kentucky Medicaid. We know for a fact, there is real hope for addiction. We’re… https://t.co/H912CyDcik]]></document><document><![CDATA[It don't matter what lane I'm in. Everywhere center-exit says Zane Smith #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile @GKeile Go trump, excellent tweet!   I read that like the opening of the movie 300 when the guy wa… https://t.co/WQo62FPLpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliecanales_ If you ever need help with anything vegan in the Fresno/Clovis area just ask!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss the Pocahontas Gun Show March 16 &amp; 17 at the expo! https://t.co/z2SuKYav8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beeboobopbip @OfficerTrevorT @ChrisMurphyCT @Alyssa_Milano Hell; there are Venezuelans in the caravan and at the B… https://t.co/rak6sDArif]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Make Peace in Afghanistan? Moscow Has Some Lessons https://t.co/MKm4yz9aaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @docrocktex26 We wonder why #ThisIsAmerica won a Grammy. This is what it’s come to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[pro tip: use jet lag to get back to a 5AM routine, works especially well from Europe to East coast USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[PIAA 4A Tournament Preview: @TepPanthers are defending champions, have won 6 state titles since 2009. Donta Scott (… https://t.co/iNnVwB151t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone down for some Mac &amp; Cheese? HMM? I had a cup of it with my dinner, and it’s great and flavorful! YUM YUM! 🍝🧀😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps a visual clue? Maybe pay site links could be green while free site links remain blue?]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Veloster N review course Ming today! Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s Rides! hyundaigi… https://t.co/mUmjGcUv4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to DC and the #Batman creators and all the Artist references I used to create this, I Call this #Batmen I… https://t.co/BzCVIuddjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I crack myself up... I must be getting sleepy and my voice is about done LOL Listen to me sing "I Want To Hold Your… https://t.co/EgTIFdHPq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[No driving, no sleeping. Live it up like it's the weekend. https://t.co/Ve4jDnQ64D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judblessed @RoyBlunt Robert Mueller’s mandate was to investigate collusion AND “any matters that arose or may aris… https://t.co/DGtldr8bCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tats for Life. w/ my #BabyGirl wanderingsyd @garbage 🗿🌴💀 @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/pIXQ73JaVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackroomSteve @stareinthesun Damn I just realized we been blowin up Tyler’s phone going back and forth. Sorry homie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstooltweetss When russ said "ima fuck you and ya wife up" 😂😂 https://t.co/6DAhPv2eCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codeofvets @MapYourSuccess Agreed 100%. Thanks for all you do. Waiting on Trump to eradicate but I am ready for in… https://t.co/BCblEDvcS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Seventh woods is balling like the high school days 😂😂😂@SeventhWoods23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrimDominic Hillary started the birther BS! she and the MSM projected her lies onto trump.. which he researched an… https://t.co/x8Bkh3JZp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow up question- How big would the kite have to be to lift me up off the ground?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaiyakiAlter @BulliedinHS ill never forget when you were like anti-porn and anti-horny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein He probably won’t get the wall, as bad as we need it. cause democrats are spending all their time try… https://t.co/fxlOsGzaEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleveland and Washington just playoffs tbh. Both can mess around and not even make the playoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron Holiday &amp; TJ Leaf making improvements this season is a great sight. #Pacers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckeyOn @mlemons1970 @WoodheadAndy @DonaldJTrumpJr Do you think that explains anything I’ve said? The government… https://t.co/DBSu1ZWwlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NefCanuck @FisherJillian It’s the text of the banner and the stillframe that capture it, more so than the team   T… https://t.co/kxbOyIz3Kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimnburbank @NancySinatra @POTUS44 You should read the article. Congress, 2007.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Lopsided to the other side. Both Ws but they were clearly lopsided games. I have only been playing Black Ops 4… https://t.co/NS6Srxs1PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPfromGV @a_jello_84 @BaldZero @EvanDryll @whiteman6293 I’m low key upset I wasn’t included in this tweet consider… https://t.co/b1w42YeC7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAST CHANCE TO ENTER! Your chance to win over $1600 in prizes from @ammunitiondepot @Stagarms @blckriflecoffee… https://t.co/VDszhFopb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monsone87 @achs_fred There were multiple organizations this season who thought Brandon Manning would be a benefici… https://t.co/Aej9twh82S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ascschoenberg @boulezian @Ford It had a 12 cylinder engine, I presume.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@croatiaheritage https://t.co/Qtnu4nLQQC Catholic, Orthodox, Muslim are all being influenced by fascism today! That is scary!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun time last night redribbongala #tulsacares @ Cox Business Center Tulsa https://t.co/sy5fXzKg8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SummitHSBball @wcsSHS @wcsSHSAthletics @SummitSquad @wcsCOjq @andersen_marli @ellieecolson Congrats ladies! Love t… https://t.co/KiTxY8U58j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerenceDavisJr put that man on a poster! 👀🔥😱😱🏀 #DunkoftheYear @SportsCenter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how “Welcome to the Black Parade” is about 500x better than “Bohemian Rhapsody”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoooo fucking fosters home for imaginary friends is on Hulu, no one speak to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone remember this:  If California, one state, was removed from the election of 2016.  Trump won the electoral… https://t.co/eDl3Q0iHjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Worker, Maintenance - https://t.co/3K4hyPuo29 #Simon #FacilitiesMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rocktuber Yo pondría . 1 a la banda. 2 regueton. La pieza de mano del dentista es un sonido maravilloso... tanto q… https://t.co/yX5udLZWBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok so Piech's one-off obviously is gonna be something Atlantic-inspired, then. They've been doing social posts on t… https://t.co/hnsNDt8RV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP senators fuming over Trump comments on Warmbier https://t.co/DM8GdeSL7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[The proles are demanding Dunkin Donuts for breakfast, but we are holding firm against their demands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @lsubasketball with get_repost ・・・ Coming in as the #SCTop10 No. 1 play is kavell6ft11 at the buzzer 💪🏼… https://t.co/SLaR72FXaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can the White River Lady Tigers make it State for the 1st Time since 1992? Tomorrow evening we shall find out!… https://t.co/LgTfuHZoxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti I think all the impersonations on SNL are weak, even Alec's. Not likely to see Davidson's, but you… https://t.co/P1DHJ9tujM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#leavingneverland @StinsonHunter was really eye opening. How could we normalize this that type of behavior 🤷🏻‍♀️😞I’… https://t.co/ZegljnjCWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe AOC gave us a hint when she said "if you're 80 or older you have lived and nice full life" what the hell does… https://t.co/KOdtrdgt1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wordofgod #odcsuffolk #pastorpeaks @ Suffolk, Virginia https://t.co/dZQoIvBKHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again to @PeelPoliceMedia 11 Division for a very informative ride-along last night in #MississaugaLakeshore.… https://t.co/TLuZq7DTx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IllinoisStateU besides being a great district @DesertSandsUSD here is another great reason to visit our table. https://t.co/Tkpafe8ayX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Lakers fans are going to rip him apart if they don’t make the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachRous @JonMeyerWNEP @WNEP Coach, I think you gave him the shirt. 👍🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC get me kicked off Twitter you crooked C*** https://t.co/7nnAdrObOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump How funny Jerry Falwell refers to “nuts”. Evidently, no mirrors in his one dimensional house. Sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelgclump negotiating with Dunder Mifflin during the MSPC buy out is brilliance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fbiradio @FBI_Agent https://t.co/pjtbmPHEsT Q&amp;A with Tim Jones, president of Innovative Support Service @ch9… https://t.co/8nkhGxjAhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Have you lost your brans and guts to stand up to Russian AGENT Traitor Trump. You act as a double faced stooge to Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllSportsAZ1 @Suns now if he could just hit an open jump shot, then we're cookin with gasoline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyWatsonX That is fantastic Tiffany &amp; can’t ask for anything more ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo if you were ever affected by my anti-social tendencies I just wanna day rn I’m srry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzywol @SamUlmschneider Yes. I skimmed through it and had the same thought. And I think it was an AP class! Too… https://t.co/pYkEUIrY5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAwesomeRyan7 @ZacStevensBSN If only someone reported this at the combine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @Twitter @IlhanMN Your level of ignorance only exceeds your privilege because it has to come through th… https://t.co/9zxAR6wlqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien It''s time for Sarah's family to make her a reservation at a looney bin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYRangers Like putting what we acquired first makes a difference 😡 Clueless Jeff is  ruining this team let’s trade… https://t.co/NzZloiFbFA]]></document></documents></author>