<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ItsOptionalFSK @TreyWallace_ @Vol_Hoops @FOXSportsKnox Props to The Incredible Fulk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I didn’t play the hand I was dealt, I changed my cards. I prayed to the skies and I changed my stars”   https://t.co/MSvV2Y7KiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister my guess was a Big Mac Omelet with cheese stuffed inside a KFC Thigh smothered in gravy &amp; a side of Ketchup...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VerbalBequeath @HeavyTankZA This isn't Marvel Studios. This is a Fox Marvel Movie. This is their second time bring… https://t.co/1mIIt0HRut]]></document><document><![CDATA[#haitiprecisadeajuda #invadiravenezuela #bozonaro #morojuizpolitico #politica #ajudahumanitaria #morocaboeleitoral… https://t.co/xa4d0mKAzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work sucked but I came home to Desmond and my cats and I feel way better]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤💛🖤💛 🐏 🏀 🏀 💪🏽 YASSS!!  #LetsGoVCU  @VCU_Hoops @VCURamNation  @VCUHorns  https://t.co/NCqhMXGHgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @83TXOCHAIR ALL JEWISH VOTERS IN THE STATE OF SOUTH CAROLINA, VOTE REPUBLICAN, WE HAVE BEEN SOLD OUT BY T… https://t.co/See4tVhfcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hope Kim shows you his flamethrower trick.  You do realize he burns people alive, right? Totally… https://t.co/rBDk0GsFzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Underrated. #mikeclevinger #cleveland #indians #mlb #baseball #topps #clevelandindians #pitcher #underrated… https://t.co/H7N4KcWwqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Yes! Thank you. Finally some candidates are taking this on. Our country has too much wealth to not ha… https://t.co/WuH7jKGosJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeraBoross @SealTeamcbsfans @SEALTeamCBS @NeilBrownJr @David_Boreanaz @SEALTeamBrigade @SEALteamFans… https://t.co/VGryDKVCTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was so much fun! Thank you @BrundageMagic for coming to FHSU! You were amazing! 😊 https://t.co/h5vItrOkMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC He ought to be sued for social security employers tax for hiring illegal immigrants.?? Why nothing happens to him as employer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonesy ties it up again! He’s on fire 🔥 @nllwarriors @MitchJones74 12-12! #nllwarriors #vanvssas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Batches in rotation, lol 🍋💛 #limoncello #homemade #lovemyworkstation #bottlingday #peelingday #lemonlove… https://t.co/MhTfjQsh4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impishchimp @Hmmmmm_Really I think she just likes being in the spotlight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️ #coffee #coffeehaert #coffeebreak #espresso #latteart #coffeegram #cappucino  #coffeeaddict #coffeelife… https://t.co/AQaV5oU1gl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diver and friend @ Historic Overland Park, Overland Park https://t.co/ki3boHjr0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy mf birthday to the baddest bitch in the game @juliablevinss i love you w all my heart ❤️ this weekend it’s badd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 24 yr old son tried to convince me since day one, but I always had an excuse not to. Finally gave in and I’m hoo… https://t.co/1wqqHm6UuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best feeling: getting in the shower when it’s cold  Worst feeling: getting out of the shower when it’s cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We never give them the time of day! They will answe for their lies and not being honest with the p… https://t.co/RFE7coJyNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was cheering from my couch! So freaking proud of you @615nickson #govols #didireallyjustsaygovols]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCPSelscienceTS “Blending” old with new is what I call #ClassroomChic 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agitpopworld @robreiner The real crisis is at our border! The fake stuff is everything the dems do to detract from… https://t.co/7kTZz2jP91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throw Back Thursday   Choose to be the best YOU can be. – Give it your all in everything you do, commit to your goa… https://t.co/JCKmC9NSSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredrikSewell So happy she won! I’ve loved her since the first time I saw her in Broadchurch (we Americans have be… https://t.co/hwQyc1u5v3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dinahellen Unfortunately, he is a protege of Cornell West. Who did he vote for, if not Hillary? Also, a lot of ver… https://t.co/SGolVDN6qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[H Finance members did seem perplexed that @GovRaimondo would single out this industry -Very accurate reporting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwgop Along with the entire Trump regime and those on Fox News advocating civil war if he’s impeached.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, thank you for opening my eyes to understand the enormity of your sacrifice on my behalf. Thank you that I can… https://t.co/5DKDRdrALF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@portilloboss que te mejores de aquellito saludos facebook live @keibron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tint, spoiler, matte black wheels, roof spoiler, chin spoiler, rose gold ponies, and rose gold/black interior 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miss__tisa @Blexit2020 @2018MAGAMidTrmT @realDonaldTrump Yes, Southern California!! 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWSchank @faithfulfamlies @JeffPassage @realDonaldTrump You’re a Democrat and think abortion is ok? No wonder you’re so nutty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now onto presentation of the #SB89 by @HeidiGansert #SafeVoice https://t.co/azNwKqKbxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Given Por Ahi... Thalia love her songs... #thalia @avonrep_online #solo #🎤 @avonrep_online Hope you enjoy!!! 💋💋💋💋💋💋… https://t.co/7rlGBdKwHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usatodayopinion @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows I believe every word Cohen said about trump waiting for the seventh ci… https://t.co/tbpdjlTVrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#buonsanvalentino Io ho un po' di nostalgia del viaggio a Los Angeles. E preparando la recensione di Vivo nex dual… https://t.co/5nHSumPwnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the weather really is as bad as they say I’m going to be that person that makes somebody come out and deliver so… https://t.co/UQ9FS74O6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @gehrig38 The ones that created un uproar over the Confederate Flag]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ELA students are rockstars! Watching their marketing presentations come alive with research, advertisements with… https://t.co/OJD6xbV2ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiezak_ is the most talented human I know! there I said it! would die for her! https://t.co/UHNt61rOSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh your mom takes care of your kid more than you do ? Eeeee don’t call yourself a mom sis ....   &amp; that’s the #tea 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yes, I will troll you on your birthday, Mentor.   @JLCS06, you really gotta love Missy. She dropped this on you… https://t.co/y4ITYXN9Ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can it please stop being so cold in LA, I’m tiredddddttt. https://t.co/e7p9qO7UKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope my character is based off of how well i can walk in heels. which is not very well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si me duermo a las 12 despierto a las 4, si me duermo a las 2 despierto a las 6... Siento que me volveré loca si sigo durmiendo así 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been listening to this song nonstop for 24 hours and it simultaneously makes me want to burst into tears and h… https://t.co/IIw40fY8Ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to people riding their bikes everywhere. Saving our planet and making ATL traffic a little less worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio Starting with your wife that spent $850m on a project &amp; cant produce one receipt!#SwampRats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVNews Hemp and Bamboo grow faster and produce more paper products.  They should be used to help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZMyersOfficial 😍 I always love PRS guitars. The bird inlays have always particularly made them stand out for me, b… https://t.co/9v1trCx9qV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LocalIdaho A friend of mine just commented that this would be funnier if it wasn’t true. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Mobile De… https://t.co/Ps4CfSGPND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Design by @fabianandmom305 Palazzo pants high and low Denim trim top ready for jazz in the gardens to purchase come… https://t.co/OeabP5yMfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this clever there's something wrong with you. https://t.co/PNPuSGGrPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALarremore I obviously won’t be able to be there, but what is this for? I’d love to pick your brains sometime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need you all to know that the church I grew up in called making out “heavy petting”.   HEAVY PETTING.   IS THIS A PETTING ZOO???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramon1234 @MartinezJerrry this is what Mrs. Ramon heard on the other side of the door 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole22___ LMAO u ab to have a shit ton of ladies in ur DM’s now 😂😂 but yeah only way I’ll be there is if it’s th… https://t.co/uuGMjdn3wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She loathed sin both in herself and others and strove to avoid it, not from fear of hell but from the fear of disp… https://t.co/VfMeKyCAau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayle_lynne @TinseltownPR Animal abusers should be put in jail and the key thrown away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi Nancy-get your head out of your ass and get this wall built!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump USED to be the envy of the world.  NOW we are the LAUGHING stock of the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me reading the antibiotics I took over a week ago will fuck my system up for 2 weeks to 6 months....*mainlines prob… https://t.co/3RWcqBqMy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr82btnvol That was my Halloween costume for school last year. https://t.co/Iep3JpXjvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sinir/Siz Highways Performance Space and Gallery #santamonica #sinirsiz Discount Tickets: https://t.co/euIweDk9Df https://t.co/g3VsGMZ1Kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love a good run. Today I aimed for a 20 min run and then suddenly felt very light and in a good head space. So ende… https://t.co/4AghNWAvZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hugostar77 @rubengluengas El mundo necesita periodistas sinceros y justos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RacingGeek10 @Summerbrooke23 Most driver accounts I follow always have whoever say it’s PR. With exception of the Bubba Pollard tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a deep dive into Big Oil’s fight against the electric vehicle tax credit @EENewsUpdates https://t.co/yiaGevmL3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like on the phone I’m like talking oh wait you go and then I start talking and  then they start talking and I’m all like wtfkdsjzhuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_com @DanielleRyanJ Communism, a threat that is not going to ever happen to Americans nor Russians. Hands tampin… https://t.co/SjAP86CSZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarragan I trully felt as you were a blessing today at the homeland security hearing!!! you are awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRayBlackXXX @mikequasar @TheSamanthaMack @TheSBWagency @PrinceYahshua You know I ain’t lying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyss_martin What you didn’t bring your second grade teacher and a bill for a landline?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmiller_FSTS @eduprotocols To start I’m going to use the template off the @eduprotocols website. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunkindonuts I’m not feeling the rebranding of Dunkin’ Donuts   They are pushing their ‘signature coffees’ and cut… https://t.co/y8KwwvkwBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mingled with you amongst the stars. Before we were born.   I’ve missed you ever since.  I’m unable to find home w… https://t.co/yhaQjPAHSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Great Falls police, assisted by Great Falls Fire Rescue, set up a perimeter around the refinery and th… https://t.co/HVzlnecuSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @cvpayne #EYES WIDE OPEN Thank you Charles we love you Charles Payne telling it like it is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baddie_influenc @RVAdirt Also the misogynistic bent of the msm has to be factored into this story. 2016 gave them… https://t.co/FpjIEjuZNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr Ham radio stuff mostly. I've also got a bunch of different transistors and ferrite cores.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Food Service Worker - Bloomsburg Univ." at Aramark by asking for referrals. It's a… https://t.co/hbbEfVrysv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to have made my office’s Top 20 list again, out of over 100 agents! I’m so grateful to all of my clients,… https://t.co/p1kyQoD3W5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lesson for today: Always be trueful to yourself even if it seems complicated or unwanted!  Billions of mixed feelin… https://t.co/mPgy9ks5dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also when you fit the exact standard of beauty and fail to recognize that, you tweet shit like this. Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulBabeuAZ @ImmoralReport @realDonaldTrump Meanwhile @cnnbrk shows this version and claims babies are being torn… https://t.co/S6ZmvwG2sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang This is VERY delicate territory for those of us who are believers in the New Testament. Hate and Isr… https://t.co/BzbLAY42LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey hope you have good day, and oh if you read this you look so pretty today🌎❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lake #snow #wakefieldlake #outdoors #bench @ Lake Quannapowitt https://t.co/TCgGEFQwey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtney0874 @MHEnetwork That is a fair point. I didn’t support RTT legislation at the state or federal level, but… https://t.co/fdg2DdOAst]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Paul's Chapel in #newyorkcity #nyctravels #travelgram #travelphoto #churches #iconicbuildings #landmarks #nyc @… https://t.co/4zS5A5IBis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit link in bio and signup today! Review all the benefits! 👩🏻‍⚕️  For coaching and psychotherapy visit… https://t.co/n2KTxJFXn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caved and purchased the nca live feed...mostly just to watch ECE J5, Maine Stars Glory, ECE M5, and WCSS, so y’all… https://t.co/McxNX5JwIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m cautiously optimistic about the United Methodist Church- can’t we all just get along?#UMCGC19]]></document><document><![CDATA[When asked WHY the bill is needed, Farley-Bouvier said: “There isn't any other small business that gets to pay thei… https://t.co/MkOlWMB30S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardhouz13 He may see the inside of a psych center though...he is definitely mentally ill.]]></document></documents></author>