<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan Yes the wall is an emergency our country was invaded by 400,000 illegals through our southern border. Build… https://t.co/VhhurXg2D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere at my moms house in Scottsdale I still have a copy of the first Umbrella Academy comic book from 2007.  I… https://t.co/ZI90XQejzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone seen Oprah yet? Has anyone at all asked them why they decided to sue, and now appeal? But I do believe t… https://t.co/x1lsvBff0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medit8now @JillWineBanks @SRuhle Check Out Those Boots!!! Rocking it @JillWineBanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backdoorviews @FAANews I’m sure. What’s the penalty for flying over someone who’s not participating in the operation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This group of girls ❤️❤️❤️ #CAmmitted #teammeal @ Fazoli's https://t.co/FcjgGrMohq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast How are you remaining sober Molly? If you do meetings, you might need one after this.  I wouldn't ha… https://t.co/bJLGhZ1KCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an example what 8 years of having a Muslin President Obama. He lied to get in office !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because he signs Bibles. #SHAME #TrumpIsADisgrace  What do you think? https://t.co/SJlsE9793h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you uncthahunk dopeeraonline @MistahFAB for continuing to support #localbusinesses #entrepreneurs #literacy… https://t.co/KER01fhejx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: Gender bent DEH, Dear Eva Hansen, a story of one woman’s self realization journey after the trag… https://t.co/QozJfWhMTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdviceFromNo @40calsolution @DelSchilling This racist piece of shit!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatfemmfatale @KelceyAnya Kelcey please get the first one. It’ll be amaze on you. Thanks, management.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@britshaniece Yeah , what happened ?? You hate it when niggahs bring you to the facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LizzLuna13 bitch lmao you’re going out next weekend, i ain’t even gnna get my ticket anymore you and @AaronSandoval10 are dangerous 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[WARNING: Neighbors say pair tried to lure kids into car twice in one day: https://t.co/ntW6TCnQCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuitNutrition @BradCLemley I gained weight trying BPC for a week a few years ago, just as an experiment. 😜 Of cour… https://t.co/HJGVibM0sT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just  - never get it with some people - me either.....  #giveitup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bei took this broken branch up the tree with him yesterday. Was he attempting to reattach it? Nope, he left it hang… https://t.co/dOLFokiNxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MathNerdCoop @LiteracyLizVB @crystal_wilky @Thalia_Elem She’s so darned cute it’s RIDICULOUS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[From: 40404 (1/3) @brandy1960: RT @CASTORFAVELO: NUEVAS PALABRAS  1-TENEMOS 20 AŃOS (2/3) EN ESTO QUE ES UN MES , A… https://t.co/JPDV1uNnGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Banalization @TheoTypes @MedillSchool But I will say this, making broad assumptions about people because of where… https://t.co/wEMm3L8IRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saturday #eastvillagenyc #phoebenewyork @ East Village, Manhattan https://t.co/lTbM6P0bap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucks to know that a hard working possibly mid major school is going to miss the tournament because someone else is… https://t.co/SZ2v2fqi6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaggsclarke @YouTube @AmazingLovelyGM @CanadianSyrup @mrshutch123 @sandytvj @a_g_m_f_63 @MrsGeorgiosP @MyAnchorGM… https://t.co/gCb3N8Wtp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GillPill77 @deeber225 @nkn03 @jerseygolden Yes that is happening but not taking my code I’ll keep trying - we’ll see!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ate a Caesar salad for dinner. From a kit. With all of the recent recalls, I'm feeling super badass. Worst cas… https://t.co/YQkY3oiFzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FUCKINGBRI Believe In yourself Bri stay positive keep thinking “i will get this job” be confident in yourself and… https://t.co/CcR1MFBkgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janice_freeman @NBCTheVoice Rest in peace, Janice.  You have earned your angel wings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattkatz00 @Fahrenthold @shanedkavanaugh @Oregonian Re: the Saudi students who have avoided prosecution,  I bet  4… https://t.co/01ECN0lpMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Na but if i know you busy working and/or i’m busy working then we know we gon speak when we can. i ain’t sweating i… https://t.co/5yhvGBOddC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamaubrian But like 2 or 3 in the morning, right? still night for me! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casting Directors are your allies. They want to help you nail your audition! https://t.co/80rj9AQp9C via @tipsonacting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewCash @NatObserver It's also frightening, but vital to read. We are playing with fire by  allowing SNC-Lavali… https://t.co/z2rkpky25J]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I went out in my #harleyquinn #dress #redandblackdress #harleyquinndress #blondehair #feltpretty #hadfun #girl… https://t.co/7Bor4C7wtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsBabyBer @benandjerrys You go get @ClementinesSTL because it’s better ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loogan640 I was thinking that too until I saw this 😹 https://t.co/MvYgC0iHPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for standing up for children and their families. “A breastfeeding baby” taking from mother]]></document><document><![CDATA[has anyone thought that @scheana is gonna look like @LeeAnneLocken when she’s older? Just me? Ok cool. #vanderpumprules #rhod]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf: *doesn’t respond to any of my snapchats, texts, or dm’s*  Me: ok he’s prolly just chillin nbd  Me: *doesn’t… https://t.co/W9vFEtkCc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH @ USAID event: Development aid is a hand-up not a hand-out (and I would argue so is humanitarian aid in most cas… https://t.co/DFbJQdmfyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeeisforBeer @ChiBrewseum @Sketchbookbrew Great to meet you, Sarah. And thanks for coming...cheers to you! 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen 1- Guessing by choice words he's sucking up, saying the judge is God and he's "repented" for his sins… https://t.co/htSl1VALqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the best investment at this point is to design robots that can take care of the remaining animals who survi… https://t.co/yPI9dAzHP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was walking through the casino last night with brie and jordan and mind you were all buzzed and some girl looked… https://t.co/Nhb1ljcxvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm motivated by trying to understand what the truth is, -Lara Logan, Television Journalist.  #MABshow… https://t.co/yQdJuEzYVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to burst out laughing. traffic sign meme | Lane fail traffic sign wtf cool stuff tumblr funny pics the… https://t.co/wjZv5Do656]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told myself i wouldn’t look at Oscars twitter because the locals rooting for Gaga and borhap would just make me m… https://t.co/GYtjjh3TGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day dinner! ♥️❤️ (@ House of Pies in Los Angeles, CA w/ @thegreatwax) https://t.co/rFKKO8oyxL https://t.co/uPjcVqnOJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[👊 Great training today caio_terra_academy #ufc #mma #bjj #caioterrabjj #ufcnashville #flyweight @ Caio Terra BJJ https://t.co/2vvBQzU9qy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @LulaMayBeHolly @tweetMalena I fucking don't want to win a twitter fight,how petty,I want to have tha… https://t.co/5IF185GxUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWald67239418 @cspanwj @RepThompson Guess nitpicking typos applies here to WALDO  People Who Constantly Point Out… https://t.co/WQTJRuzSMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USRepKeating @SpeakerPelosi @RepLynch A true life story happening today in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania in February of… https://t.co/9Nca2eJoeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyCurtis68 @PGar58 @gemcos12 @kckittie13 @BostonSprtsNews @polarbear52710 @GettyBosSports @jade78052492… https://t.co/PwO3KbJxdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csmunday @CaptainSuburb @unionwill @ChannelMgtow @kiteie @RobertFife You are talking through your hat. I know many… https://t.co/JhRScD3yy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@remosmith17 Omg please you can do my makeup all day I will be your canvas I volunteer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I’m in a gc (actually 2 now) and I have found a roomie and my SWEETmates 😭🐾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBabylonBee @SUPERRANGO73 Ilan Omar is a disgrace !! PELOSI should remove her from the foreign relations committ… https://t.co/je65hQTJul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally the best show on the planet. Been a bunch of times and it wasn’t enough. 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[*sharing a bed with Josee  Josee: “you just made my armpit itch huh weirdo”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlossmoorHills #littlefreelibrary is full of all new books! Come check it out! ❤️📚🦅 https://t.co/HTt7ANqTQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I taught myself to laugh in uncomfortable situations because it’s more comfortable than feeling uneasy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It started out as promoting socialism so whatever you choose to call it now, it was socialism that didn't work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tishrich @TaraMartinEDU Last year was seriously insane! 💥🙌🏼 they put us in the BIG room this year so that the 🔥Fir… https://t.co/j0S2mjMNpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chatshys @shibabalnakba you got me f*CKED up yo drop ur location i wanna talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faucets dripping...again. is it really going to be spring in 2 weeks? Indy hasn't gotten the memo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night with #Templekids He makes His presence evident whether we have 2 or 10! #Heleftthe99… https://t.co/snrrtuzDhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doraguevarat @GrantORourke Or when there's a sock or two missing its mate. Blame it on the washing machine eating… https://t.co/Qb9KbZ07Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proverbs 18:22 New King James Version (NKJV) 22 He who finds a wife finds a good thing, And obtains favor from the Lord.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arwen and her piggy 🐖. #arwenwillow @ St. Louis https://t.co/GqzjSp2S7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Errand Three: Laundry! Giving Top Kat in Berlin a try. @ Top Kat Super Laundromat Deming Rd. https://t.co/AKrYJbsL80]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I sat in church yesterday I thought about all that we are able to do as humans.  We make choices everyday.  We a… https://t.co/lqY229PEu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertPicardo This administration is so depressing and glad I have #StartrekVoyager to watch to take my mind off t… https://t.co/alMNGMdsz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my reaction to when people honk at me even though i’m the one that cut them off https://t.co/HbilWYnCds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk cause I be like “should I go to the mall” then I’m like “nah I’ll buy something online.”I just be going back an… https://t.co/Lemk6GRJCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rob Thomas - Someday (Official Video) https://t.co/zA0yOjBpX4 via @YouTube    #robthomas #someday #faith]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 days  til the #Oscars where this #beautifulman will be presenting so i will be counting down with a new pic of th… https://t.co/eJarnRJkTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm ready to go to dalhart tx for the weekend yasss!!#Friyay🤘🤗 #weekendvibes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovrega @QuesaVerdades Mmm si yo se que no estoy falseando información, que las cifras que estoy dando como gobier… https://t.co/J53qKpkgZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You remember when he taped your daddy talking about the hush payments? Golly Jr, u can’t possibly be that dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2 Thank u for sharing this story. Please help put pressure on Legislation 2 change the laws 2 make senseless v… https://t.co/ah8xi6RqOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friends cousin from Mexico is here and this fool wants to MARRY me tonight since he leaves tomorrow... omg lmfao!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dperkins01 @GenoBiscontePA And those whiska’ treats too please. Been a long trip I’m too tired to stop. She prefer… https://t.co/Wk3mXmlVUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustineBateman I say if they don't like the way I look, then don't look at all. If my husband told me I needed a f… https://t.co/DzF3pk2swS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is like night and day going from cheap conditioner to salon-standard conditioner when it comes to brushing hair.… https://t.co/Bin04GSglk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Unfiltered Wheat Beer by @Boulevard_Beer at @greatwolflodge — https://t.co/uDQm9NEzRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Right... cause murdering babies, men sucking each other’s penis, starting the kkk, changing the narr… https://t.co/JRtDvY1llz]]></document><document><![CDATA[THERE’S VIDEO OF YOU BRO WITH A 14 YR OLD GIRL AND YOU PEEING ON HER, IN WHAT WORLD ARE YOU INNOCENT?!?! I’LL WAIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A special thank you to Paul Schlegel from the @FarmBureau Public Policy team for stopping by to talk to our Young F… https://t.co/UUxVcxS2C7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashiRafael que decepción abrir la pagina del ministerio de trabajo y ver la pobreza de programas que tienen... do… https://t.co/XX4PLglrEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to my awesome boyfriend robgagee for teaching us how to snowboard 🏂❄️💙💙Aidan is off to a great start...me no… https://t.co/JTUZUWDV8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[tem um @ que eu sinto até prazer de conversar por que ele eh o único americano q eu conheço que escreve direitinho e ainda poe pontuações 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks I want u to know that your store in Brentwood (LA) always plays musicals in the morning and it is the highlight of my day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an inspiring story. Tenacity, passion, and entrepreneurship rule the day! @AIMBusinessNews @Friends_Roxbury Th… https://t.co/qB5NsIcAc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me crazy......FINE❤️🙌🏀 #justdoit #nike #breakingbarriers #girlpower @EdnieshaCurry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m loving Disco though, I don’t get the people who don’t think it’s Star Trek. I grew up with TNG reruns with my g… https://t.co/yEJBIOWEJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My short list, that I retreat to when live gets overwhelming includes, first Bridget Jones, Panic Room, Enough, Whi… https://t.co/UzvdSgz4EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnthemcnamara @albinokid @startrekcbs @StarTrekNetflix So true. Discovery has made me a "defend unto death" fan.… https://t.co/wqNJZ1PF2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The road back home for Berwick Fire Capt. Joel Barnes was filled with well wishers Sunday, honoring the man who gav… https://t.co/umGf1e6d7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterMoments @IAmSophiaNelson SOME BUILDINGS MUST BE TORN DOWN SO SOMETHING ELSE CAN BE BUILT BETTER. https://t.co/OzXRYmQ74s]]></document></documents></author>